<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 23:33:29 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 23:33:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Beginner’s Guide to Using Static Site Generators For Creating Superior Websites</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I began to look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/45118/guide-to-host-website-github-pages&quot;&gt;creating my own website&lt;/a&gt;, I ran across quite a few blogs advising me to use a static site generator like &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://middlemanapp.com/&quot;&gt;Middleman&lt;/a&gt;. The problem was, no one bothered to explain in layman’s terms what a static site generator &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt;. How am I supposed to work with something when I don’t even know why it’s useful? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some research, I found out that static site generators are tremendously promising tools that can deliver a superior website, though they require a tremendous amount of upfront work as well. Consider this your introduction to static site generators and why they’re important. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-beginners-guide-to-static-site-generators&quot;&gt;The Beginner’s Guide to Static Site Generators&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-a-static-site&quot;&gt;What is a static site?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, let’s define a static site. Websites can be generally divided into two categories- static and dynamic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A static website is one that is designed, stored and delivered to the user as-is. It doesn’t change between the point when you hit save and when the user clicks on it. You write the HTML, format it with CSS, and upload the page to your server. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dynamic websites, conversely, are constructed by a server-side controller that can substitute content into the site through another program. A simple example of this is WordPress. You use a simple browser-based interface to input content and the server backend renders it on a webpage dynamically using PHP. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dynamic web pages are useful for hosting updated content and adding content through a simpler interface than raw HTML. Imagine running a blog in a static format where you have to hand-code every new post from scratch- talk about a nightmare. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each type of website has its own advantages. Dynamic websites tend to be capable of more fancy stuff than their static counterparts, as well as being easier to manage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, static websites are cheap to store, easy to build, and load much faster. If you’re making a website without a lot of dynamic or interactive elements, it’s worth looking at using a static site of HTML, CSS and some JavaScript. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where mobile devices are quickly becoming the dominant type of device people use to browse the web, having a fast and lightweight website is crucially important. Users’ attention spans grow shorter every year, and every second your site spends loading that super cool client-side scripting increases the chances users will bail. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web designers also have a tendency to over-design. You can add in a bunch of crazy scripts, but you probably shouldn’t. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should make your website as simple as possible for the sake of good design and loading quickly. Look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://bettermotherfuckingwebsite.com&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; and tell me they don’t have a point. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-a-static-site-generator&quot;&gt;What is a static site generator?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A static site generator is a set of tools for building static websites automatically based on a set of input files. You give it some text files and content, and the generator will give you back a complete website. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this guide, we’ll just look at using &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, the static site generator cooked up by one of the founders of GitHub. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Jekyll, you have a set of nested templates. Each one has a bit of content you’ll put on every webpage. For example, head.html has a bit of code the generator will paste into the head of every HTML page you create. Change head.html and you change the head of every HTML page. This makes updating and managing the site infinitely easier. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole generation system works like this. You leave holes in the HTML pages and put in special placeholders that tell the generator what to fill in there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-do-i-generate-content&quot;&gt;How do I generate content?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content comes when you feed in specially formatted .markdown files. Markdown is a special markup language that is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/44197/write-in-markdown-on-wordpress&quot;&gt;amazing for blogging&lt;/a&gt;. You can type in plain English with a few symbols for formatting and the computer converts it into HTML. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the top of every .markdown file for your content, you also must put an info box. Enter it like this: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
layout: post
title: title here
---
Content starts here
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everthing between those sets of three dashes won’t appear within the body of the story but is instead accessed as a variable. If you look within your other page templates, you might see: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Beginner’s Guide to Using Static Site Generators For Creating Superior Websites&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tells the static site generator to substitute whatever you put after the colon beside “title” in each individual post. That way you can define a page title once within the text and the generator pastes it everywhere in the HTML for you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The really cool part is that you can roll your own variables and use those to substitute in content. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I started putting together a blog with links to all my old stories. My HTML template has a link at the bottom of every page with “Original Link” as a link. The code looks like this: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/45284/beginners-guide-static-site-generators&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&amp;gt;Original Story&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this case, the generator knows to fill in whatever link I define under “original: (link)” in every post to substitute there. Simple, and so much more efficient than manual editing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the real reward of static site generators. They’re an absolute pain to set up and get right, but once they’re ready adding new content and maintaining the system is incredibly easy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully this helped clear up some differences between static and dynamic websites and why it matters. Static websites have tremendous potential, especially in a mobile-first world. A good website that’s done the work to set up its static generator could do well. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/05/ssgSetup.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/05/ssgSetup.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>web,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>technorms,</category>
        
        <category>guide</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building paves over snake habitat</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auburn University shattered an unusual ecological system when it gave land for a new medical college, leaving only “fragments,” according to John Kush, research fellow in the School of Forestry and Wildlife Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Edward Via College of Osteopathic Medicine building, which began construction in February 2013, sits atop 15 of 21 acres in a plot of land which Kush said was managed by the School of Forestry and Wildlife Sciences since the 1950s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Most people didn’t realize (the site) had a remarkable amount of what an ecologist might call residual biodiversity,” said Sharon Hermann, assistant professor of biological sciences. “The natural native ecosystem was not really intact, but there were a surprising number of individuals scattered around, of both plants and animals, that were once there 200-300 years ago.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hermann said the VCOM site was useful because it showed the Southeast as it existed in the past. The site held animals and plants such as trillium, mayapple and the cardinal flower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hermann said she and her students also found eastern kingsnakes on the property. According to her field notes, her undergraduate students spotted the snakes four times between Oct. 28, 2012, and June 30, 2013. The eastern kingsnake is a protected species in the state of Alabama, according to Craig Guyer, professor of biological sciences and the herpetologist who positively identified the snakes found by the students. Guyer said the black-and-white-banded serpents have been hard to find in the Southeastern United States since the early 1980s, though they are not federally protected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kingsnakes are considered useful, Guyer said, because they generally leave people alone, are not venomous and eat other venomous snakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“there’s a lot of money involved.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The University announced in October 2013 its plan to give the land to VCOM for development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Becky Barlow, professor of biological sciences, and Kush said despite a letter-writing campaign from themselves and students who had used the area for research projects, the University still used the land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The site had tremendous potential,” Hermann said. “It was hard to lose that site, even though I understand the University needed someplace to put that building and that there’s a lot of money involved.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auburn University architect Jim Carroll said the Office of Facilities Management recommended the site because of its advantageous location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Long term, we are master-planning that for the health sciences sector,” Carroll said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carroll said his office selected the site because its proximity to campus and the research park could encourage collaborative research between the College of Osteopathic Medicine and the planned nursing school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s our job to evaluate the highest and best use of every piece of property the University owns,” Carroll said. “You could argue that we could have had that on Wire Road, or it could have been down by the veterinary school, but that did not have the strength of having it adjacent to the health science sector.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike Kensler, director of the Office of Sustainability, said the University has been working with VCOM and contractor Brasfield and Gorrie to develop the building in an environmentally friendly manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kensler said if done properly, developing campus land did not have to affect the stormwater runoff and remaining habitat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“What they left were little fragments.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kush, who worked on the VCOM land for 12 years, said he doubted the contractors could handle the flooding. Kush also said the building would inevitably impact the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re taking something that was 21 acres and paving over most of it,” Kush said. “What they left were little fragments that couldn’t support the whole variety [of species].”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kush said the exact spot where Hermann found the rare kingsnakes is now a parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one who spoke to The Plainsman said they knew what happened to the eastern kingsnakes found on the VCOM site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guyer said it is “virtually certain” the snakes stayed on the site through construction in spring 2014 because they had begun reproducing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carroll said the Office of Facilities Management commissioned a study by BioResources, LLC., an outside contractor, to check the site for federally listed plant and animal species.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carroll said though he knew kingsnakes were on the property, he did not know if they lived on the 15 acres occupied by the VCOM building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roger Clay, marine biologist for the Alabama Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, said his department would need proof of the kingsnakes being killed during construction to pursue action against Auburn University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He called chances of any legal consequences “slim to none.” With the VCOM building almost complete, Guyer said it’s too late to save rare species such as the eastern kingsnake on that particular site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best plan for the future, according to Guyer, is to map every plant and animal species on campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’d love to see it,” Guyer said. “We’d like to provide that so that the campus will be armed with that when they think about developing in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I spent several months investigating, reporting and re-reporting this story. The final product you see here is an abridged version of the original 1,500 word version. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The story sparked a decent bit of controversy within Auburn when it was published. Guyer told me later that an anonymous donor read the story and wanted to give the School of Forestry money to investigate what happened to the kingsnakes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/03/17/snakes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/03/17/snakes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>environment,opening,business,plainsman,features</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From David to Darcy, student embraces new identity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On May 11, 2013, Darcy Corbitt was born at 21 years of age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With her friends gone for the summer, Corbitt moved a couch, three bookshelves and more than 350 books into an apartment to start her new life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She had $70 in her checking account. It was the day before her birthday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Auburn University senior no longer wanted to go by her birth name, David Hall. She wanted to start again as Darcy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When I was really little, 3, 4, I thought I was a girl,” Corbitt said. “I went by a girl’s name in my mind, but I never told anyone because I knew it was socially unacceptable.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt struggled with such feelings throughout her childhood and said despite being born biologically male, she never felt like a man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I tried to be that person for 18 years and it didn’t fit me,” Corbitt said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With help from her friends, she began exploring the idea of living as a woman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonnie Wilson in the Women’s Initiatives Office said she recalled a poignant conversation about gender identity with Corbitt when she still went by David.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I asked her, ‘if there weren’t any barriers, what would you be?’” Wilson said. “And (Corbitt) said, ‘a woman.’ And I said, ‘then that’s what you are.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“My whole life, all the decisions I’ve ever made, I’ve made for love.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said she also credits Spectrum, Auburn’s Gay-Straight Alliance, with helping her come to understand her identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I didn’t have the GSA, I don’t know what I would have done,” Corbitt said. “I’d have probably killed myself.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she still used the name David, Corbitt said she came within seconds of committing suicide after being outed as someone attracted to men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The only thing stopping me was I couldn’t break the razor blade out of my razor,” Corbitt said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just kind of thought that was funny. I laughed, and I thought, ‘I can’t really kill myself. I’ve got so much I can do in the world.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt fully accepted being Darcy last May, on her 21st birthday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The transition hasn’t been easy. Some friends offered minimal support for her new public identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said her best friend from high school, a girl who drove three hours from the University of Montevallo to see her during their freshman year, unfriended her on Facebook last summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You post a lot of gay stuff,” Corbitt said the friend told her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said she recently ran into her former best friend. When Corbitt tried to start a conversation, the friend showed little pleasure in seeing her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other groups have reacted differently to the news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt sent an email to every professor she’s worked with in the past to let them know about the change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The faculty responded with immediate and overwhelming support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The University was really classy about it,” Corbitt said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Corbitt said she embraces her identity as a woman. She dresses in a women’s suit with thick-frame glasses, a red-and-orange scarf and a purple shirt to match her purple wristwatch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silver eye shadow and lipstick adorn her face. Her fingernails bear pink Ballet Slippers nail polish, which she said she fidgets with when nervous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her friends admire the change, citing its positive effects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I saw how it truly made her happy to do that,” said Alyssa Patterson, a junior who shared English classes with Corbitt. “She’s so much more confident in who she is.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conversation, Corbitt appears confident. She laughs easily and jokes about blasting “Dancing Queen” by ABBA, her favorite song, at annoying neighbors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In her new life, the senior majoring in English and psychology serves as director of social affairs for Spectrum, an advocacy group for lesbian, bisexual, gay and transgender (LBGT) students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said she hopes to attend graduate school to become a therapist for LBGT teens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her friends spoke highly of her academic work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She’s a good G–d— student,” said Kelly Tsaltas, senior in psychology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt’s peers said they also admire her intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She’s really smart and cognizant in how people think and feel and express themselves,” Wilson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said she would prefer to remain at Auburn for graduate school, but thinks she’ll probably attend another institution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until she leaves, she also wants to stay close to her parents. They declined to comment for this story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corbitt said she understands her transition has been difficult for her mother and father, but she would have been unhappy any other way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My whole life, all the decisions I’ve ever made, I’ve made for love,” Corbitt said. “I came out for myself, the second time because I wanted to be happy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is the best story I’ve ever written. The characterization, the material, everything just works. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Plainsman editor at the time, Kelsey Davis, made a bold choice and put this on the front page, above the fold. Remember, this was fall 2013. Most people couldn’t tell you what “transgender” meant if you asked, and Auburn is still a conservative school in a conservative town. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The story was a huge hit and &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.al.com/spotnews/2014/02/ive_always_been_darcy_transgen.html&quot;&gt;got picked up by AL.com&lt;/a&gt;. Apparently it made one of our photographers cry. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It was also responsible for passing transgender protections into university law at Auburn. The Gay-Straight Alliance had been trying to get protections for trans people passed for three years. They got the bill all the way to President Jay Gouge’s desk and there it sat for a year. Four days after we published Darcy’s story, Gouge signed the bill. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2013/10/30/darcy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2013/10/30/darcy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>lgbt,</category>
        
        <category>plainsman,</category>
        
        <category>features</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
