<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:13:39 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:13:39 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Traveling, the way he would have wanted</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;William Nathan Thomas Daniels died too soon.&lt;!--break--&gt; The 23-year-old Phenix City resident ran off Randolph County Road 82 at 6 a.m. and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/anniston-gadsden/index.ssf/2015/10/phenix_city_man_killed_when_ve.html&quot;&gt;struck an embankment&lt;/a&gt;. He was pronounced dead at the scene by Alabama state troopers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The loss of the beloved son, older brother and boyfriend turned his loved ones’ world upside down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she met Daniels at his house in Phenix City on June 14, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was instant,” she said. “He told me within the first week we were soulmates. I thought he was crazy. I just shrugged it off… [but] it didn’t take me long before I realized he was onto something.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton and Daniels connected over a shared love of travel and music. They loved discovering new bands together and sharing them with the other person. They had already booked a hotel and bought tickets to a Zeds Dead concert in Nashville in November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/assets/overton2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;imgRight&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said the two wanted to wait to have kids until their 30s so they could travel the world. They made plans to go to Europe the following year. Daniels, an Army brat who moved around the world, spent three years in Baumholder, Germany, when he was a baby and wanted to visit again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The couple had planned to rent a house in LaGrange in February. They’d already picked out a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she loved Daniels’ passion for life, travel, music and his small circle of close friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If he loved you, then you knew it,” Overton said. “He gave it his all in everything.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said when she collected his possessions after the wreck, she pressed play on his Galaxy S6 and received a shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was in the middle of a song… it was our band,” she said. “The whole band was about love and passion and that one song was about losing that love. It was just bone-chilling.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she wants to make sure William Nathan Thomas Daniels is remembered. She is planning a cross-country road trip with his ashes. Daniels’ father Tom Daniels said he hopes he can go for some of the trip, if circumstances allow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton’s plan starts with renting a car and driving out to El Paso, Texas, where Daniels lived. After that, Las Vegas and Fort Irvin, Calif., where Daniels was born. From there she’ll drive up to Portland, Ore., and Seattle, where one of Daniels’ friends lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s running a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gofundme.com/r76j58ws&quot;&gt;GoFundMe drive&lt;/a&gt; to help collect money for the trip. If Overton raises enough, she is thinking about flying to Germany and spending time in Europe. She said they had planned to go to Italy next summer. She’d love to see the country and backpack around as much as possible. Overton does not plan to leave until next spring break, so the plans are still in motion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she’s also applied for as many overtime shifts as is legally possible at her job as a lab assistant at Columbus Regional Medical Center. It helps save money for the trip and keep her mind off of her loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just want to go as many places as I possibly can,” Overton said. “It is my last gift to him. It’s something I want to do to make sure he’s remembered. I don’t want him to just go away. I don’t want him to just sit up on a shelf and collect dust. I want him to be where his heart wanted to be.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/assets/overton3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;ImgMiddle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/27/samOverton.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/27/samOverton.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>human</category>
        
        <category>interest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>features</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Katherine McCarron is mad because Bengals players were shown changing on TV</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Katherine McCarron, a Phenix City native and wife of former Alabama quarterback AJ McCarron, was not happy about an invasion of the Cincinnati Bengals’ privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NFL Network conducted an interview with Adam “Pacman” Jones with several of his teammates nude in the background. They were showering and changing into street clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;No missing the point. Players should have their privacy. I&amp;#39;m sure female reports would rather not be in there &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/1FjAXHQxPH&quot;&gt;https://t.co/1FjAXHQxPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Katherine McCarron (@_KatherineWebb) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/_KatherineWebb/status/656216906165329924&quot;&gt;October 19, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An NFL Network told ESPN the interview was “a regrettable mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bengals offensive lineman Andrew Whitworth also took to Twitter to vent his frustrations over the choice of interview location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;why do I have to explain to my kids why their dad is naked on tv? &amp;#10;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nflcommish&quot;&gt;@nflcommish&lt;/a&gt; ?? &amp;#10;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nflnetwork&quot;&gt;@nflnetwork&lt;/a&gt; ??&amp;#10;Time for a media policy change!!&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Andrew Whitworth (@BigWhit77_fndn) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BigWhit77_fndn/status/656107615588626433&quot;&gt;October 19, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katherine McCarron  was raised in the Columbus-Phenix City area and graduated from Auburn University. She first entered the national spotlight after some &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29325652.html&quot;&gt;odd comments&lt;/a&gt; were made about her during a national championship. She has also appeared in the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue and competed on reality show “Splash.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29291965.html&quot;&gt;Overnight celebrity: Katherine Webb aims to prove she’s ‘more than just a pretty face’&lt;/a&gt; - Our 2013 profile of Webb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/cincinnati-bengals-katherine-webb-loses-it-over-players-being-shown-nude-in-locker-room-101915&quot;&gt;h/t Fox Sports&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/20/mccarronLockerRoom.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/20/mccarronLockerRoom.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>nfl,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cigarette taxes went up in Alabama, so why aren’t smokers coming to Georgia?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alabama hiked the tax on cigarettes this year, but it doesn’t seem to be affecting smokers’ behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sept. 17, Gov. Robert Bentley signed Act No. 2015-535 into law and raised the tax on a pack of 20 cigarettes from $0.43 to $0.675. The price hike took effect on Oct. 1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama’s tax is now more than 30 cents higher than Georgia’s statewide rate of 37 cents per pack. The retail price is affected by other things like store markup, but the tax is still a factor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price of a pack of Marlboro Red cigarettes was $6.35 at the Marathon Gas at 410 Martin Luther King Jr. Parkway in Phenix City. That same pack cost only $5.46 at the Circle K at 1445 Veterans Parkway in Columbus. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The effect on smokers’ behavior, however, seems to be minimal. In a strictly unscientific survey of several convenience stores and gas stations close to the Chattahoochee River, employees said they had not seen any noticeable shift in their businesses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhonda Montalbo, manager of the Bizzy Bee Mart at 2100 Crawford Road in Phenix City, said her customers were not changing their behavior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Just a lot of fussin’,” Montalbo said. “A smoker is going to pay what they are going to pay for the convenience of wherever they are.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine Mudd, who manages the Circle K at 215 4th Street in Columbus, said she hadn’t seen many new faces at her store, though she’d heard customers discuss the tax hike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenneth Justice, the manager of Justice Food Mart at 1403 11th Ave. in Phenix City, said he’s less worried about the higher tax than he is about bootleggers who resell packs by the cigarette. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cigarette smokers don’t go that far to buy their cigarettes unless they’re buying in bulk,” said Paresh Patel, manager of the Liberty gas station at 400 3rd Ave. He said he has not seen a lot of new customers either. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patel pointed out that the cost of a pack of cigarettes is more than its retail price. It may not be worth spending the time, effort and gas to cross the river just to save money on a single pack. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frank J. Chaloupka, professor of economics at the University of Illinois at Chicago, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tigger.uic.edu/~fjc/Presentations/Papers/taxes_consump_rev.pdf&quot;&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; changes in behavior from new cigarette taxes take a long time to become noticeable. It may be too soon to measure any significant change just weeks in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama Arise executive director Kimble Forrister said legislators and interest groups expected little change from this hike.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forrister said a tobacco industry lobbyist was present during committee hearings over the tax increase and told Alabama legislators a 25-cent increase was acceptable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you keep the tax increase as low as 25 cents a pack, it’s not gonna affect behavior that much,” Forrister said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama Arise supported a higher tax increase for its beneficial health effects, according to Forrister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3228562/#b4-ijerph-08-04118&quot;&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; on cigarette taxes found that raising cigarette prices made low-income families more likely to quit buying them. Any decrease in smokering is a financial and health benefit to Alabama, Forrister said, especially if it saves money with Medicaid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It should be at least 55 cents, preferably a dollar,” Forrister said. “That’s going to be a fight for another day.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This story was featured on the front page, above the fold for the Ledger-Enquirer for Oct. 19, 2015. We also wrote an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/opinion/article40282173.html&quot;&gt;editorial&lt;/a&gt; about the issue. I’m proud of this story because of the reporting involved and how it localized a state story. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/smokingTax.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/smokingTax.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>alabama,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fort Benning conducts mass casualty exercise</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you hear a lot of sirens and see emergency response vehicles near Fort Benning today, this is the most likely cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fort Benning personnel are conducting a “mass casualty exercise” today near Lawson Army Airfield, according to a release. The Army advises anyone entering post through the Fort Mitchell access point should prepare for delays between now and noon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exercise will also close Sunshine Road along the airfield for 15 minutes once it begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The release said the exercise would help keep first responders’ skills sharp in the event of an actual emergency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/benningExercise.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/benningExercise.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus police officer connects with community</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cpl. Travis Spencer of the Columbus Police Department was spotted doing some good today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missy Behar said she posted this photo of Spencer handing out badge-shaped stickers to several children to Facebook. Spencer didn’t know about the picture until someone tagged him in it later in the day. It was taken between 12 p.m. and 1:30 p.m. Friday afternoon at Jim Bob’s Chicken Fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spencer said the boy pictured, whose name he does not know, waved to him several times as he was eating. Spencer said he then went out to his vehicle and got a roll of stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The corporal, who is six-foot-three, said he made sure to crouch down to the 3-4-year-old’s level before talking to the excited child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I love it,” Spencer said. “If a kid says hello and is excited to see you, you have to talk to them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spencer is a part of the Crime Prevention Unit, a group within CPD that does outreach events at churches and schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We try to engage children, make sure they’re not afraid of us,” Spencer said. “Kinda breaks down barriers between us and the community.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behar said she took  wanted to document Spencer’s actions for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I thought, ‘Well, that’s so sweet,’” Behar said. “He just seemed so nice.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mary Katherine Holton, who was also at the restaurant, said she thought it was sweet as well for Spencer to talk to everyone like that during his lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just hope more people get to see police officers do the right thing,” Holton said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/stickers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/stickers.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>human</category>
        
        <category>interest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Beat Bama at a free Brad Paisley concert in Auburn</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Country star Brad Paisley is putting on a free concert at Auburn University as the second stop on his Country Nation College Tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paisley will play at the Green Space (by the student center) at 8:30 p.m. tonight, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.oanow.com/news/auburnuniversity/article_322e918a-6ba9-11e5-b493-9f2711f2ee53.html&quot;&gt;OA News&lt;/a&gt;. New country artist Eric Paslay will open for him at 7:30. The show will go on, rain or shine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admission is free. There will be bins set up around the area to collect canned food for the Food Bank of East Alabama. Concertgoers are encouraged to donate money or canned food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As the food comes in, we package it and get it ready to go out to our agencies,” Martha Henk, who works with the food bank, told &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsfa.com/story/30221773/brad-paisley-headlines-free-concert-in-auburn-on-friday&quot;&gt;WSFA&lt;/a&gt;. “There are no losers in this, there are only winners.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Beat Bama Food Drive has happened annually for more than 20 years. Auburn and Alabama compete to see who can raise more for families in need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I know it is a competition and that is what we like to say to students because students love that competitive factor of it, but it is really about the people in our area and who we are able to feed,” said Beat Bama Food Drive president Sarah Perez.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tents, coolers, glass bottles, chairs, saving space and alcohol will be prohibited. Food trucks and concession stands will be available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information see the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ocm.auburn.edu/concerts/&quot;&gt;concert listing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/bradPaisley.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/bradPaisley.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>country,</category>
        
        <category>auburn,</category>
        
        <category>arts,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fort Benning soldier awarded medal for saving two kids from drowning in the Chattahoochee</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;1st Lt. James R. Lamoreaux received the Soldier’s Medal Thursday afternoon for his quick actions diving into the Chattahoochee River and saving two boys from drowning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am humbled before you to receive this medal,” Lamoreaux said. “I am an ordinary soldier who happened to be at the right place at a fortunate time.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That fortunate moment took place on the Chattahoochee River Island near 11th Street and Bay Avenue on March 15, 2014. Lamoreaux and his wife Shannon were exploring the RiverWalk for the first time when he saw two boys, ages 9 and 15, struggling in the current.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The younger boy was in the water first just south of the area known as Cut Bait, and the older boy had gone in after him, according to Robert Futrell, deputy chief of Columbus Fire &amp;amp; Emergency Medical Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lamoreaux, a former lifeguard and strong swimmer, said he immediately slipped behind his wife and jumped in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He caught up to them and pulled him onto the rocks,” Shannon told the Ledger-Enquirer at the time. “He still had his phone and keys in his pocket. His phone was ruined, but the kids were safe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lamoreaux demurred from praising himself for saving the children. He asked the 644 members of the 15th Infantry Regiment gathered at Sledgehammer Field to instead ook up to other people who save lives every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been told several times that the actions that took place on March 15, 2014, have made me a hero in some way,” Lamoreaux said during his speech. “Indeed, I despise the usage of that word in reference to me because I know there are numerous actions that soldiers have done that have gone unnoticed.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Col. Fred Tanner, Lamoreaux’s commander, said the first lieutenant’s act was undeniably heroic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As uncomfortable as he may be with that word, that’s what it is,” Tanner said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The out-of-the-ordinary nature of Lamoreaux’s actions won him a Soldier’s Medal, a major award given to those who risk their lives for others outside of combat. They are rarely given, according to Tanner, who guessed that the last one was received by one of the men who stopped the Paris train attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tanner said the significance of the award and Lamoreaux switching from training command to forces command were some of the reasons why it took so long to give it to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tanner praised the newly promoted first lieutenant, saying he was a better-than-average young officer who showed great promise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m super proud,” Tanner said. “This may be the pinnacle of what he’s done so far, but I don’t think it’s the pinnacle of what he’ll do.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/08/soldiersMedal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/08/soldiersMedal.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Doubters fueled Tim Hudson&#39;s amazing baseball career, which came to a close Sunday</title>
        <description>&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://media.ledger-enquirer.com/static/projects/hudson/&quot;&gt;Proving them wrong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Though I did not write this story, I worked on the formatting and publishing tools for it for several weeks to make a web-native version that would stand out and impress readers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Our sports editor, Kevin Price, wrote it to celebrate a local man who had a long and successful pro career. I edited the story and produced the layout specifically for the web using &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mcclatchy/sinclair&quot;&gt;Sinclair&lt;/a&gt;, a McClatchy tool for building amazing web stories. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I started by hosting the story &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/sports/mlb/article37724499.html&quot;&gt;on our website&lt;/a&gt; with a couple other story assets. Sinclair scrapes the story and assets from our site (which we know will always be up) and reformats them in the visually appealing way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sinclair is not actively developed by McClatchy anymore, as far as I can tell, and required a lot of work to bring up to production levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My workflow was to run the story content and assets through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AuRuRdHZo6DPdG9oLXlVNjV2bDN0clJuX294dER0RUE&amp;amp;usp=sharing&quot;&gt;Sinclair generator&lt;/a&gt;, download the .html file and edit in all the other necessary features. I removed the paragraph numbers and added a title, subhead, byline and meta tags so it would share properly on Facebook. The header formatting is based on CSS I added as an extra file to Sinclair, thanks to stuff from the Macon Telegraph. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It was a lot of work, but the feature looks fantastic and uses its web format to its advantage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/04/timHudson.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/04/timHudson.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>baseball,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>features</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two dogs are recovering after being chained together</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two American bulldogs were brought to Animal Ark Rescue by Columbus Animal Care &amp;amp; Control yesterday in rough shape, according to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/118069674930375/photos/a.118483231555686.17028.118069674930375/911782775559057/?type=3&amp;amp;theater&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; by the Rescue on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animal control officers found the two chained together for “breeding purposes” when responding to a complaint in Columbus backyard, the post said. The heavy metal chain was padlocked and drawn so tightly, the Rescue wrote, that it embedded into the dogs’ necks and caused painful injuries. The two had to be tranquilized and cut apart with bolt cutters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dogs are recovering at the Animal Ark Rescue according to Charlene Rallo, a full-time volunteer for the Rescue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rallo said these kinds of cases are sadly common. In her year working for the Rescue, she said she’s seen four or five similar incidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is unknown if Animal Care &amp;amp; Control plans to bring charges against the owner. They did not return multiple calls to their office for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rallo said the dogs are named Devin and Lacey. She guesses they are both 2-year-old American bulldogs. Devin was injured most and will take three to four weeks to recover. Even then, the damage will leave a mark until the hair grows back. Lacey should recover slightly faster in “a few weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rescue staff plans to spay and neuter the dogs (as required by law) and  before putting them up for adoption, according to Rallo. There is already some interest in the dogs, as Rallo said some people have said they are mailing in donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We just want to get them healthy,” Rallo said. “(This case) seems to have touched quite a few people’s hearts.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/02/dogsChained.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/02/dogsChained.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roaches found in DeKalb Starbucks during health inspection</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A Starbucks in the Atlanta area failed its health inspection for issues with roaches, among other problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Starbucks, located on North Druid Hills Road in DeKalb County, received a score of 65 out of 100 from health inspectors according to WSB-TV. Violations included roaches crawling under the espresso machine and on the floor in front of the hand-washing sink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An inspector said he saw an employee put his or her hand into a trash can and then use food utensils without and hand washing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We immediately engaged a third party vendor to conduct a thorough inspection and in-depth cleaning of our store following this health inspection,” said Jaime Riley, spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsbtv.com/news/news/local/dekalb-county-starbucks-fails-health-inspection/nnrmD/&quot;&gt;WSB-TV has the rest of the story.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;object id=&quot;flashObj&quot; width=&quot;615&quot; height=&quot;392&quot; classid=&quot;clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000&quot; codebase=&quot;http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,47,0&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;bgcolor&quot; value=&quot;#FFFFFF&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;flashVars&quot; value=&quot;videoId=4521768591001&amp;amp;linkBaseURL=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wsbtv.com%2Fvideos%2Fnews%2Fstarbucks-near-toco-hills-shopping-plaza-fails%2FvDbww3%2F&amp;amp;playerID=836827756001&amp;amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAAFIvhljk~,Nz7UFI321EYSAUsYGYx5WAk9m9XiXaY8&amp;amp;domain=embed&amp;amp;dynamicStreaming=true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;base&quot; value=&quot;http://admin.brightcove.com&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;seamlesstabbing&quot; value=&quot;false&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowFullScreen&quot; value=&quot;true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;swLiveConnect&quot; value=&quot;true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;always&quot; /&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&quot; bgcolor=&quot;#FFFFFF&quot; flashvars=&quot;videoId=4521768591001&amp;amp;linkBaseURL=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wsbtv.com%2Fvideos%2Fnews%2Fstarbucks-near-toco-hills-shopping-plaza-fails%2FvDbww3%2F&amp;amp;playerID=836827756001&amp;amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAAFIvhljk~,Nz7UFI321EYSAUsYGYx5WAk9m9XiXaY8&amp;amp;domain=embed&amp;amp;dynamicStreaming=true&quot; base=&quot;http://admin.brightcove.com&quot; name=&quot;flashObj&quot; width=&quot;615&quot; height=&quot;392&quot; seamlesstabbing=&quot;false&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; swliveconnect=&quot;true&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;always&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.macromedia.com/shockwave/download/index.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash&quot; /&gt;&lt;/object&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/01/dekalbStarbucks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/01/dekalbStarbucks.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
