<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 13:36:59 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 13:36:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>This family lost their home in a fire, but the community gave back</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the Robinson family, Halloween was Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anthony St. Pierre, a Columbus firefighter paramedic, &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/09/29/batman.html&quot;&gt;collected donations&lt;/a&gt; of toys, blankets and clothing for the family for the past month. On Halloween, he presented the family with the collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Robinsons have had a hard month. On Sept. 15, Tuesday, John Robinson’s mother passed away. Her funeral was on Friday. On Saturday, the Robinson’s rental trailer caught fire. Sunday was Robin’s fifth birthday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We lost it all,” John said. “Every bit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John said what wasn’t ruined by the fire was stolen when the family was living out of a motel. He said the “scavengers” took kitchen appliances, DVD players (only one worked) and a TV bought for $3 at a garage sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre said when he saw Raven Rose Robinson, 2, and Robin Renee Robinson, 5, he thought of his own children and wanted to give them a good Halloween. He originally planned to have the kids go to fire stations all over Columbus for a private trick-or-treat, but the Robinson parents John and Jessica decided it would be better to stay at fire station #4 on North Oakley Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For their private Halloween, Robin and Raven dressed up as princesses. St. Pierre, a comic book fan, came as Batman. His friend Caitlin Norton drove in from Atlanta and dressed as Batgirl to help present the donations to the family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article42072678.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The oldest one, Robin, she almost started crying when she saw all of this,” Norton said. “Even Raven was starting to cry because all of the stuff was for them. That’s what it’s all about right there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin and Raven got to play with dozens of toys donated by people as far away as Los Angeles and Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre said news of the family’s plight spread over social media and inspired an outpouring of donations. He said he filled up one of the ambulances several times over with all the blankets and toys people donated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(This) gives our girls things they haven’t had for a month,” John said. “We appreciate it. It’s nice to see people willing to help.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to donate gently used goods or toys, drop them off at the fire station at 200 North Oakley Drive, Columbus, GA 31907.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;imgur-embed-pub&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot; data-id=&quot;a/iLmcK&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;//imgur.com/a/iLmcK&quot;&gt;Columbus family receives a special Halloween&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/31/halloween-charity-batman.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/31/halloween-charity-batman.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>halloween,</category>
        
        <category>human</category>
        
        <category>interest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ToDo this Halloween- Trunk-or-treat, Spooktacular and a Paw-rade</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t already carved your pumpkin, you only have a couple more days left to dig out those seeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is Saturday and there are numerous things going on around town for your fall festival pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trick-or-treat times in the area vary a little: Columbus 6-9 p.m., Phenix City 5:30-8:30 p.m., Fort Benning 6-8 p.m. and Hamilton 5-7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, be careful crossing the streets if you’re out asking for candy. Drivers, be wary of kids and keep an eye out especially when it gets dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some Halloween events going on in the area. If we’re missing any, email me at knazario@ledger-enquirer.com and I’ll add it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;friday&quot;&gt;FRIDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ZOMBIE ZIP: Zip over the Chattahoochee and enjoy two towers full of terrors. 10 percent of proceeds benefit the Springer Opera House. Friday and Saturday. $40, 8 p.m. 1000 Bay Ave. Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NORTH HIGHLAND PUMPKIN PATCH: Runs through Saturday. Call 706-561-7777 for group reservations. $2 and up per pumpkin, 10 a.m.-dark Friday and Saturday. 7300 Whittlesey Blvd Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUMMERVILLE PUMPKIN PATCH: Runs through Saturday. Free, 1-7 p.m. 1201 32nd St., Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JACK-O-LANTERN LANE: Come see the beautiful country setting, pumpkin patch, fresh corn meal, train rides, pony rides and farm animals. Admission includes a wagon ride and pumpkin, but other activities cost extra. $7, Noon-5 p.m. Friday, 9 a.m.-6 p.m. Saturday. 18151 Veterans Memorial Parkway, LaFayette, Ala. 36862&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GEORGIA PUMPKIN PATCH: Celebrate the harvest with corn stalks, decorative gourds, terra-cotta pumpkins, marigolds, mums, autumn merchandise, and every pumpkin related food you can imagine. Free, 8 a.m.-6 p.m. Friday and Saturday. 9616 Fortson Road Fortson, Ga. 31808&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALL HALLOWS EVE: Columbus Public Library will host family fun with movies and treats in the auditorium. There is limited space. Free, 3-6 p.m. 3000 Macon Road, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL AT THE Y: D.A. Turner YMCA will host a festival with a treat trail, pumpkin carving contest, costume contest, face painting, arts and crafts, carnival games and a bounce house. No masks or weapons. Free, 4 p.m. 4384 Warm Springs Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ROCK-O-WEEN: Treadstone Climbing Gym will have candy, prizes, a costume party, games and black light climbing. $25 per person, $5 off with costume, 6-10 p.m. 4209 Milgren Road, Suite 7. Columbus 31907&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLELUJAH NIGHT: New Birth Outreach Church will have hay rides, face painting, a wing-eating contest, cake walk, cotton handy, hula-hoop contest and free food. Free, 6:30-8:30 p.m. 10107 Veterans Parkway, Midland, Ga. 31820&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRUNK OR TREAT: Rose Hill Church is having a night of family fun with dinner, games, hay rides and more. Free, 6:30 p.m. 7479 Old Moon Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE ROCKY HORROR SHOW: See the spooky rock-n-roll musical that inspired the cult movie. Also plays at 7:30 p.m. and 11 p.m. Saturday. $20 for adults, $17 for seniors/active duty military/groups of 10+, $12 for children 12 and under. 7:30 p.m. 6 W. 10th St. Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN HOTEL HORROR: See the dinner theater show that will have you guessing who the villain is to win a special prize. Guests are encouraged to come in costume and compete for best costume. Two audience roles will be assigned each evening to the most promising actors as well. Runs at the same times on Saturday. $30, with discounts for groups, 12 a.m. and 9:30 p.m. 8701 Garrett Road Midland, Ga. 31820&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;saturday&quot;&gt;SATURDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OPERATION TROOP TREATS: Kool Smiles Columbus is encouraging children to bring their Halloween candy to any area Kool Smiles dental offices in exchange for a toy. The candy will be sent in care packages to U.S. soldiers overseas as part of Operation Gratitude. Children will receive one toy for every 25 pieces of unopened candy in its original packaging. Limit three toys per child. Runs through Nov. 4. Free, All Day, 4519 Woodruff Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SPOOKTACULAR HALLOWEEN FESTIVAL: A free and safe environment for children to enjoy an afternoon of ghosts and goblins, spooky activities, candy and lots of fun. There will be a costume contest. Free, 2-4 p.m. 25 W. 10th St., Ste 4, Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRUNK OR TREAT: Candy, rides, inflatables, games, a petting zoo, pony rides and a rock wall. $5, 5-7 p.m. 7300 Whittlesey Blvd. Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN AT BUTTS MILL FARM: Celebrate Halloween at Butts Mill Farm. The first 100 kids will receive a free pumpkin to collect candy, which will be given out for free by staff throughout the farm. There will be carnival games, a bonfire, carnival food and a free mini-pumpkin to paint for the first 50 kids. $10, 10 a.m.-4 p.m., 2280 Butts Mill Road, Pine Mountain, Ga. 31822&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BROADWAY PAW-RADE: The fourth annual Broadway Paw-rade at Market Days raises money for Paws Humane and the Columbus Animal Care &amp;amp; Control Center. There will be a costume contets for the dogs and a live DJ. $10, 9:30 a.m. Broadway, in the median in front of The Loft&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOT SO SPOOKY HALLOWEEN FESTIVAL: The Rock Ranch will have magic shows, a children’s costume contest, pet costume contest, trick-or-treating, the Frisbee dog state championship, a pumpkin cannon and a magician. $15, 10 a.m.-8 p.m. 5020 Barnesville Highway, The Rock, Ga. 30285&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUMMERVILLE UMC FALL FESTIVAL: Summerville United Methodist Church is hosting a Fall Festival every Saturday during October. This week will have games, inflatables, baked goods, a pumpkin patch and a huge corn bin. Games and inflatables are free. $1 per person for groups, 10 a.m.-2 p.m. 1201 32nd St., Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FARM HOUSE PUMPKIN PATCH: Take a hay ride over to the pumpkin field and enjoy lunch with fall activities. Price not listed, 10 a.m., 469 Farmhouse Road, Ellerslie, Ga. 31807&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL: Redeemer Lutheran Church will have a Fall Festival with carnival games, a bounce house, food, fall crafts, a cupcake walk and Trunk or Treat. Bring a canned good to support Feeding the Valley. Free, 11 a.m.-2 p.m. 4700 Armour Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN STORYTIME: Barnes &amp;amp; Noble will feature Halloween stories and complete a craft. Children are encouraged to come in costume and parade around the store for trick-or-treat goodies. Free, 11 a.m.-12 p.m. 5555 Whittlesey Blvd No. 1800, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK-OR-TREAT AROUND THE LIBRARY: Come hear not-so-scary stories at the Columbus Public Library. Free, 2-4 p.m. 3000 Macon Road, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BLOCK PARTY: There will be a free block party behind the Huddle House with free food, refreshments, giveaways, and free candy for children. Free, 2-4 p.m. 1811 Victory Drive, Suite 3 Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLELUJAH FESTIVAL: Mt. Zion UMC will have games, a costume contest, Trunk or Treat, a cake walk, inflatables and Elsa and Anna from “Frozen.” Free, 3-5 p.m. 2616 Lee Road 243 Smiths Station, Ala. 36877&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK OR TREAT AT PUBLIX: Come to Publix to get a coloring sheet and candy. Free, 4-7 p.m. 3201 Macon Road Ste 201, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL: Epworth UMC will have a festival with food, music, inflatables and Trunk or Treat. 4 p.m. 3763 U.S. 280, Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK OR TRUNK: The Way Church will host a Trick or Trunk. Free, 1593 Lee Road 242 Smiths Station, Ala. 36877&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN AT THE SPEEDWAY: The East Alabama Motor Speedway will celebrate Halloween with trick-or-treating, face painting, balloon animals, and a costume contest. Free with price of admission, 5-7 p.m. 4238 U.S. 80 Phenix City 36869&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARK IN THE PARK: Join Britt David Baptist Church for a safe, Christ-centered trick-or-treat alternative with candy, games, rides, inflatables, food and prizes. Free, 5:30-7:30 p.m. 5560 Armour Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN BASH: Stop by Fuddruckers for a special Halloween party with live music from Johnny Kempt. Free kids’ meals for children 12 and under in costume. 6-9 p.m. 5524 Whitesville Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sunday&quot;&gt;SUNDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL BACK SERVICE AND FESTIVAL: Join RiverTown Church for a Fall Back Worship Service and festival with hay rides, a petting zoo, popcorn, a bake sale and barbecue. A $10 lunch includes chicken or pork, sides, bread and drinks. Proceeds support missions in Guatemala. $10, 6953 Schomburg Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/30/halloween-todo-events.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/30/halloween-todo-events.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>halloween,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>living,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eufaula latex plant to restart under Steve Harvey, Greg Calhoun</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Comedian Steve Harvey and Montgomery businessman Greg Calhoun are reopening a latex plant in Eufaula next year, according to Calhoun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We wanted to put people back to work,” Calhoun said. “It’s a blessed opportunity.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun, who has been friends with Steve Harvey for 15 years, said the two were interested in Eufaula because it has the only latex plant in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eufaula Mayor Jack Tibbs Jr. said the plant now known as Ameritex closed down in 2008 when it lost its contract with USAID producing condoms for AIDS prevention. Tibbs estimated that contract was 95 percent of the plant’s business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said he plans to have the factory produce mostly latex gloves for major organizations such as Wal-Mart, the Transportation Security Administration, poultry producers and hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he’s already spoken with Rob Walton, chairman of Wal-Mart, who has indicated interest in buying gloves from the factory as part of the retailer’s initiative to move jobs back to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said he hopes to have the first two lines operational by January 2016 and the whole plant online in four phases through 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Calhoun said it was “nice to have Wal-Mart to start out with,” he doesn’t plan on having only one major customer like the plant did before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(Walton) didn’t want to be our only customer,” Calhoun said. “He wanted us to get out there and find others.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said the output from one line in Ameritex could supply Wal-Mart, leaving several others for different customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Bradley, director of economic development for the city of Eufaula, said there are about 10 people working on retooling the four production lines to make them ready to produce latex gloves instead of condoms. He said only one of the four was already set up to do gloves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tibbs said there is a great deal of excitement for the plant, which is estimated to bring 300 jobs over two years. Each line will require 65-70 people, plus supervisors, management and warehouse employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bradley said the plant will slowly staff up as more of it comes online. He estimates that 27 people will be working there on Jan. 4, 2016, and 100 by the end of 2016. By 2018, there should be 350 people hired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s a long, complicated process, but Mr. Harvey and Mr. Calhoun have a terrific vision for the future of latex,” Bradley said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tibbs said he was happy to see jobs returning to Alabama and especially Eufaula.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(Harvey) can be a serious guy,” Tibbs said. “He wants to put people back to work.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;***STEVE HARVEY TALKING JOBS FOR EUFAULA***&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/&quot;&gt;Help Eufaula Alabama Live&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot;&gt;Friday, October 23, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/steve-harvey-eufaula-condom-factory-plant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/steve-harvey-eufaula-condom-factory-plant.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>eufaula,</category>
        
        <category>opening,</category>
        
        <category>business,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That Secret Society letter is as fake as it sounds</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Better Business Bureau sent out a warning about a scam that may show up in postal service mailboxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The letter from the “Secret Society” asks for $135 for “10 miracles that will transform your life,” including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slim down to a body others will envy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Become a genius&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Unlock your hidden creativity&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Live as a VIP&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make $5,000 a month&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The service offers to send you a Secret Manuscript explaining how to obtain these rewards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bureau called the whole system a pyramid scheme that would require victims to recruit more people into the scam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bureau advised consumers to avoid letters that offer pie-in-the-sky statements, say they’ll give benefits if you recruit others, ask that you keep information confidential, or require you to send a check or credit card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always with scams: If it sounds too good to be true, it probably is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/secret-society-letter-scam.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/secret-society-letter-scam.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>scams,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Traveling, the way he would have wanted</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;William Nathan Thomas Daniels died too soon.&lt;!--break--&gt; The 23-year-old Phenix City resident ran off Randolph County Road 82 at 6 a.m. and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/anniston-gadsden/index.ssf/2015/10/phenix_city_man_killed_when_ve.html&quot;&gt;struck an embankment&lt;/a&gt;. He was pronounced dead at the scene by Alabama state troopers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The loss of the beloved son, older brother and boyfriend turned his loved ones’ world upside down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she met Daniels at his house in Phenix City on June 14, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was instant,” she said. “He told me within the first week we were soulmates. I thought he was crazy. I just shrugged it off… [but] it didn’t take me long before I realized he was onto something.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton and Daniels connected over a shared love of travel and music. They loved discovering new bands together and sharing them with the other person. They had already booked a hotel and bought tickets to a Zeds Dead concert in Nashville in November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/assets/overton2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;imgRight&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said the two wanted to wait to have kids until their 30s so they could travel the world. They made plans to go to Europe the following year. Daniels, an Army brat who moved around the world, spent three years in Baumholder, Germany, when he was a baby and wanted to visit again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The couple had planned to rent a house in LaGrange in February. They’d already picked out a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she loved Daniels’ passion for life, travel, music and his small circle of close friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If he loved you, then you knew it,” Overton said. “He gave it his all in everything.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said when she collected his possessions after the wreck, she pressed play on his Galaxy S6 and received a shock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was in the middle of a song… it was our band,” she said. “The whole band was about love and passion and that one song was about losing that love. It was just bone-chilling.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she wants to make sure William Nathan Thomas Daniels is remembered. She is planning a cross-country road trip with his ashes. Daniels’ father Tom Daniels said he hopes he can go for some of the trip, if circumstances allow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton’s plan starts with renting a car and driving out to El Paso, Texas, where Daniels lived. After that, Las Vegas and Fort Irvin, Calif., where Daniels was born. From there she’ll drive up to Portland, Ore., and Seattle, where one of Daniels’ friends lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s running a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gofundme.com/r76j58ws&quot;&gt;GoFundMe drive&lt;/a&gt; to help collect money for the trip. If Overton raises enough, she is thinking about flying to Germany and spending time in Europe. She said they had planned to go to Italy next summer. She’d love to see the country and backpack around as much as possible. Overton does not plan to leave until next spring break, so the plans are still in motion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overton said she’s also applied for as many overtime shifts as is legally possible at her job as a lab assistant at Columbus Regional Medical Center. It helps save money for the trip and keep her mind off of her loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just want to go as many places as I possibly can,” Overton said. “It is my last gift to him. It’s something I want to do to make sure he’s remembered. I don’t want him to just go away. I don’t want him to just sit up on a shelf and collect dust. I want him to be where his heart wanted to be.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/blog/assets/overton3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;ImgMiddle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/27/samOverton.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/27/samOverton.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>human</category>
        
        <category>interest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>features</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Videos filmed for heroin project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The effects of heroin addiction, as told by those involved. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I filmed these videos while assisting Ledger reporter Alva James-Johnson with her Red Ribbon Week series on heroin addiction. The paper does not have any professional video equipment, so I jury-rigged a tripod stand for an iPad Air 2 and filmed heroin addict Joseph Sibold in the quietest room the jail had. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article41210955.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article41198343.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article40976757.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heroin crisis series: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article41368176.html&quot;&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article41419356.html&quot;&gt;Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article41512062.html&quot;&gt;Part 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article41645310.html&quot;&gt;Part 4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article41882292.html&quot;&gt;Part 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/25/heroin-series-videos.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/25/heroin-series-videos.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>heroin,</category>
        
        <category>drugs,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>video</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Katherine McCarron is mad because Bengals players were shown changing on TV</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Katherine McCarron, a Phenix City native and wife of former Alabama quarterback AJ McCarron, was not happy about an invasion of the Cincinnati Bengals’ privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NFL Network conducted an interview with Adam “Pacman” Jones with several of his teammates nude in the background. They were showering and changing into street clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;No missing the point. Players should have their privacy. I&amp;#39;m sure female reports would rather not be in there &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/1FjAXHQxPH&quot;&gt;https://t.co/1FjAXHQxPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Katherine McCarron (@_KatherineWebb) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/_KatherineWebb/status/656216906165329924&quot;&gt;October 19, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An NFL Network told ESPN the interview was “a regrettable mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bengals offensive lineman Andrew Whitworth also took to Twitter to vent his frustrations over the choice of interview location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;why do I have to explain to my kids why their dad is naked on tv? &amp;#10;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nflcommish&quot;&gt;@nflcommish&lt;/a&gt; ?? &amp;#10;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nflnetwork&quot;&gt;@nflnetwork&lt;/a&gt; ??&amp;#10;Time for a media policy change!!&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Andrew Whitworth (@BigWhit77_fndn) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/BigWhit77_fndn/status/656107615588626433&quot;&gt;October 19, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katherine McCarron  was raised in the Columbus-Phenix City area and graduated from Auburn University. She first entered the national spotlight after some &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29325652.html&quot;&gt;odd comments&lt;/a&gt; were made about her during a national championship. She has also appeared in the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue and competed on reality show “Splash.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29291965.html&quot;&gt;Overnight celebrity: Katherine Webb aims to prove she’s ‘more than just a pretty face’&lt;/a&gt; - Our 2013 profile of Webb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/cincinnati-bengals-katherine-webb-loses-it-over-players-being-shown-nude-in-locker-room-101915&quot;&gt;h/t Fox Sports&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/20/mccarronLockerRoom.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/20/mccarronLockerRoom.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>nfl,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cigarette taxes went up in Alabama, so why aren’t smokers coming to Georgia?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alabama hiked the tax on cigarettes this year, but it doesn’t seem to be affecting smokers’ behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Sept. 17, Gov. Robert Bentley signed Act No. 2015-535 into law and raised the tax on a pack of 20 cigarettes from $0.43 to $0.675. The price hike took effect on Oct. 1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama’s tax is now more than 30 cents higher than Georgia’s statewide rate of 37 cents per pack. The retail price is affected by other things like store markup, but the tax is still a factor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price of a pack of Marlboro Red cigarettes was $6.35 at the Marathon Gas at 410 Martin Luther King Jr. Parkway in Phenix City. That same pack cost only $5.46 at the Circle K at 1445 Veterans Parkway in Columbus. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The effect on smokers’ behavior, however, seems to be minimal. In a strictly unscientific survey of several convenience stores and gas stations close to the Chattahoochee River, employees said they had not seen any noticeable shift in their businesses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhonda Montalbo, manager of the Bizzy Bee Mart at 2100 Crawford Road in Phenix City, said her customers were not changing their behavior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Just a lot of fussin’,” Montalbo said. “A smoker is going to pay what they are going to pay for the convenience of wherever they are.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christine Mudd, who manages the Circle K at 215 4th Street in Columbus, said she hadn’t seen many new faces at her store, though she’d heard customers discuss the tax hike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kenneth Justice, the manager of Justice Food Mart at 1403 11th Ave. in Phenix City, said he’s less worried about the higher tax than he is about bootleggers who resell packs by the cigarette. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Cigarette smokers don’t go that far to buy their cigarettes unless they’re buying in bulk,” said Paresh Patel, manager of the Liberty gas station at 400 3rd Ave. He said he has not seen a lot of new customers either. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patel pointed out that the cost of a pack of cigarettes is more than its retail price. It may not be worth spending the time, effort and gas to cross the river just to save money on a single pack. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frank J. Chaloupka, professor of economics at the University of Illinois at Chicago, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tigger.uic.edu/~fjc/Presentations/Papers/taxes_consump_rev.pdf&quot;&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; changes in behavior from new cigarette taxes take a long time to become noticeable. It may be too soon to measure any significant change just weeks in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama Arise executive director Kimble Forrister said legislators and interest groups expected little change from this hike.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forrister said a tobacco industry lobbyist was present during committee hearings over the tax increase and told Alabama legislators a 25-cent increase was acceptable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you keep the tax increase as low as 25 cents a pack, it’s not gonna affect behavior that much,” Forrister said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama Arise supported a higher tax increase for its beneficial health effects, according to Forrister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3228562/#b4-ijerph-08-04118&quot;&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; on cigarette taxes found that raising cigarette prices made low-income families more likely to quit buying them. Any decrease in smokering is a financial and health benefit to Alabama, Forrister said, especially if it saves money with Medicaid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It should be at least 55 cents, preferably a dollar,” Forrister said. “That’s going to be a fight for another day.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This story was featured on the front page, above the fold for the Ledger-Enquirer for Oct. 19, 2015. We also wrote an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/opinion/article40282173.html&quot;&gt;editorial&lt;/a&gt; about the issue. I’m proud of this story because of the reporting involved and how it localized a state story. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/smokingTax.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/smokingTax.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>alabama,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fort Benning conducts mass casualty exercise</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you hear a lot of sirens and see emergency response vehicles near Fort Benning today, this is the most likely cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fort Benning personnel are conducting a “mass casualty exercise” today near Lawson Army Airfield, according to a release. The Army advises anyone entering post through the Fort Mitchell access point should prepare for delays between now and noon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exercise will also close Sunshine Road along the airfield for 15 minutes once it begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The release said the exercise would help keep first responders’ skills sharp in the event of an actual emergency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/benningExercise.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/19/benningExercise.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus police officer connects with community</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cpl. Travis Spencer of the Columbus Police Department was spotted doing some good today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missy Behar said she posted this photo of Spencer handing out badge-shaped stickers to several children to Facebook. Spencer didn’t know about the picture until someone tagged him in it later in the day. It was taken between 12 p.m. and 1:30 p.m. Friday afternoon at Jim Bob’s Chicken Fingers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spencer said the boy pictured, whose name he does not know, waved to him several times as he was eating. Spencer said he then went out to his vehicle and got a roll of stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The corporal, who is six-foot-three, said he made sure to crouch down to the 3-4-year-old’s level before talking to the excited child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I love it,” Spencer said. “If a kid says hello and is excited to see you, you have to talk to them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spencer is a part of the Crime Prevention Unit, a group within CPD that does outreach events at churches and schools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We try to engage children, make sure they’re not afraid of us,” Spencer said. “Kinda breaks down barriers between us and the community.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behar said she took  wanted to document Spencer’s actions for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I thought, ‘Well, that’s so sweet,’” Behar said. “He just seemed so nice.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mary Katherine Holton, who was also at the restaurant, said she thought it was sweet as well for Spencer to talk to everyone like that during his lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just hope more people get to see police officers do the right thing,” Holton said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/stickers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/09/stickers.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>human</category>
        
        <category>interest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
