<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 11:50:28 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 11:50:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two dogs are recovering after being chained together</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two American bulldogs were brought to Animal Ark Rescue by Columbus Animal Care &amp;amp; Control yesterday in rough shape, according to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/118069674930375/photos/a.118483231555686.17028.118069674930375/911782775559057/?type=3&amp;amp;theater&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; by the Rescue on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animal control officers found the two chained together for “breeding purposes” when responding to a complaint in Columbus backyard, the post said. The heavy metal chain was padlocked and drawn so tightly, the Rescue wrote, that it embedded into the dogs’ necks and caused painful injuries. The two had to be tranquilized and cut apart with bolt cutters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dogs are recovering at the Animal Ark Rescue according to Charlene Rallo, a full-time volunteer for the Rescue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rallo said these kinds of cases are sadly common. In her year working for the Rescue, she said she’s seen four or five similar incidents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is unknown if Animal Care &amp;amp; Control plans to bring charges against the owner. They did not return multiple calls to their office for comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rallo said the dogs are named Devin and Lacey. She guesses they are both 2-year-old American bulldogs. Devin was injured most and will take three to four weeks to recover. Even then, the damage will leave a mark until the hair grows back. Lacey should recover slightly faster in “a few weeks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Rescue staff plans to spay and neuter the dogs (as required by law) and  before putting them up for adoption, according to Rallo. There is already some interest in the dogs, as Rallo said some people have said they are mailing in donations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We just want to get them healthy,” Rallo said. “(This case) seems to have touched quite a few people’s hearts.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/10/02/dogsChained.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/10/02/dogsChained.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roaches found in DeKalb Starbucks during health inspection</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A Starbucks in the Atlanta area failed its health inspection for issues with roaches, among other problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Starbucks, located on North Druid Hills Road in DeKalb County, received a score of 65 out of 100 from health inspectors according to WSB-TV. Violations included roaches crawling under the espresso machine and on the floor in front of the hand-washing sink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An inspector said he saw an employee put his or her hand into a trash can and then use food utensils without and hand washing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We immediately engaged a third party vendor to conduct a thorough inspection and in-depth cleaning of our store following this health inspection,” said Jaime Riley, spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsbtv.com/news/news/local/dekalb-county-starbucks-fails-health-inspection/nnrmD/&quot;&gt;WSB-TV has the rest of the story.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;object id=&quot;flashObj&quot; width=&quot;615&quot; height=&quot;392&quot; classid=&quot;clsid:D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000&quot; codebase=&quot;http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,47,0&quot;&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;movie&quot; value=&quot;http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;bgcolor&quot; value=&quot;#FFFFFF&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;flashVars&quot; value=&quot;videoId=4521768591001&amp;amp;linkBaseURL=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wsbtv.com%2Fvideos%2Fnews%2Fstarbucks-near-toco-hills-shopping-plaza-fails%2FvDbww3%2F&amp;amp;playerID=836827756001&amp;amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAAFIvhljk~,Nz7UFI321EYSAUsYGYx5WAk9m9XiXaY8&amp;amp;domain=embed&amp;amp;dynamicStreaming=true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;base&quot; value=&quot;http://admin.brightcove.com&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;seamlesstabbing&quot; value=&quot;false&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowFullScreen&quot; value=&quot;true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;swLiveConnect&quot; value=&quot;true&quot; /&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;allowScriptAccess&quot; value=&quot;always&quot; /&gt;&lt;embed src=&quot;http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&quot; bgcolor=&quot;#FFFFFF&quot; flashvars=&quot;videoId=4521768591001&amp;amp;linkBaseURL=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wsbtv.com%2Fvideos%2Fnews%2Fstarbucks-near-toco-hills-shopping-plaza-fails%2FvDbww3%2F&amp;amp;playerID=836827756001&amp;amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAAFIvhljk~,Nz7UFI321EYSAUsYGYx5WAk9m9XiXaY8&amp;amp;domain=embed&amp;amp;dynamicStreaming=true&quot; base=&quot;http://admin.brightcove.com&quot; name=&quot;flashObj&quot; width=&quot;615&quot; height=&quot;392&quot; seamlesstabbing=&quot;false&quot; type=&quot;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; swliveconnect=&quot;true&quot; allowscriptaccess=&quot;always&quot; pluginspage=&quot;http://www.macromedia.com/shockwave/download/index.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash&quot; /&gt;&lt;/object&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/briefs,/viral,/ledger/2015/10/01/dekalbStarbucks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/briefs,/viral,/ledger/2015/10/01/dekalbStarbucks.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hardaway graduate appears on &#39;Price is Right&#39;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hardaway graduate and former Columbus resident Michelle Ekwoge got the surprise of her life when her name was called during a taping of “The Price is Right.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cbs.com/shows/the_price_is_right/video/&quot;&gt;Watch the “Price is Right” episode with Michelle Ekwoge&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ekwoge bought tickets to be in the audience at a taping July 6. The show aired yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s everybody’s dream [to be on the show], right?” she asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said she talked to a producer and gave him a hug before the show during a segment. Ekwoge said she did not realize the segment was for the producers to figure out who to call up onto the stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was just trying to find a way to stand out,” Ekwoge said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her hug must have worked, because she was called down to be a contestant after the first commercial break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was so excited,” she said. “I just wanted to get down there as soon as possible in case they made a mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ekwoge guessed the price of several items but did not win a round and pass onto a solo contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the show, Ekwoge said she got $300 for her trouble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ll keep it or use it to pay a bill or something,” she said, laughing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ekwoge said some aspects of attending “The Price is Right” surprised her. She said she saw people who won major prizes like cars and vacations turn down some of them because of the taxes involved. California, where the show is filmed, has a heavy gift tax that can make keeping prizes &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.accountingweb.com/tax/individuals/can-you-afford-free-taxes-spoil-the-game-show-win&quot;&gt;an expensive proposition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ekwoge graduated from Hardaway High School in 2007 and Georgia State. She moved to Oakland two years ago and works as an office manager in San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/pageants,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/30/priceIsRight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/pageants,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/30/priceIsRight.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>pageants,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Date, time and channel for the Alabama-Georgia game</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;No. 8 Georgia and No. 13 Alabama are set to play each other today in Athens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game starts today, Oct. 3, at 3:30 p.m. Eastern (2:30 p.m. Central) on CBS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Georgia is coming off an easy 48-6 win against Southern last week. The defense limited Southern to 184 total yards, and only 10 first downs. Running back Nick Chubb rushed for more than 100 yards for a 12th straight game. He is now one 100-yard game away from breaking Herschel Walker’s school record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Alabama’s side, the Crimson Tide is looking to prove that they’re still a top-10 contender. A 14-0 lead at halftime in last week’s game against Louisiana Monroe was nothing to write home about, but the Tide’s defense was fairly impressive in a 34-0 win. The defense racked up six sacks, had two interceptions and held ULM to 91 total yards (nine rushing yards). Alabama will need to find more offensive consistency if it hopes to get past Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check back for our live coverage of the game.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/sports,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/30/alaGaGame.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/sports,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/30/alaGaGame.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russell County Sheriff&#39;s Office offers reward for information on armed robbers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Russell County Sheriff’s Office is offering a $5,000 reward for information leading to the arrest and conviction of the people responsible for the armed robbery of City Grill on Sept. 16 and Dollar General on Sept. 26 in Hurtsboro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two black men held City Grill’s owner and a Dollar General employee at gunpoint before taking undisclosed amounts of cash in the two robberies, according to a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/55849517861/photos/a.10150275462792862.339881.55849517861/10153245737497862/?type=3&amp;amp;theater&quot;&gt;release&lt;/a&gt; from the sheriff’s office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone with relevant information should contact Inv. Allen Newman at (334) 664 - 9856 or Inv. Bob Atkin at (334) 297 - 0101.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/09/29/rusCoReward.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/09/29/rusCoReward.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Batman take these Columbus girls trick-or-treating</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Anthony St. Pierre wants to make sure two Columbus girls have a fun Halloween, even after their family lost their trailer in a fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre plans to take them trick-or-treating from fire station #4 to every other fire station in Columbus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre, who’s worked as a firefighter paramedic for 10 years, said he saw Raven and Robin after a fire destroyed their trailer near the corner of Old Cusseta Road and Allied Drive two weeks ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I saw those kids and thought of my own,” St. Pierre said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre said he did not know the last names of Raven, 2, and Robin, 5. Their family did not immediately respond to calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fire medic said the Columbus Fire Department Brotherhood will buy the girls costumes to wear. Robin wants to dress up as Princess Aurora from “Sleeping Beauty,” and Raven will probably go as Batgirl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a big comic book fan, St. Pierre plans to go as Batman. He said he had the costume from a previous trip to DragonCon in Atlanta and really likes the character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the rest of Halloween work, St. Pierre said, the family will need donations of candy and any kind of supplies to rebuild a house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They lost everything,” St. Pierre said. “Just take whatever you can to the closest fire station. Even if you can just give a candy bar, that’s great.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/human-interest,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/29/batman.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/human-interest,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/29/batman.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>human-interest,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Watch the Army commercial featuring female Ranger School graduate Kristen Griest</title>
        <description>&lt;div style=&quot;position:relative;width:100%;padding-top:56.25%;padding-bottom:40px;&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;right:0;left:0;bottom:0;width:100%;height:100%;&quot; src=&quot;http://www.ispot.tv/share/ALAX&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than four weeks after Capt. Kristen Griest and 1st Lt. Shaye Haver became &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article31334486.html&quot;&gt;the first women to graduate from Ranger School&lt;/a&gt;, Griest is one of several soldiers featured in an advertisement for the Army.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The photo is part of a montage showing her carrying another soldier. You can see it 6 seconds into the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture was taken at Fort Benning on April 20 during close arms combat training in Ranger School by Spc. Nikayla Shodeen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ispot.tv/ad/ALAX/us-army-never-stop&quot;&gt;iSpot.tv&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/army,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/24/armyCommercial.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/army,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/24/armyCommercial.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phenix City native looks to raise for heart transplant</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Steven Moore has a bad heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I do well enough,” Moore said. “I get tired easily and can’t work.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Phenix City native is attempting to raise money through a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gofundme.com/Steven-Moore&quot;&gt;GoFundMe page&lt;/a&gt;. After years of working as a volunteer firefighter in Seale and youth group leader for St. Mark Free Will Baptist Church, he’s hoping people will give back for a surgery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore said he was born and bred in Phenix City, graduating from Central High School. In 1973, he left to join the Army where he worked as a Morse code translator. In 1977, Moore started a 25-year career in aviation. The job took him all over the country as he worked his way up from cleaner to regional manager of the Northeast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After he couldn’t do the work any more, Moore kept himself busy as a volunteer firefighter in Seale. He worked as a first responder and firefighter, burning buildings and all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the last three to four years, though, he said he stuck to “engineer” duties to stay out of the front line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he felt the defibulator shock his pacemaker twice during a traffic accident, though, Moore said he knew it was time to retire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore’s heart has been bad for a while. After five heart attacks and six stents and two pacemakers, it can’t pump blood like most people’s hearts can. According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cpmc.org/services/heart/tx/ejectionfraction.html&quot;&gt;Sutter Health Network&lt;/a&gt;, a normal heart can pump out 55 to 75 percent of the blood within it with every heartbeat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore said his heart can pump 15 percent, well below the norm. It means he can’t drink more than two liters of liquids a day or his lungs fill up with fluid. A bad heart means he could drown on dry land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The heart’s worn out,” Moore said. “The muscle, it’s not there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This April was the tipping point. Moore suffered a fifth heart attack while in the hospital for a GI bleed from an ulcer. It was time for a change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore is on the heart transplant list. In six months to a year, he’ll have to move to Birmingham to stay close to the hospital at UAB for the surgery and recovery. Medicare covers 70 percent of the $300,000 surgery, but not all of it. It also doesn’t cover the drugs that will keep his body from rejecting the heart, or the costs of moving close to Birmingham to stay close to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore doesn’t have a lot of other financial options. He can’t work. His wife, Kathy, has had two strokes, an elbow injury from a car crash and is legally blind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s been a journey for us,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore said he needs the transplant so he can go back to work. He doesn’t know when it’ll be his turn for a transplant. If it doesn’t work out, it means trying to get a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/heart-failure/left-ventricular-assist-device&quot;&gt;left ventricular assist device&lt;/a&gt; (LVAD, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sm.stanford.edu/archive/stanmed/2014spring/article3.html&quot;&gt;the thing Dick Cheney used&lt;/a&gt;) or accepting the worst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moore said he hopes people will help with some of his costs for the transplant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“With the faith I have, God puts no more on you than you can handle,” Moore said. “Seems like a pretty hard test of faith sometimes. God has a plan for all of us. He has something else for me out there.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/human-interest,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/23/stevenMoore.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/human-interest,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/23/stevenMoore.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>human-interest,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neil Patrick Harris was Big Al when Alabama played Wisconsin</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you see Big Al at Alabama’s opener against Wisconsin? That was Neil Patrick Harris, star of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C19US6rqqAo&quot;&gt;“How I Met Your Mother”&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mrERtikdPus&quot;&gt;“Doogie Howser”&lt;/a&gt;. He started a variety show called “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbc.com/best-time-ever&quot;&gt;Best Time Ever&lt;/a&gt;” and followed a couple from Tuscaloosa for the first episode. One of his disguises? Big Al.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NPH wore the full costume onto the field and spent some time as the mascot (twerking) before going into the stands to dance weirdly in place next to the couple and get on the kiss cam. If you’ve ever wondered what it looks like when Big Al tries to give two people a kiss, well… it’s really just a hug.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s some more dancing and a lot of NPH sweating inside the costume. Being Big Al ain’t easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watch the segment below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div itemprop=&quot;video&quot; itemscope=&quot;&quot; itemtype=&quot;http://schema.org/VideoObject&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;270&quot; seamless=&quot;seamless&quot; src=&quot;//player.theplatform.com/p/NnzsPC/widget/select/media/GbFWjxdflg1B?carouselID=241966&quot; width=&quot;480&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[h/t &lt;a href=&quot;http://bamahammer.com/2015/09/15/neil-patrick-harris-was-big-al-at-alabama-vs-wisconsin/&quot;&gt;Bamahammer&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/sports,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/16/nph.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/sports,/viral,/ledger/2015/09/16/nph.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>viral,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Phenix City police find this robbery suspect</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police are looking for the man pictured above. He is suspected of robbing Walmart Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suspect attempted to exit Walmart without paying for merchandise, according to police. Police said when the man was confronted by loss prevention, he began fighting with them, pulled out a knife and threatened employees. He then fled in a white SUV, according to the PC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=890958827606389&amp;amp;id=224351267600485&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police describe the suspect as 6-foot, 160-pound white man with dark hair, a goatee and tattoos on both arms. Anyone with information on the incident should call the Phenix City police at one of the numbers below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Staudinger - (334) 448 - 2837&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Whitten - (334) 448 - 2825&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capt. Ivey - (334) 448 - 2836&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.kylenazario.com/blog/assets/walmartguy.jpg&quot; class=&quot;imgRight&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Phenix City police arrested Haroldean Peace III and charged him with first-degree robbery, according to the PCPD Facebook page. Police cited “numerous tips” identifying Pearce. He was arrested without incident in Smiths Station, according to police.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/crime,/briefs,/ledger/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>briefs,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
