<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>Everything I&#39;ve had published at previous positions. Feel free to  browse my published works and see what I&#39;ve covered for previous  and current jobs.
</description>
    <link>http://kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 12:54:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 12:54:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The internet hates this Columbus couple, but they&#39;re too happy to care</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A photo of two Columbus State students went viral four days ago, gathering more than 1.7 million views and more than a few negative reactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Stevens, 21, said she was attending the wedding of her cousin Dani Carlucci last Saturday in Norfolk, Va., with her boyfriend, Christopher Reed, 21, when she caught the new bride’s bouquet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens said she and Reed sat down after catching the bouquet and posed for a goofy photo with her father, Jim Stevens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said she posted the photo to her Facebook page that night before her friend Stephen Pace posted it to Reddit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reactions to the photo were generally negative, with most people implying that Stevens was too good-looking for Reed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens rebutted this, calling the reaction “shallow and rude.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have won the jackpot with Christopher,” she said. “He may not have rock-hard abs like the world tells girls to want in a guy, but really, why does that even matter when you are trying to really find someone you want to spend the rest of your life with? He is so thoughtful and patient… he is my best friend.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens said though she was offended by other people’s reactions at first, she now feels sorry for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s making us laugh a little bit because it’s people who are jealous,” Reed said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for catching the bouquet, Reed and Stevens said they have discussed marriage and it is something they are interested in. They said they plan to finish school first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to the people saying mean things about them on the internet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“People don’t define me or determine who I am,” Reed said. “God does. And thanks for making me internet famous.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://abcnews.go.com/GMA/video/mismatched-couple-fires-back-facebook-photo-viral-32514356&quot;&gt;Featured on ‘Good Morning America’!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/23/couple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/23/couple.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Award-winning kayakers take on Chattahoochee whitewater course</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of the best kayakers in the world rode the local rapids on a hot Georgia afternoon Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Claire O’Hara won seven world championships in various kayaking events in eight years. She called the rapids on the Chattahoochee River “amazing” after her first time on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They were super smooth and super fast,” she said before getting into a second boat to go out again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jez Jezz has won three kayaking World Cups and more than 10 national championships. He’s kayaked in Europe, Southeast Asia, New Zealand, Canada and South America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he’s impressed by what the area has on the Chattahoochee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a world-class feature,” Jezz said. “Waves are hard to create.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz and O’Hara both rode the rapids in short, wide kayaks. They bounced around in a trough in front of a curve of foam. O’Hara dipped under the water as her kayak flipped, only to pop back up a moment later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz, the head coach of the Australian freestyle kayaking team, said making artificial waves this well is impressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said the area is bound to change as soon as more people get wind of the kayaking courses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is still a bit of a sleeper,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Not many people know what you’ve got down here, but people will flock to it. People travel the world to get to these features.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz coaches at Falling Creek Camp in North Carolina and teaches kayaking to children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he brought a group of 12 to 16-year-olds from the camp to Columbus so they could practice on the rapids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“For these kids, it’s perfect training,” he said. “Not only do I know I’m coming back, but for these kids it’s perfect training.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz watched the kids as they jumped into the rapids in short, wide kayaks, shouting encouragement when one finally landed a move he’d been practicing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In freestyle kayaking, Jezz explained, the boater has 45 seconds to do as many tricks and moves as possible. The move the kid did, called “the roundhouse,” involves aggressively moving into a wave edge before being bounced backward into the air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz said he also did some training for the World Championships in Ottowa, Canada, on the course. When he competes there in six weeks, he’ll have prepared in part on the Chattahoochee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’ve got such an amazing thing here,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/16/kayaker.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/16/kayaker.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shooters of Columbus criticized for target showing black teenager</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Shooters of Columbus faced a wave of criticism Tuesday when a Facebook post alleging racist practices by the store went viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Javell Woods posted an image of a black man with a gun on a target, which he said he found at Shooters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So I go to the range yesterday and this is the pic they had for target practice…. I ask if he had any teenage white males I could practice shooting at and he told me I was a racist,” Woods wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post was shared 59,234 times as of writing. A manager for Shooters of Columbus said the store received calls about it all day Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shooters management declined to reveal which staff member was on duty when Woods was shooting or if someone had told him that choosing a target with a white man was racist. Woods has not responded to requests for comment as of publication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They didn’t have a target on the shelf,” Woods wrote in a comment. “Not even an option. I’m making a life-size poster of the Brady Bunch and going back to wreck shop. It’s just sad that it’s even acceptable to buy something like this on the shelf.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David Peacock, who has worked for Shooters for a year, said there are many different targets people can choose to use on the the range. He said the target Woods posted showing a black teenager is one of many choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shooters of Columbus management showed the Ledger-Enquirer a dozen targets depicting real people sold by the store. Most were white men with guns, though there was a white woman and an Asian man as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who use Shooters’ range are free to buy any of those targets, according to Peacock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peacock said Shooters of Columbus orders its targets from Law Enforcement Targets. According to the company’s website, it provides targets for the government and law enforcement agencies as well as shooting ranges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most popular target at Shooters, according to Peacock, is actually an image of a zombie from the television show “The Walking Dead.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m really sorry the internet was not factual for the first time in history,” Peacock said. “If we only offered black posters I wouldn’t be working here.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/15/shooters.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/15/shooters.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greenville woman dies in three-car collision</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A Greenville woman died in a three-vehicle crash at 5:30 p.m. on Thursday on U.S. Route 29 at the 167 mile marker, 1.5 miles south of Troy, according to Alabama state troopers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said Amanda Suzanne Carter, 23, was a passenger in a 2007 Nissan Altima driven by Salena Kathleen Stephens, 24.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Altima side-swiped a 2012 Ford driven by Tiffany Rena Hill, a 23-year-old Troy woman, according to police. The troopers said the Altima then struck a 2005 Jeep Wrangler driven by Justin Tyler Jacobs, a 31-year-old Rutledge man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pike County Coroner Jerry Williams pronounced Carter dead at the scene, according to the release. Police said the four children in the Altima and Jacobs were transported to local hospitals for non-life-threatening injuries. Hill and Stephens were not injured, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said they are still investigating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/10/greenville%20crash.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/10/greenville%20crash.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dog with terminal cancer adopted for final adventures with Columbus woman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Nicole Elliott, 24, said she aims to help her dog live as much as possible in the time he has left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott adopted Chester from Animal Ark Rescue on June 27. She’d been following pictures of him posted on Facebook and decided to take him home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To call Chester a tough adoption, however, would be an understatement. The dog is 13 or 14 years old and had a large tumor his previous owners had neglected to fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott is unsure about Chester’s age or breed (probably a miniature schnauzer), only that he was in rough shape when he was surrendered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I thought about it for a while and decided it’d be something I could take on,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chester has mast cell cancer. Despite removing a large tumor, the disease is rapidly spreading all over his body. He also has heartworms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott said the veterinarians aren’t sure how long he has left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t really think he has much time, but it’s up to him and the cancer,” she said. “I just want him to experience as many things that normal dogs do as possible.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott said she spoils Chester with extra treats, shopping trips, Bruster’s Doggy Sundaes and trips to the park, where Chester loves playing in the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He seems to be absorbing all the love I’m giving him,” Elliott said, calling the dog “very sweet” and “playful.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A trip to the beach, a boat ride and more trips to the park are in Chester’s future, provided he’s healthy enough to make them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I wish I would have gotten him sooner,” Elliott said. “It’s hard because I’ve already fallen in love with him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott said she’s been overwhelmed with the response to her story, which was featured on Good Morning America and has gone viral on Facebook. She said she hopes people will adopt more older pets or other animals less likely to be taken home from the shelter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliott declined to accept donations for Chester. She prefers people donate to Animal Ark Rescue’s senior hospice program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It feels really good to be making that impact,” she said. “[Older animals] make really good pets. They deserve it.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/07/cancerdog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/07/cancerdog.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus Police- Burglary suspect commits suicide during standoff with officers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A burglary suspect committed suicide during a standoff with authorities, Columbus Police Maj. J.D. Hawk said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pamela Ann Skinner, 55, was pronounced dead of a self-inflicted gunshot wound to the chest today at 2:15 p.m., Muscogee County Coroner Buddy Bryan said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At about 7 p.m. Sunday, Columbus police went to the woman’s mobile home in the 900 block of Joy Road to arrest Skinner on a burglary warrant, Hawk said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When they approached the door and knocked on it, they were told to get away and a shot was fired through the wall of the trailer,” Hawk said. “The officers backed off and began negotiating with the individual.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said the standoff continued into the night and another shot was fired from the trailer after midnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They talked to the individual as late as 7 a.m. this morning and lost contact from then on,” Hawk said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Officials went into the residence before 2:15 p.m. and found the woman with a gunshot wound to the chest. No one else was injured, Hawk said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joseph Braxton Jr., the woman’s neighbor, said she had some mental issues and was diagnosed with cancer last Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She wasn’t really a bad lady,” Braxton said. “She just had drug problems.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/06/standoff.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/06/standoff.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Muscogee County issues first same-sex marriage license</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vtrbvD22CEQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Updated story: James Wherry and Mario Jay Jamandron Occena, now Mario Jay Wherry, were married today at about 4:30 p.m. by Judge Marc D’Antonio. The two were the first same-sex couple to receive a marriage license from Muscogee County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m very happy about it,” James Wherry said. “Marriage is the bedrock of our society. I hope that same-sex couples can rejuvenate and revitalize marriage and give it the respect it is due.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Wherry said he and Mario Jay Wherry met through gaymatchmaker.com. James Wherry proposed and flew to the Philippines to hold an engagement party with Mario Jay Wherry and his family. Mario Jay Wherry arrived in the United States at the end of May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the two heard about the Supreme Court decision, they came to the courthouse at approximately 4 p.m. Friday to obtain a marriage license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“MARRIAGE IS THE BEDROCK OF OUR SOCIETY”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Wherry, who describes himself as a conservative Republican, said he wishes same-sex marriage could have been legalized through the legislature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In many places, it was done with the legislature,” James Wherry said. “However, legislatures are sometimes driven by minorities and special-interest groups and it’s necessary for the court to pry those apart.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, though, James Wherry and Mario Jay Wherry said they are happy to be married and appreciate the overwhelming support they’ve received from friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Wherry said the two plan to go to Disney World for their honeymoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It feels good,” James Wherry said. “We’ll try this for 50 years and if it doesn’t work out we’ll get a divorce.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Original story: The Muscogee County Probate Court office will begin marrying same-sex couples immediately, Judge Marc D’Antonio said Friday at noon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision comes in the wake of the U.S. Supreme Court’s decision earlier in the day to make such unions legal in all 50 states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I am going to continue to do marriages, I can’t discriminate,” D’Antonio said. “… I took an oath to follow the law of the land, and this is the law of the land now.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of noon, no same-sex marriages had been performed in the Columbus government center, D’Antonio said. His office has received a number of inquiries since the landmark Supreme Court decision was announced mid-morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Across the river in Alabama, Russell County Probate Judge Alford Harden said his office would cease issuing marriage licenses for the remainder of Friday, then start Monday morning issuing them to all couples — gay and straight. His office, as has been the policy since earlier this year when the gay marriage issue surfaced in Alabama just ahead of the Supreme Court decision, will not perform marriage ceremonies for any couples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“THE SUPREME COURT IS THE LAW OF THE LAND, AND I WILL FOLLOW THE LAW OF THE LAND.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama probate judges have been dealing with conflicting judicial orders. A U.S. District Court judge has ordered Alabama probate judges to issue same-sex marriage licenses, while Alabama Supreme Court Judge Roy Moore has issued an order countering that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In my opinion, we have not had any general direction,” Harden said. “The Supreme Court is the law of the land, and I will follow the law of the land.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Georgia Attorney General Sam Olens, a Republican, wasted little time giving direction to that state’s probate judges, who are charged with issuing marriage licenses. Less than two hours after the Supreme Court ruling, Olens sent a directive to the probate judges telling them to follow the law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Today the Supreme Court of the United States ruled the Constitution requires a state to license a marriage between two people of the same sex and to recognize a marriage between two people of the same sex when their marriage was lawfully licensed and performed out of state,” Olens said in a statement. “It does not permit bans on same-sex marriage. In our system of government, the Supreme Court bears the ultimate responsibility for determining the constitutionality of our laws. Once the Supreme Court has ruled, its order is the law of the land. As such, Georgia will follow the law and adhere to the ruling of the court.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike in Alabama where many judges, including Harden, have chosen to cease performing all marriages, D’Antonio said he will not do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Columbus is a military town,” D’Antonio said. “We have a lot of service members who need to get married in short order. If I stopped doing marriages, I could not do the ones for the service members.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the judges on the Alabama side have stopped performing marriage ceremonies, D’Antonio said couples have been coming to his office to get married.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Muscogee County Probate Court can perform marriages for those who live outside the county and the state, but they have to purchase the license in Muscogee County. The form in Muscogee County already has changed from groom and bride to applicant 1 and applicant 2.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/26/license.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/26/license.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smiths Station graduate to perform on America&#39;s Got Talent</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A Smiths Station High School graduate and former Columbus State student will perform on “America’s Got Talent” tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brittney Allen said her audition will be featured when the show airs at 8 p.m. Eastern on NBC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I really didn’t think I was that interesting,” Allen said. “I was really surprised when I got picked.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allen said she performed her talent in front of the judges and more than a thousand people in the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She can’t say what her talent was or whether she passed before the show airs, but Allen said performing in front of so many people and TV cameras was nerve-wracking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I hardly remember anything from the audition,” Allen said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Smiths Station graduate said she went to Columbus State University to study music for a semester. She dropped the major because she wanted to pursue music on her own terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Allen lives with her fiancé Will Ortiz in Jacksonville. She said she misses Columbus and appreciates all the support her family and friends back home still give her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allen also said she hopes to continue her music career now that auditioning on “America’s Got Talent” has helped force her out of her comfort zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I hope this is my first step,” Allen said. “I feel more open and confident.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/23/allen.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/23/allen.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus canine sniffs source of forced fires</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Iggie is one of the most important tools in Columbus’ fight against arson, and he’s only two years old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iggie is a yellow lab trained to detect fire accelerants such as gasoline and other materials favored by arsonists. He’s one of only two dogs with such training in all of Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Arson is especially difficult to prove,” said Jeff Meyer, fire chief. “Having Iggie and having David will help protect the citizens of Columbus.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fire marshal Ricky Shores said human investigators can find accelerants used in a fire 30-40 percent of the time. Accelerant detection canines can find the materials used by arsonists in more than 90 percent of cases in just a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shores said the Columbus Fire Department looked into a double homicide last fall where the suspect attempted to cover the evidence with a fire. The department had to wait for an accelerant detection canine from north Alabama in order to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, when the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms offered to train a firefighter from Columbus on handling an accelerant detection canine, they accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do this job, Iggie was trained by the bureau in Front Royal, Va., for 12 weeks before returning to Columbus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firefighter David Smith worked with Iggie for the second six weeks of Iggie’s training in Front Royal as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There’s a lot of arson, but people don’t see it,” Smith said. “Good thing about Iggie is if an accelerant was used, he’ll find it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As his handler, Smith feeds Iggie every meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before meals, Smith said he hides a tin can or rag nearby and adds a few drops of an accelerant. When Iggie finds it, Smith feeds him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s basically like playing hide and seek with a dog twice a day,” Smith said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shores said the fire department keeps track of the arson rate over the last few years, and it hasn’t changed much. He said Smith and Iggie were trained as a way to be proactive and change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Shores, the dogs tend to have an eight-year service life. After that, the handler gets to keep the dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I can’t tell you how fortunate we are in Columbus to have this resource here,” Shores said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/19/firedog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/06/19/firedog.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Case dismissed against woman accused of using replica of pistol in robbery</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Update: The armed robbery charge issued against 62-year-old Linda Marshall was dismissed in Recorder’s Court in a Thursday morning hearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski dropped the case, because there was a lot hearsay but no witnesses attended the preliminary hearing to testify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 37-year-old victim told the court he actually handed the woman the hat when he was selling caps, but Columbus Police Officer Charles Hickman testified that the victim reported the item stolen on the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The replica that appeared to be a pistol was actually a cigarette lighter, Hickman said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Original Story: A Columbus man was robbed at gunpoint in the 2000 block of Amos Street on Sunday at 8:05 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linda Marshall, 62, was arrested and charged with armed robbery in connection with the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the report, the suspect pointed a “replica of [a] pistol” at the victim and used it to take a red, white and blue Gametek ball cap worth $4. No one was injured, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said they have recovered the cap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Reporter Sarah Robinson contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/05/25/replicapistol.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/05/25/replicapistol.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
