<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 14:09:59 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 14:09:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whose identical PSA was better, Gus Malzahn or Nick Saban?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Gus Malzahn and Nick Saban are going head to head in an unexpected contest: the public service announcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two head coaches recorded 30-second videos supporting a statewide voter identification drive run by John Merrill, Alabama’s secretary of state. They used the same script in both videos, changing only the names of each man’s wife and team battle cry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To be an impact player in football as well as in life, you have to be prepared to make a difference,” said Saban and Malzahn. “One of the most significant ways to make a positive impact on your community, state or nation is by participating in the electoral process.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our question for readers is, whose video was better? Gus seemed to stumble out of the block with reading the script. Saban had some issues with the way the camera framed only half of his hand motions and made them look odd. Who do you think won?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you don’t watch the videos, they’ll be played on the jumbotrons at Jordan-Hare and Bryant-Denny Stadium, according to a release. You can even get a poster of this from your local Board of Registrar’s office. It’s the perfect way to combine two of most commonly associated passions: football and voter registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;its-all-to-get-you-to-vote&quot;&gt;It’s all to get you to vote&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this is a way to help voters navigate Alabama’s somewhat confusing &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/&quot;&gt;voter registration laws&lt;/a&gt;. After the passage of HB-19 in 2011, Alabama voters need a valid form of photo identification to take part at the polls. Acceptable IDs include a driver’s license, passport or state, federal, government employee, military, tribal or student ID.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have any of those, you can pick up a free photo voter ID card from the courthouse, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/permanentLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;Board of Registrar’s office&lt;/a&gt; or one of these voter ID drives the secretary of state’s office is holding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clay Helms, supervisor of voter registration for the secretary of state’s office, said his office is working on holding a voter ID drive in all of Alabama’s 67 counties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helms said the Russell County drive already happened on July 1 at the Phenix City Activity Center and Hurtsboro City Hall. There are no plans at the moment to revisit Russell County, according to Helms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/mobileLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; of planned voter ID drive locations lists two visits to Lee County on Oct. 14 and Nov. 4. Both will be from 10 a.m. to 12 p.m. at Smiths Station City Hall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember also that in order to pick up your voter ID card, you need to already be registered to vote. You can do that by calling 1-800-274-8683 or visiting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.alabamavotes.gov/GetRegForm.aspx?m=voters&quot;&gt;Alabama’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to recap: Register to vote first, then go to the courthouse or one of the Lee County drives to get a free voter ID, but only if you don’t already have one of the other valid IDs listed above, and don’t forget to bring everything to the polls in November 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police- LaGrange man faces murder charge after infant dies in his care</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A LaGrange, Ga., man is facing a murder charge after police said a 4-month-old died in his care, according to a release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brandon Heard, 30, was arrested Thursday afternoon and charged with murder and first-degree cruelty to children. He is held in the Troup County Jail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaGrange police were called to the 1500 block of Hogansville Road Tuesday around 2:55 p.m. in reference to a child not breathing. Upon arrival, police found 4-month-old Skylar King unresponsive. The infant was taken to the West Georgia Medical Center where he was pronounced dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Georgia Bureau of Investigation conducted an autopsy Wednesday and found Skylar died from blunt-force trauma to the head, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said the injury was inflicted Tuesday by Heard, the boyfriend of Skylar’s mom. Heard was taking care of the child while the mother was at work, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case remains under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Update- Man shot earlier this week on 28th Avenue dies in hospital</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The man police say was shot early Thursday morning on 28th Avenue died Saturday at Midtown Medical Center, according to Muscogee County Coroner Buddy Bryan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simon Lee King Jr., 57, was pronounced dead at 2:20 p.m., Bryan said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witnesses told police King was walking down the street when a vehicle with two black men stopped next to him. After calling King over to the vehicle, they shot him, witnesses told police. The vehicle, which police believe was a silver or gold four-door sedan, was last seen fleeing the scene near Clover Lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King was said to have suffered from multiple gunshot wounds to the torso and arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to incident reports, the police were called to the 300 block of 28th Avenue around 12:46 a.m. Thursday. They found King lying in a driveway, according to an incident report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witnesses told authorities the suspects appeared to be between 19 and 24 years old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police believe one suspect has a slender build, low haircut and a medium-to-dark complexion. A description of the second individual wasn’t available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Columbus Police Department is asking for anyone with any knowledge about the homicide to contact Sgt. Ken Hudson at 706-225-4257 or the Robbery/Assault Unit at 706-653-3400.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King’s death comes three weeks after 56-year-old William Edwards was found dead in his tent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edwards, who was homeless, lived in an area called tent city near the Second Avenue bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Crime reporter Sarah Robinson contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/shootingDeath.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/shootingDeath.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12th Avenue home catches fire</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus fire and emergency services put out a house fire early Saturday morning near the corner of 12th Avenue and 32nd Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A home at 1206 12th Ave. caught fire sometime after 7 a.m., according to Capt. Mary Simonton. She couldn’t estimate the time of the call to emergency services, but said fire engine 2 was there within three minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blaze had subsided and firefighters were spraying down the house by approximately 8:30 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simonton said there were no major injuries, though a firefighter injured his ankle on the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sabine James, a neighbor who’s been friends with the house’s residents for 25 years, said she was just thankful no one was hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Everybody got out alive,” James said. “The rest can be replaced.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Lance Christenson said the fire spread into the front living room and attic before it was put out, causing an estimated $40,000 worth of damage. The fire department is treating the case as an accident and does not plan to investigate further, Christenson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon Dunbar, who lives in the home, said her house had burned down before on Christmas Day in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, Dunbar said she plans to stay with family until she figures out what to do next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have no clue [what’s next],” Dunbar said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/12fire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/12fire.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notasulga man arrested in connection to armed robbery</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auburn police said they arrested Marion D. Page, 21, of Notasulga on charges of first-degree burglary and first-degree robbery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said they found Page while investigating a burglary that occurred in the 60 block of Lee Road 872 on July 26. When warrants were issued for Page’s arrest, he turned himself in to detectives and was transported to the Lee County Jail, according to a release. Police said he is being held on a $125 bond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Page’s arrest is the second connected to the July 26 robbery. Auburn police also arrested Joshua M. Cameron, 20, on felony warrants for first-degree robbery and first-degree burglary, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initial reports from the robbery stated that Cameron and another unknown black man forcibly entered the Lee Road residence and demanded money before fleeing the residence on foot with an unspecified amount of cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victim sustained minor injuries in the incident and was treated by paramedics and at the East Alabama Medical Center emergency room.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/04/notaRobber.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/04/notaRobber.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>America&#39;s Got Talent Smiths Station singer cut from show</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A 24-year-old Smiths Station, Ala., native was eliminated Tuesday night on “America’s Got Talent” after the judges said she gave a disappointing performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brittney Allen did not pass to the second round following a rendition of “Too Close” by Alex Clare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The judges, which included Mel B, Heidi Klum, Howie Mandel and Howard Stern, unanimously disapproved of her song choice and backup track, saying it did not fit her voice. They said they would have preferred a ballad instead of something as electronic as “Too Close.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allen told the Ledger-Enquirer the song was not her first choice and was picked for her by the producers of “America’s Got Talent.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said she emailed them a list of five songs (all ballads) and was instead told to perform the Alex Clare song.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I do slow, pretty stuff,” Allen said. “They put a weird dubstep track. That’s not who I am, though. I did what I could with what I had.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allen said she wishes she could have chosen a different song, but she understands reality TV isn’t always what it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She also said she did not realize she would be performing in front of an 800-person audience and Marlon Wayans, a celebrity guest judge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The singer, who suffers from persistent stage fright, felt more nervous singing without a guitar as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It wasn’t my best,” Allen said. “I learned from it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said she plans to keep focusing on music between her jobs at Kohl’s and LongHorn Steakhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t even dwell on it that I didn’t make it,” Allen said. “I have so many people supporting me.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/28/agtCut.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/28/agtCut.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man convicted of murdering 8-month-old son</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The jury returned with a guilty verdict in the case of Shane Eric Hinkson just before noon Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hinkson was found not guilty on one count of malice murder, but guilty on a lesser included charge of involuntary manslaughter, two counts of felony murder, one count of aggravated assault and one count of first-degree cruelty to children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jury returned with a unanimous verdict in Hinkson’s case around 10:20 a.m. When Judge Frank Jordan silently read it, he called the counsel for both sides to his bench for a conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The court recessed until 11 a.m., when the judge conferred with the lawyers again. The court then recessed until 11:40 a.m., when the jury returned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The defense asked Jordan for time to prepare before sentencing. Hinkson’s sentencing is scheduled for Aug. 20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The jury sided with the prosecution’s version of events, which said that Hinkson deliberately threw the child down in a fit of anger. They declined to convict Hinkson on malice murder, but did declare him guilty of felony murder for doing so and not calling 911 as soon as he discovered the baby was hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prosecutor William Hocutt IV told jurors Hinkson had told police in a recorded interview that he was having trouble holding his temper after service in Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I got angry,” Hinkson said in the interview. “Sometimes I can’t control myself.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three physicians testified in the case and all said the baby died from abusive head trauma from being violently shaken or slammed down on a soft surface. The infant’s brain was smashed against the inside of his skull, leaving internal bleeding and swelling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The prosecution also cited testimony from the baby’s mother, Jennifer Cabanayan, who said Hinkson called her and said “something bad had happened.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the verdict was read, Hinkson hugged his lawyers and left the courtroom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/24/shane.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/24/shane.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The internet hates this Columbus couple, but they&#39;re too happy to care</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A photo of two Columbus State students went viral four days ago, gathering more than 1.7 million views and more than a few negative reactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Stevens, 21, said she was attending the wedding of her cousin Dani Carlucci last Saturday in Norfolk, Va., with her boyfriend, Christopher Reed, 21, when she caught the new bride’s bouquet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens said she and Reed sat down after catching the bouquet and posed for a goofy photo with her father, Jim Stevens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said she posted the photo to her Facebook page that night before her friend Stephen Pace posted it to Reddit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/3akgg7/my_friend_caught_the_bouquet_that_is_her/&quot;&gt;reactions&lt;/a&gt; to the photo were generally negative, with most people implying that Stevens was too good-looking for Reed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;quote&quot;&gt;“Thanks for making me internet famous.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens rebutted this, calling the reaction “shallow and rude.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have won the jackpot with Christopher,” she said. “He may not have rock-hard abs like the world tells girls to want in a guy, but really, why does that even matter when you are trying to really find someone you want to spend the rest of your life with? He is so thoughtful and patient… he is my best friend.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens said though she was offended by other people’s reactions at first, she now feels sorry for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s making us laugh a little bit because it’s people who are jealous,” Reed said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for catching the bouquet, Reed and Stevens said they have discussed marriage and it is something they are interested in. They said they plan to finish school first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to the people saying mean things about them on the internet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“People don’t define me or determine who I am,” Reed said. “God does. And thanks for making me internet famous.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://abcnews.go.com/GMA/video/mismatched-couple-fires-back-facebook-photo-viral-32514356&quot;&gt;Featured on ‘Good Morning America’!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/23/couple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/23/couple.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Update- Missing autistic Phenix City 16-year-old found</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A 16-year-old Phenix City boy with severe autism was found Tuesday about two hours after he was reported missing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Timothy Robinson was located in a deep ravine by an Alabama Law Enforcement Agency’s helicopter after he was seen on a neighbor’s security camera. Authorities said he appeared exhausted while lying on the ground between two logs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The helicopter crew directed law enforcement personnel to the teen who was taken to a waiting ambulance. Police sent out a notice at 2:56 p.m. that an aviation unit located Robinson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a heat index of triple digits, Secretary of Law Enforcement Spencer Collier said the search could have ended differently. “With a triple digit heat index, today’s rescue of the missing 16-year-old could have had a tragic ending without ALEA’s Aviation Unit. This unit provides an essential state service as we assist in rescue efforts throughout the state,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A missing child alert was issued of the teen after he was discovered missing from his residence on Williamsburg Drive in Phenix City, according to a release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authorities said the 5-foot-4 inch Robinson is autistic and unable to verbally communicate. He was last seen wearing a white t-shirt and pull-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone with information on his whereabouts was asked to contact the Phenix City Police Department at 334- 298-0611.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/21/missingPC.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/21/missingPC.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Award-winning kayakers take on Chattahoochee whitewater course</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of the best kayakers in the world rode the local rapids on a hot Georgia afternoon Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Claire O’Hara won seven world championships in various kayaking events in eight years. She called the rapids on the Chattahoochee River “amazing” after her first time on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They were super smooth and super fast,” she said before getting into a second boat to go out again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jez Jezz has won three kayaking World Cups and more than 10 national championships. He’s kayaked in Europe, Southeast Asia, New Zealand, Canada and South America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he’s impressed by what the area has on the Chattahoochee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a world-class feature,” Jezz said. “Waves are hard to create.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz and O’Hara both rode the rapids in short, wide kayaks. They bounced around in a trough in front of a curve of foam. O’Hara dipped under the water as her kayak flipped, only to pop back up a moment later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz, the head coach of the Australian freestyle kayaking team, said making artificial waves this well is impressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said the area is bound to change as soon as more people get wind of the kayaking courses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is still a bit of a sleeper,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Not many people know what you’ve got down here, but people will flock to it. People travel the world to get to these features.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz coaches at Falling Creek Camp in North Carolina and teaches kayaking to children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he brought a group of 12 to 16-year-olds from the camp to Columbus so they could practice on the rapids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“For these kids, it’s perfect training,” he said. “Not only do I know I’m coming back, but for these kids it’s perfect training.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz watched the kids as they jumped into the rapids in short, wide kayaks, shouting encouragement when one finally landed a move he’d been practicing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In freestyle kayaking, Jezz explained, the boater has 45 seconds to do as many tricks and moves as possible. The move the kid did, called “the roundhouse,” involves aggressively moving into a wave edge before being bounced backward into the air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jezz said he also did some training for the World Championships in Ottowa, Canada, on the course. When he competes there in six weeks, he’ll have prepared in part on the Chattahoochee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’ve got such an amazing thing here,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/16/kayaker.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/07/16/kayaker.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
