<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:29:46 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 14:29:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Phenix City police find this robbery suspect</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police are looking for the man pictured above. He is suspected of robbing Walmart Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suspect attempted to exit Walmart without paying for merchandise, according to police. Police said when the man was confronted by loss prevention, he began fighting with them, pulled out a knife and threatened employees. He then fled in a white SUV, according to the PC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=890958827606389&amp;amp;id=224351267600485&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police describe the suspect as 6-foot, 160-pound white man with dark hair, a goatee and tattoos on both arms. Anyone with information on the incident should call the Phenix City police at one of the numbers below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Staudinger - (334) 448 - 2837&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Whitten - (334) 448 - 2825&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capt. Ivey - (334) 448 - 2836&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Miss Alabama on Donald Trump- Republicans should be &#39;absolutely terrified&#39;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Meg McGuffin, a former Miss Phenix City and Auburn student, had some harsh words for Donald Trump at last night’s Miss America contest. When asked why Trump has an impressive lead over the rest of the Republican Party, McGuffin didn’t hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think Donald Trump is an entertainer,” McGuffin said. “I think he says what’s on a lot of people’s minds but I think that the Republican Party should be absolutely terrified of all the attention he’s taking from credible candidates like Jeb Bush and Chris Christie who can absolutely do the job of president of the United States. And, if I were a Republican, I would absolutely be terrified of that. Thank you so much.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McGuffin was supported by a group from the Miss Phenix City program who made the trip to New Jersey. McGuffin, a former winner from Ozark, Ala., said she aims to pursue a Ph.D. in education leadership funded by her winnings from pageants, which total more than $80,000 after she finished in fourth place at last night’s Miss America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will hopefully attain my Ph.D. and be student-debt free,” McGuffin said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Meg McGuffin posted this on Facebook:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. Last night, I was named the 95th 4th Runner-Up to Miss America. Had I placed 52nd or 1st, I am proud of the way I...&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL&quot;&gt;Miss Alabama Meg McGuffin&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot;&gt;Monday, September 14, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29458081.html&quot;&gt;profile on Meg McGuffin&lt;/a&gt;, as well as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/entertainment/article29461165.html&quot;&gt;Miss America (and Miss Georgia) Betty Cantrell&lt;/a&gt;. If you missed the show, there’s also a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/entertainment/article35149809.html&quot;&gt;recap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dmusMt2A8BA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[h/t &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?t=1&amp;amp;v=dmusMt2A8BA&quot;&gt;Yellowhammer&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/missAmerica.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/missAmerica.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man charged with murder in fatal shooting of Columbus woman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Phenix City Police have charged 18-year-old Demetrius Devonta Dorsey with the murder of Mariah Farrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dorsey was taken into custody without incident around 11:15 a.m. today. Members of Phenix City Police Departments Criminal Investigation Division and the U.S. Marshals Gulf Coast Regional Task Force executed a search and arrest warrant at 2601 14th Court in that resulted in Dorsey’s arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th Street and 10th Court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th Street and 10th Court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is currently incarcerated in Russell County Jail, authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City Police would like anyone who may have firsthand information pertinent to the investigation to contact Phenix City Police Criminal Investigations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Story&lt;/strong&gt;: A 19-year-old Columbus woman suffering from a gunshot wound died this morning at Midtown Medical Center, according to a post by Phenix City Police on their Facebook page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police said they received reports of shots fired in the 1000 block of 16th Street around 11:50 p.m. Sunday but did not find anyone when they arrived. They said they were notified by Columbus police “a short time later” that a woman had been driven to Midtown Medical Center while suffering from multiple gunshot wounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hospital personnel were unable to revive 19-year-old Mariah Farrow, a 2015 graduate of Carver High School and current Columbus State University student. She was pronounced at 12:18 a.m., Russell County Coroner Arthur Sumbry Jr. said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her body will be transported to the Department of Forensic Sciences in Montgomery for an autopsy, according to the coroner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police said they are investigating the case and are “currently interviewing a number of witnesses.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th street and 10th court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 2:45 p.m. Monday, CSU sent out an email to their students, faculty and staff informing them about Farrow’s death, according to CSU Communications Specialist Christa Robbins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unofficial statement reads as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSU students, faculty and staff,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It is with great sadness that we report the death of a Columbus State University freshman, Mariah Farrow, 19, an undeclared first-term, first-year student from Columbus. She was apparently involved in an off-campus shooting last evening.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please keep the family in your thoughts and prayers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone with additional information on the case should contact the Phenix City Police Department Criminal Investigations Division. The police dispatch number is 334-298-0611.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Staff writer Sarah Robinson contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/csuShooting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/csuShooting.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police- Man caught after fleeing on sight from police</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus Police testified in Recorder’s Court Friday that Jasper D. Dunlap, 22, was arrested after a foot chase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An officer said when he approached a group outside Wilson Apartments at 3400 8th Ave. on possible loitering charges, Dunlap took off running. Police said they caught him after a foot chase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time the chase ended, the other members of the group had already disappeared, according to the officer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dunlap, who police said gave a false name, was identified at Muscogee County Jail as being someone on probation and who had an outstanding warrant for theft by taking a motor vehicle, according to testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He pleaded not guilty to charges of loitering, obstructing a law enforcement officer, theft by taking a motor vehicle, violation of probation and giving false information to an officer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set his bond at $1,000 for obstruction, $500 for false information and a 30-day suspended sentence. He then bound the case over to state court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/dunlap.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/dunlap.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Woman denies involving 2-year-old in sex</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Shannon Crisp, 23, pleaded not guilty Friday morning in Recorder’s Court to charges of child molestation. She also pleaded guilty to sexual exploitation of children and enticing a child for an indecent purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crisp was arrested after the Sex Crimes division investigated a case of child molestation involving an adult male and female juvenile, according to testimony from Cpl. Brittney Hayes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said police seized a computer and other electronics and forwarded them to the Georgia Bureau of Investigations on March 18, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the GBI returned them in July 2015, Hayes said they found a video of a woman, later identified as Crisp, performing a sexual act on a man while an 18-24-month-old girl was on the bed as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Warrants were issued for Crisp on Wednesday and she was arrested Thursday at 2 p.m., according to court testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said although Crisp initially denied everything, she later admitted that she and her child were in the video and the child was present during the act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I did not know it was on video, and the child wasn’t involved,” Crisp told the court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said the video shows Crisp taking her child’s hand and trying to make her participate in the sexual act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m trying to move her hand and get her not to do that,” Crisp responded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set her bonds at $25,000 apiece for the exploitation and enticing charges and $50,000 for the charge of molestation. He bound the case over to Superior Court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/crisp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/crisp.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man pleads not guilty to child molestation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A man pleaded not guilty to charges of child molestation today in Recorder’s Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police said a child reported Stefon T. Baker touched her crotch over her clothes and showed her pornography on a phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident was originally reported on June 26, according to police. Police said they questioned Baker, who denied the charges at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baker came in Tuesday at 12:35 p.m. to take a polygraph test and speak with police, during which he admitted to child molestation, according to testimony from police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set Baker’s bond at $20,000 and bound the case over to Superior Court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/baker.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/baker.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything You Need to Know About the Launch of iPhone 6S, New Apple TV and iPad Pro</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s that time of year again- Apple has graced us with news of a new iPhone and even a new Apple TV. The company from Cupertino is changing up its lineup of products to adjust to an ever-changing tech market. Here’s what they announced today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;apple-conference-iphone-6s-apple-tv-ipad-pro-launched&quot;&gt;Apple Conference: iPhone 6S, Apple TV, iPad Pro Launched&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apple-tv-is-happening&quot;&gt;Apple TV is happening&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tim Cook is promising a lot with the new Apple TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To deliver on this vision, we need a new foundation for TV, built on powerful hardware, that runs a modern operating system, with a new user experience, great developer tools, and of course an App Store,” Cook said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Apple TV ships with a remote with a touchpad and menu, TV, Siri, pause/play and volume controller buttons. Apple showed people flipping the remote sideways as well to play games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary interface, though, is voice commands through Siri. You can talk to the TV and search content in iTunes, Netflix, Hulu, HBO and Showtime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TV interface looks like Neflix on the desktop. Lots of box art, plenty of images, rectangles everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus is very much on content and apps. It’s all about shows and movies and also your music. Apple TV plays music and other content through Apple’s redesigned stock apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The games look to split the gap between phone games and full-blown console experiences. There isn’t anything you’d see on Xbox or PlayStation, but there are lots of big-screen games that are more complex than your usual iPhone apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shopping apps on the TV&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Live baseball with stats&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;64-bit A8 chip with Bluetooth 4.0, 802.11ac and an IR receiver&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;32 GB model costs $150, 64 GB will run $200.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iphone-6s&quot;&gt;iPhone 6S&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple stuck to the usual tick-tock product cycle with the iPhone 6S and 6S Plus. The two phones don’t change the overall design in a large way, but they do improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new iPhones use Ion-X glass, the strongest in the industry. That glass supports a display capable of something called 3D Touch. It’s Force Touch, but with three different levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the software, 3D Touch acts as a right-click for your thumb. It opens hidden menus and different options. Expect integration with iOS 9 to add stuff like selfies without opening the camera app or calling frequent contacts from the desktop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The phones run on the new A9 chip, a 64-bit SoC that is 70% faster than the A8. Considering the A8 was no slouch, this is impressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cameras are also being upgraded to 12-megapixel iSight shooters. This adds more details and better high-light images. Those of you who hated the camera bump, they have not fixed it this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news you may not want to hear, Apple added “live photos.” Take a photo, then long press it, and it will come to life… much like a video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pricing remains the same, with $200 for 16 GB, $300 for 64 and $400 for 128 for the iPhone 6S. iPhone 6S Plus is priced at the same intervals but starts at $300, all on a two-year contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, Apple is running an upgrade program. For $32 per month, you can participate in the Apple Upgrade Program and get a new unlocked iPhone every year. The plan includes AppleCare+.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Available Sept. 25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ships in silver, gold, space gray and rose gold&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4K video capable&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5-megapixel front-facing FaceTime HD front camera&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Retina Flash that lights up the whole display as a flash for the front-facing camera&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New app on the Play Store to help you move to iOS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Second-generation Touch ID&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;7000 series aluminum, hopefully no more bending&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apple-watch-improves&quot;&gt;Apple Watch improves&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple announced that the Watch will now ship with AirStrip, an in-depth medical examination app. It can test for stuff like heart rate and glucose levels. It even does real-time vital stats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll also be able to enjoy the Apple Watch with three leather bands from Hermes, in case that smartwatch wasn’t fashionable enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WatchOS 2, the brain behind all the new features announced at WWDC 2015 like custom pokes from third-party apps and Facebook Messenger, ships on Sept. 16.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cheaper rose gold and gold finishes now come on the Apple Watch Sport, no change in price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ipad-pro&quot;&gt;iPad Pro&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The biggest news in iPad since iPad” is a gigantic 12.9-inch slab that is the biggest device to ever run iOS. To put it in perspective, the width of the iPad Pro is the length of the iPad Air. It’s slightly thicker, too, at 6.9 mm compared to the Air 2’s 6.1 mm. At 1.57 lbs, it’s heavier than the first iPad, which is saying something. Don’t expect to carry this thing around all day like an iPad Mini.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple’s putting some serious juice behind its new monstrosity with a 64-bit A9X chip. Apple claims you’ll be able to get 10 hours of battery out of this thing, though probably not while running AutoCAD at 60 FPS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While you’re using AutoCAD, you’ll probably want a keyboard to work on. The iPad Pro comes with a smart keyboard attachment that could pass as a Surface Pro at a glance. Apple also copied Microsoft’s tendency to use questionable materials in the keyboard with some kind of fiber keys for the iPad Pro keyboard. Weird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of weird, Steve Jobs may rise again to stop Apple from offering a stylus with the iPad Pro. It’s called the Apple Pencil, a pressure and tilt-sensitive stylus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPad Pro also received support from a company that might surprise you- Microsoft. Redmond is building support for the iPad Pro’s side-by-side apps into Office to make it the best possible experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting this laptop-esque experience will require laptop-esque pricing. The iPad Pro starts at $800 for 32 GB with wifi, $950 for 64 GB with wifi, and $1080 for 128 GB with cellular. The Apple Pencil is $100 and the smart keyboard will run $170. All available this November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;iPad Mini 4 with power of iPad Air 2 at $400&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;iPad Mini 2 at $270&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TypeKit support for Adobe apps for iPad&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3D4Medical medical imaging app for iPad Pro&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4-speaker audio&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;8-megapixel iSight camera, good luck taking pictures with it&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;802.11 ac support&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TouchID&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;everything-else&quot;&gt;Everything Else&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;iOS 9 will be available Sept. 16&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;iCloud pricing has changed- 50 GB is $1/month, 200 is $3/month, and 1 TB is $10/month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts-and-analysis&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts and Analysis&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Apple TV is the biggest new product here, and it’s as unremarkable as was leaked. This is another box that can help us manage our living rooms and stream content to our TVs. The interface looks nicer than a Roku or Chromecast, but the feature differentiation seems minimal. Apple promised more to come on TV, and we expect a lot more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new iPhones seem good. They’re faster, prettier and come with new features, which is nice. 3D Touch seems like a bad direction to go in, though. iOS is great specifically because it’s simple and easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding a right-click function is exactly the kind of thing that confuses people. I don’t see how this adds to the experience (take that with a grain of salt, though, as we haven’t seen iOS 9 yet).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, new iPhone, with a better camera, and some interesting features. It’ll sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPad Pro is more mysterious. Apple talked about the consumer use cases on stage, but… who wants a 12.9-inch tablet? Is this something people will really buy? Or is it an enterprise tablet made to sell to businesses for them to stuff in kiosks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, here’s to the next few months and finding out how well this stuff works.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/appleConference.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/appleConference.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whose identical PSA was better, Gus Malzahn or Nick Saban?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Gus Malzahn and Nick Saban are going head to head in an unexpected contest: the public service announcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two head coaches recorded 30-second videos supporting a statewide voter identification drive run by John Merrill, Alabama’s secretary of state. They used the same script in both videos, changing only the names of each man’s wife and team battle cry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To be an impact player in football as well as in life, you have to be prepared to make a difference,” said Saban and Malzahn. “One of the most significant ways to make a positive impact on your community, state or nation is by participating in the electoral process.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our question for readers is, whose video was better? Gus seemed to stumble out of the block with reading the script. Saban had some issues with the way the camera framed only half of his hand motions and made them look odd. Who do you think won?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you don’t watch the videos, they’ll be played on the jumbotrons at Jordan-Hare and Bryant-Denny Stadium, according to a release. You can even get a poster of this from your local Board of Registrar’s office. It’s the perfect way to combine two of most commonly associated passions: football and voter registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;its-all-to-get-you-to-vote&quot;&gt;It’s all to get you to vote&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this is a way to help voters navigate Alabama’s somewhat confusing &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/&quot;&gt;voter registration laws&lt;/a&gt;. After the passage of HB-19 in 2011, Alabama voters need a valid form of photo identification to take part at the polls. Acceptable IDs include a driver’s license, passport or state, federal, government employee, military, tribal or student ID.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have any of those, you can pick up a free photo voter ID card from the courthouse, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/permanentLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;Board of Registrar’s office&lt;/a&gt; or one of these voter ID drives the secretary of state’s office is holding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clay Helms, supervisor of voter registration for the secretary of state’s office, said his office is working on holding a voter ID drive in all of Alabama’s 67 counties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helms said the Russell County drive already happened on July 1 at the Phenix City Activity Center and Hurtsboro City Hall. There are no plans at the moment to revisit Russell County, according to Helms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/mobileLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; of planned voter ID drive locations lists two visits to Lee County on Oct. 14 and Nov. 4. Both will be from 10 a.m. to 12 p.m. at Smiths Station City Hall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember also that in order to pick up your voter ID card, you need to already be registered to vote. You can do that by calling 1-800-274-8683 or visiting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.alabamavotes.gov/GetRegForm.aspx?m=voters&quot;&gt;Alabama’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to recap: Register to vote first, then go to the courthouse or one of the Lee County drives to get a free voter ID, but only if you don’t already have one of the other valid IDs listed above, and don’t forget to bring everything to the polls in November 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police- LaGrange man faces murder charge after infant dies in his care</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A LaGrange, Ga., man is facing a murder charge after police said a 4-month-old died in his care, according to a release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brandon Heard, 30, was arrested Thursday afternoon and charged with murder and first-degree cruelty to children. He is held in the Troup County Jail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaGrange police were called to the 1500 block of Hogansville Road Tuesday around 2:55 p.m. in reference to a child not breathing. Upon arrival, police found 4-month-old Skylar King unresponsive. The infant was taken to the West Georgia Medical Center where he was pronounced dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Georgia Bureau of Investigation conducted an autopsy Wednesday and found Skylar died from blunt-force trauma to the head, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said the injury was inflicted Tuesday by Heard, the boyfriend of Skylar’s mom. Heard was taking care of the child while the mother was at work, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case remains under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Things To Know About the Command Line Before You Start Using Linux</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you get started on Linux (like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/39938/a-mac-users-experience-of-using-linux-ubuntu&quot;&gt;I, a Mac user, did after getting curious&lt;/a&gt;), getting used to the platforms quirks can be challenging. Linux doesn’t work like other platforms. It requires rethinking how a computer “should” work and understanding a whole different paradigm with its own strengths and weaknesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest changes is the command line. Windows has Command Prompt (which any good sysadmin will spend a good bit of time in) and Mac has Terminal, but both prefer to keep command line stuff as a last resort. Mac and Windows (and some Linux brands, such as Ubuntu) would first present a GUI for managing programs and updating your OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Linux, however, runs mostly on the command line. Doing all the cool (and useful) things in the operating system requires understanding how some funny-sounding commands can operate your system. However, the command line can be intimidating. To help you understand it and work in it better, here are some things you should know before starting on Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;things-about-the-command-line-to-know-before-using-linux&quot;&gt;Things About the Command Line to Know Before Using Linux&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-a-command-line&quot;&gt;What is a command line?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.ubuntu.com/community/UsingTheTerminal&quot;&gt;humorously documented in the Ubuntu beginner’s guide&lt;/a&gt;, terminal commands can look bizarre and intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;sudo gobbledegook blah_blah -w -t -h –long-switch aWkward/ComBinationOf/mixedCase/underscores_strokes/and.dots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At its core, a command line is a way to input orders into a computer with special bits of text the computer knows. It’s confusing because you have to remember what command does what. However, once you learn the commands, it can be very fast and powerful (especially since Linux will let you change almost everything).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you input commands in a terminal window, a program called a shell takes those and translates them into computer code. There are several different shells, but for our purposes we’ll focus on the most popular, bash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;command-line-grammar&quot;&gt;Command-line grammar&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you break it down, you can understand some of the weirdness in command lines. There’s a kind of rough grammar to it (with plenty of exceptions).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many commands will start with the word “sudo.” What that means is instead of executing the command with regular privileges, you want to do it as a superuser (hence “su”). This gives you access to system files and all the important stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next is a program name. This tells the system what to invoke. For example, a command that reads:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;sudo apt-get update&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tells the shell to execute the apt program as a superuser. The -get part is an additional flag that tells apt what to do. “Update” is the other part of telling apt what to do (update its source list).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might see a lot of these kinds of modifiers. Generally letters after dashes are modifying flags on a base command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you see something like /var/etc/test.txt, that’s a reference to a file. All files stored on a Linux computer’s hard drive can be found with some kind of file reference, just like on Mac and Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes files are used as modifiers to commands. For example, you might tell the command line to copy a file to the desktop like so:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;cp test.txt ~/Desktop/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notice something: in this case, we referred to test.txt without a long preceding string to reference its absolute path. Each terminal window runs at a certain location on your computer, referenced by the bit before the dollar sign but after the colon. For example, this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;kylenazario@ubuntu:~$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is me at my home directory. If I type:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;cd ~/Downloads&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;pushd Downloads&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It changes the Terminal window’s location to my downloads folder. You can always check what’s within your current folder by simply typing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ls&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, why does it matter where the terminal process is running? Because it means you can cheat a little. Instead of referring to a file’s absolute, complete path and name (e.g. ~/Desktop/cmdline.txt), you can just call it by the name (cmdline.txt). Definitely makes things easier to type.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-the-command-line-good-for&quot;&gt;What is the command line good for?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The previous section was all about using the command line for file management, but I would not recommend it unless you’re doing batch renaming or something you need to automate. Honestly, basic file management is awkward on the command line. It’s much easier to drag and drop a file onto your desktop than it is to type out the full cp command (in my opinion).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, say you wanted to automatically copy that file into your Dropbox folder at 11pm every night to save your work. In that case, a script of commands would be perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The command line is also great for installing and managing software utilities. It’s better to just type in sudo apt-get install whatever when you’re downloading the ten dependencies needed for Ruby than it is to go to Ruby’s website and download every zip you need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the command line rewards expertise. While it’ll be hard at first, it’ll reward you with some really awesome time-saving shortcuts once you get the hang of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;always-useful-basic-commands&quot;&gt;Always useful basic commands&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;cd [directory]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to [directory]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;sudo apt-get update&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refresh the list of available software&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;sudo apt-get upgrade&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download updates for your installed software&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&amp;amp;&amp;amp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put between commands to make the computer execute the first, then the second. For example, you might enter sudo apt-get update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt-get upgrade to download all new software without having to type in commands twice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;rm -r [directory or file]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delete file or everything in that directory. Use with caution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;pwd&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Print working directory. Tells you where you are so you can cd somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;man [program]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Show the manual of a certain program. Useful for checking how to use a command-line program without Google.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;sudo [command]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do as superuser. Use with caution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[Up Arrow]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Autofills last command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[Tab]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Autocompletes filenames or commands. Saves typing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested, there’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.ubuntu.com/community/UsingTheTerminal&quot;&gt;good list of guides&lt;/a&gt; on Ubuntu’s website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/25/commandLineStarter.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/08/25/commandLineStarter.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
