<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 13:21:29 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 13:21:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Phenix City police find this robbery suspect</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police are looking for the man pictured above. He is suspected of robbing Walmart Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suspect attempted to exit Walmart without paying for merchandise, according to police. Police said when the man was confronted by loss prevention, he began fighting with them, pulled out a knife and threatened employees. He then fled in a white SUV, according to the PC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=890958827606389&amp;amp;id=224351267600485&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police describe the suspect as 6-foot, 160-pound white man with dark hair, a goatee and tattoos on both arms. Anyone with information on the incident should call the Phenix City police at one of the numbers below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Staudinger - (334) 448 - 2837&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lt. Whitten - (334) 448 - 2825&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capt. Ivey - (334) 448 - 2836&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/15/walmartRobber.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Miss Alabama on Donald Trump- Republicans should be &#39;absolutely terrified&#39;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Meg McGuffin, a former Miss Phenix City and Auburn student, had some harsh words for Donald Trump at last night’s Miss America contest. When asked why Trump has an impressive lead over the rest of the Republican Party, McGuffin didn’t hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think Donald Trump is an entertainer,” McGuffin said. “I think he says what’s on a lot of people’s minds but I think that the Republican Party should be absolutely terrified of all the attention he’s taking from credible candidates like Jeb Bush and Chris Christie who can absolutely do the job of president of the United States. And, if I were a Republican, I would absolutely be terrified of that. Thank you so much.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McGuffin was supported by a group from the Miss Phenix City program who made the trip to New Jersey. McGuffin, a former winner from Ozark, Ala., said she aims to pursue a Ph.D. in education leadership funded by her winnings from pageants, which total more than $80,000 after she finished in fourth place at last night’s Miss America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will hopefully attain my Ph.D. and be student-debt free,” McGuffin said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Meg McGuffin posted this on Facebook:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. Last night, I was named the 95th 4th Runner-Up to Miss America. Had I placed 52nd or 1st, I am proud of the way I...&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL&quot;&gt;Miss Alabama Meg McGuffin&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/MissAmericaAL/posts/520102951499030:0&quot;&gt;Monday, September 14, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29458081.html&quot;&gt;profile on Meg McGuffin&lt;/a&gt;, as well as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/entertainment/article29461165.html&quot;&gt;Miss America (and Miss Georgia) Betty Cantrell&lt;/a&gt;. If you missed the show, there’s also a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/entertainment/article35149809.html&quot;&gt;recap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dmusMt2A8BA&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[h/t &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?t=1&amp;amp;v=dmusMt2A8BA&quot;&gt;Yellowhammer&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/missAmerica.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/missAmerica.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man charged with murder in fatal shooting of Columbus woman</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Phenix City Police have charged 18-year-old Demetrius Devonta Dorsey with the murder of Mariah Farrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dorsey was taken into custody without incident around 11:15 a.m. today. Members of Phenix City Police Departments Criminal Investigation Division and the U.S. Marshals Gulf Coast Regional Task Force executed a search and arrest warrant at 2601 14th Court in that resulted in Dorsey’s arrest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike Haskey mhaskey@ledger-enquirer.comNeighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th Street and 10th Court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said. 09/14/15 Demetrius Devonta Dorsey Mike Haskey mhaskey@ledger-enquirer.comNeighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th Street and 10th Court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is currently incarcerated in Russell County Jail, authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City Police would like anyone who may have firsthand information pertinent to the investigation to contact Phenix City Police Criminal Investigations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Story&lt;/strong&gt;: A 19-year-old Columbus woman suffering from a gunshot wound died this morning at Midtown Medical Center, according to a post by Phenix City Police on their Facebook page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police said they received reports of shots fired in the 1000 block of 16th Street around 11:50 p.m. Sunday but did not find anyone when they arrived. They said they were notified by Columbus police “a short time later” that a woman had been driven to Midtown Medical Center while suffering from multiple gunshot wounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hospital personnel were unable to revive 19-year-old Mariah Farrow, a 2015 graduate of Carver High School and current Columbus State University student. She was pronounced at 12:18 a.m., Russell County Coroner Arthur Sumbry Jr. said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her body will be transported to the Department of Forensic Sciences in Montgomery for an autopsy, according to the coroner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police said they are investigating the case and are “currently interviewing a number of witnesses.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neighbors told the Ledger-Enquirer they heard loud arguing near the intersection of 16th street and 10th court around 11 to 11:30 p.m. It was near midnight when they heard two gunshots before the sounds of some vehicles “peeling out,” they said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 2:45 p.m. Monday, CSU sent out an email to their students, faculty and staff informing them about Farrow’s death, according to CSU Communications Specialist Christa Robbins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unofficial statement reads as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSU students, faculty and staff,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;It is with great sadness that we report the death of a Columbus State University freshman, Mariah Farrow, 19, an undeclared first-term, first-year student from Columbus. She was apparently involved in an off-campus shooting last evening.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please keep the family in your thoughts and prayers.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone with additional information on the case should contact the Phenix City Police Department Criminal Investigations Division. The police dispatch number is 334-298-0611.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Staff writer Sarah Robinson contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/csuShooting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/14/csuShooting.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police- Man caught after fleeing on sight from police</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus Police testified in Recorder’s Court Friday that Jasper D. Dunlap, 22, was arrested after a foot chase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An officer said when he approached a group outside Wilson Apartments at 3400 8th Ave. on possible loitering charges, Dunlap took off running. Police said they caught him after a foot chase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time the chase ended, the other members of the group had already disappeared, according to the officer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dunlap, who police said gave a false name, was identified at Muscogee County Jail as being someone on probation and who had an outstanding warrant for theft by taking a motor vehicle, according to testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He pleaded not guilty to charges of loitering, obstructing a law enforcement officer, theft by taking a motor vehicle, violation of probation and giving false information to an officer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set his bond at $1,000 for obstruction, $500 for false information and a 30-day suspended sentence. He then bound the case over to state court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/dunlap.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/dunlap.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Woman denies involving 2-year-old in sex</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Shannon Crisp, 23, pleaded not guilty Friday morning in Recorder’s Court to charges of child molestation. She also pleaded guilty to sexual exploitation of children and enticing a child for an indecent purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crisp was arrested after the Sex Crimes division investigated a case of child molestation involving an adult male and female juvenile, according to testimony from Cpl. Brittney Hayes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said police seized a computer and other electronics and forwarded them to the Georgia Bureau of Investigations on March 18, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the GBI returned them in July 2015, Hayes said they found a video of a woman, later identified as Crisp, performing a sexual act on a man while an 18-24-month-old girl was on the bed as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Warrants were issued for Crisp on Wednesday and she was arrested Thursday at 2 p.m., according to court testimony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said although Crisp initially denied everything, she later admitted that she and her child were in the video and the child was present during the act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I did not know it was on video, and the child wasn’t involved,” Crisp told the court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hayes said the video shows Crisp taking her child’s hand and trying to make her participate in the sexual act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m trying to move her hand and get her not to do that,” Crisp responded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set her bonds at $25,000 apiece for the exploitation and enticing charges and $50,000 for the charge of molestation. He bound the case over to Superior Court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/crisp.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/11/crisp.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man pleads not guilty to child molestation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A man pleaded not guilty to charges of child molestation today in Recorder’s Court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police said a child reported Stefon T. Baker touched her crotch over her clothes and showed her pornography on a phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The incident was originally reported on June 26, according to police. Police said they questioned Baker, who denied the charges at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baker came in Tuesday at 12:35 p.m. to take a polygraph test and speak with police, during which he admitted to child molestation, according to testimony from police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Judge Michael Cielinski set Baker’s bond at $20,000 and bound the case over to Superior Court.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/baker.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/09/09/baker.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whose identical PSA was better, Gus Malzahn or Nick Saban?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Gus Malzahn and Nick Saban are going head to head in an unexpected contest: the public service announcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two head coaches recorded 30-second videos supporting a statewide voter identification drive run by John Merrill, Alabama’s secretary of state. They used the same script in both videos, changing only the names of each man’s wife and team battle cry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To be an impact player in football as well as in life, you have to be prepared to make a difference,” said Saban and Malzahn. “One of the most significant ways to make a positive impact on your community, state or nation is by participating in the electoral process.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our question for readers is, whose video was better? Gus seemed to stumble out of the block with reading the script. Saban had some issues with the way the camera framed only half of his hand motions and made them look odd. Who do you think won?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you don’t watch the videos, they’ll be played on the jumbotrons at Jordan-Hare and Bryant-Denny Stadium, according to a release. You can even get a poster of this from your local Board of Registrar’s office. It’s the perfect way to combine two of most commonly associated passions: football and voter registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;its-all-to-get-you-to-vote&quot;&gt;It’s all to get you to vote&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this is a way to help voters navigate Alabama’s somewhat confusing &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/&quot;&gt;voter registration laws&lt;/a&gt;. After the passage of HB-19 in 2011, Alabama voters need a valid form of photo identification to take part at the polls. Acceptable IDs include a driver’s license, passport or state, federal, government employee, military, tribal or student ID.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have any of those, you can pick up a free photo voter ID card from the courthouse, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/permanentLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;Board of Registrar’s office&lt;/a&gt; or one of these voter ID drives the secretary of state’s office is holding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clay Helms, supervisor of voter registration for the secretary of state’s office, said his office is working on holding a voter ID drive in all of Alabama’s 67 counties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Helms said the Russell County drive already happened on July 1 at the Phenix City Activity Center and Hurtsboro City Hall. There are no plans at the moment to revisit Russell County, according to Helms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://alabamavoterid.com/mobileLocations.aspx&quot;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; of planned voter ID drive locations lists two visits to Lee County on Oct. 14 and Nov. 4. Both will be from 10 a.m. to 12 p.m. at Smiths Station City Hall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember also that in order to pick up your voter ID card, you need to already be registered to vote. You can do that by calling 1-800-274-8683 or visiting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.alabamavotes.gov/GetRegForm.aspx?m=voters&quot;&gt;Alabama’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to recap: Register to vote first, then go to the courthouse or one of the Lee County drives to get a free voter ID, but only if you don’t already have one of the other valid IDs listed above, and don’t forget to bring everything to the polls in November 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/31/coachPSA.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police- LaGrange man faces murder charge after infant dies in his care</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A LaGrange, Ga., man is facing a murder charge after police said a 4-month-old died in his care, according to a release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brandon Heard, 30, was arrested Thursday afternoon and charged with murder and first-degree cruelty to children. He is held in the Troup County Jail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LaGrange police were called to the 1500 block of Hogansville Road Tuesday around 2:55 p.m. in reference to a child not breathing. Upon arrival, police found 4-month-old Skylar King unresponsive. The infant was taken to the West Georgia Medical Center where he was pronounced dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Georgia Bureau of Investigation conducted an autopsy Wednesday and found Skylar died from blunt-force trauma to the head, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said the injury was inflicted Tuesday by Heard, the boyfriend of Skylar’s mom. Heard was taking care of the child while the mother was at work, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case remains under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/28/infantDeath.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Update- Man shot earlier this week on 28th Avenue dies in hospital</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The man police say was shot early Thursday morning on 28th Avenue died Saturday at Midtown Medical Center, according to Muscogee County Coroner Buddy Bryan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simon Lee King Jr., 57, was pronounced dead at 2:20 p.m., Bryan said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witnesses told police King was walking down the street when a vehicle with two black men stopped next to him. After calling King over to the vehicle, they shot him, witnesses told police. The vehicle, which police believe was a silver or gold four-door sedan, was last seen fleeing the scene near Clover Lane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King was said to have suffered from multiple gunshot wounds to the torso and arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to incident reports, the police were called to the 300 block of 28th Avenue around 12:46 a.m. Thursday. They found King lying in a driveway, according to an incident report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witnesses told authorities the suspects appeared to be between 19 and 24 years old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police believe one suspect has a slender build, low haircut and a medium-to-dark complexion. A description of the second individual wasn’t available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Columbus Police Department is asking for anyone with any knowledge about the homicide to contact Sgt. Ken Hudson at 706-225-4257 or the Robbery/Assault Unit at 706-653-3400.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;King’s death comes three weeks after 56-year-old William Edwards was found dead in his tent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edwards, who was homeless, lived in an area called tent city near the Second Avenue bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Crime reporter Sarah Robinson contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/shootingDeath.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/shootingDeath.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12th Avenue home catches fire</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus fire and emergency services put out a house fire early Saturday morning near the corner of 12th Avenue and 32nd Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A home at 1206 12th Ave. caught fire sometime after 7 a.m., according to Capt. Mary Simonton. She couldn’t estimate the time of the call to emergency services, but said fire engine 2 was there within three minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blaze had subsided and firefighters were spraying down the house by approximately 8:30 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simonton said there were no major injuries, though a firefighter injured his ankle on the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sabine James, a neighbor who’s been friends with the house’s residents for 25 years, said she was just thankful no one was hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Everybody got out alive,” James said. “The rest can be replaced.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Lance Christenson said the fire spread into the front living room and attic before it was put out, causing an estimated $40,000 worth of damage. The fire department is treating the case as an accident and does not plan to investigate further, Christenson said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon Dunbar, who lives in the home, said her house had burned down before on Christmas Day in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now, Dunbar said she plans to stay with family until she figures out what to do next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have no clue [what’s next],” Dunbar said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/12fire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kylenazario.com/2015/08/15/12fire.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
