<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 14:07:55 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 14:07:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Complete guide to Ponce City Market&amp;#58; Food, shopping and history</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Atlantans who wander down to what used to be City Hall East can experience a wide array of restaurants and shopping. The food is made by some of the most famous chefs in Atlanta at places including H&amp;amp;F Burger and the Mercury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This century-old warehouse has also been renovated into the Flats at Ponce City Market, some of the most expensive apartments in the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check the Ponce City Market hours before you go, they vary by business. See the directory for a listing for each store and restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also a page with help getting there, whether you’re paying for parking or taking MARTA. The market also connects to the Atlanta Beltline via a small bridge that opened last fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you need to know before seeing the old Sears warehouse:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything you need to know about Ponce City market. Consider this our go-to guide for learning what this place is and why it’s exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check what restaurants and food stalls are open. The phrase “authentic Indian streetfood” is in that article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the area’s transition from Sears to Ponce City market over 80 years. A must-see gallery for local history buffs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget the amusement park. This rooftop attraction is a throwback to the historical site’s former claim to fame as the “Coney Island of the South.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a tour of the market with this gallery. The only thing easier than shopping is looking at pictures of stores where you could shop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn about the building’s history with this fascinating look back. Ponce City Market has come full circle, from Sears to to ruin to a massive $300 million project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where to go at Ponce City Market. You have problems, we have a guide for stores that will sell you a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explore Ponce City Market with an interactive map. Don’t go in blind. See the lay of the land before visiting to find your destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some Ponce City Market restaurants let you dine with your dog. Because some restaurant owners love dogs as much as you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the restaurant with a famously great patio. Cocktails on the patio is the perfect way to spend a summer evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some couples that run the restaurants have adorable stories. 21 years of marriage and three restaurants is impressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The famer’s market and Beltline shed just launched. Come on a Tuesday for products from local farmers and artisans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be warned– not everyone likes the paid parking. Some tenants and customers think it hurts business and some owners say it hasn’t hurt their bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not just retail. Tech companies seem to like the office space and location. 
Ponce Food:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mercury oozes retro cool. Flash back in time with classic decor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;W.H. Stiles Fish Camp puts seafood in the spotlight. Quirky service and barbecue shrimp make this an interesting pick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brezza Cucina and the titanic chef teamup. A little bit Southern, a little bit Italian, and completely delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eat your vegetables at farm to ladle. A constant rotation of good food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Casual meets Mexican at Minero. No reservations, Mexican-inspired cocktails and low- and highbrow beer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet your meat fix at H&amp;amp; F Burger Bar and Hop’s Chicken. Chicken and burgers in various guises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Try the fresh daily punch at King of Pops Bar &amp;amp; Good Grub. There is also local beer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be confused by City Winery. Is it a winery? A concert venue? A restaurant? Find out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrate El Super Pan with other sandwich fans. “The guy is pretty much throwing us a house party every day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taste the flavors of Morocco at Marrakesh Mediterranean. They’re aiming for “simple, healthy food made with love.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out Botiwalla’s new take on Indian street food. A creative version of charcoal-grilled Indian street food and Parsi cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the menu for Biltong Bar. All kinds of South African-style jerky, savory hand pies, cheese and charcuterie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quick-facts&quot;&gt;Quick Facts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Built in 1926 as a warehouse for Sears, Roebuck &amp;amp; Co.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shut down by Sears by 1989.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Purchased by the city of Atlanta in 1990 as City hall East in what then-Mayor Maynard Jackson called the “deal of the century.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sold to Jamestown in 2010, which spent $300 million renovating it for its 2014 opening&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Covers 2.1 million square feet, about half of which is for parking, circulation and other uses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A studio apartment in the Flats at Ponce City market with 560 square feet of space and one bathroom costs $1,675 per month, according to their website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/10/ponce-city-market-guide-history.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/10/ponce-city-market-guide-history.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>food,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sixth new business expansion in two months to open in Stone Mountain Village</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stone Mountain has seen five ribbon cuttings for “new or expanded businesses” since the start of March, according to a press release from the City of Stone Mountain Downtown Development Authority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sixth business, Flex Point Studio, will have its ribbon cutting during a ceremony on Wednesday, March 11, at 11 a.m. at 913 Main Street, Suite B. It will also have an opening party this Saturday with a DJ, food, free raffle and demo class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the release, the expansions and openings have created approximately eight new jobs. This rate of openings compares with its 2015 equivalent time period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The newest business, Flex Point Studio, will offer fitness classes featuring yoga, Zumba, tap, hip-hop dance, contemporary dance, African dance, modern dance and ballet. According to the release, the studio also plans to include a “Mommy and Me” class on Sundays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flex Point owner Jennifer Cornelius said she was tired of driving into Atlanta for the fitness classes she enjoyed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So I put together my dance background, my legal expertise and public relations skills and have created Flex Point Sudio,” Cornelius says. “I hope it will fill the gap in fitness that people are looking for.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other new businesses and expansions include Better Body Image, Cool Breeze Smoothie, Stone Mountain Manor, Twisted Swisher and Vim Rise (website under construction, call 770-217-9882).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jean Milice, co-owner of Vim Rise, said he and his wife Frida Milice started their tax and insurance business in Stone Mountain because it was “suitable” and his wife had lots of clients in the area. He said the city was “very helpful in every step of the way” while they were getting started, and he’d recomend the area to another small business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I wouldn’t want them to open another tax prep business on the same street, but there’s plenty of vacancies in the area,” Milice said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mechel McKinley, executive director of the city’s Downtown Development Authority, said Stone Mountain is still bringing in more businesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’re not done yet,” McKinley says. “Another business will be finished with an expansion soon and there are three more ribbon cuttings in the planning stages.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/10/flexpoint-opening-stone-mountain-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/10/flexpoint-opening-stone-mountain-business.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>stonemtn,</category>
        
        <category>dekalb,</category>
        
        <category>hyperlocal,</category>
        
        <category>business,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tell Decatur what art you want at the W. Trinity overpass</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The city of Decatur announced in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedecaturminute.com/2016/05/06/marta-mural-project-community-input-meeting/&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; Friday that it wants input from residents about what they want to see in a mural. The transportation organization  is working on a large piece of public art which will be displayed on the overpass at the corner of W. Trinity Place and Atlanta Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The meeting is Wednesday, May 11, from 6 p.m. to 8 p.m. at the Ebster Recreation Center at 105 Electric Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joey Fillastre and Felici Asteinza of MILAGROS Collective, the artists, will be there to discuss their work and philosophy. “The artists have come up with some fun, creative ways to engage our collective imagination(s) as we reflect and envision what will ultimately become our community mural based on the Making History in Our Region theme,” the announcement reads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To RSVP or ask questions, call 404 - 371 - 9583. Those who cannot make this meeting can also attend an additional community input meeting in August.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city said it expects the mural to be complete by October. There is &lt;a href=&quot;http://commuting.blog.ajc.com/2016/03/21/marta-stations-to-feature-mural-artwork/&quot;&gt;an initiative&lt;/a&gt; to create murals representative of their communities around Atlanta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.myajc.com/news/entertainment/arts-theater/marta-art/nrDPB/&quot;&gt;Inside MARTA’s double life as an art gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/09/decatur-mural-overpass-meeting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/09/decatur-mural-overpass-meeting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>decatur,</category>
        
        <category>dekalb,</category>
        
        <category>hyperlocal,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 10 industries where people change jobs the most</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;According to public data, people don’t work the same food service job for very long. The Bureau of Labor Statistics tracks how long people spend at a given job in several industries. They found that among certain fields, employees tended to have been at their current job for less time than in others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, people working in laundry and arts and entertainment had some of the shortest time on a single job of most industries. Such job hopping bear a toll on the companies in these industries. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ajc.com/news/business/the-cost-of-millennials-job-hopping/nZKJC/&quot;&gt;One survey&lt;/a&gt; found 87 percent of companies said it cost $15,000 to $25,000 to replace a departed employee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;» RELATED: These are the top 10 job picks for high school seniors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Workers in these industries may change positions because of a &lt;a href=&quot;http://smallbusiness.chron.com/employee-turnover-statistics-restaurants-16744.html&quot;&gt;lack of advancement&lt;/a&gt; and poor working conditions. They’re not alone, either. These days the average American has &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ajc.com/news/news/national/average-american-has-jobs-28/nq4MM/&quot;&gt;7.2 jobs by 28&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://infogr.am/7c30921c-fdcb-4bf9-afd8-8da96cfa1f5b&quot;&gt;View a graph of the 10 industries with the shortest time in one job&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, these numbers vary by age as well. Older workers, unsurprisingly, are more likely to have been in their current job for longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bls.gov/news.release/tenure.htm&quot;&gt;Click here to read the full report.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/04/jobs-people-change-most.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/04/jobs-people-change-most.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jobs,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 Georgia baby names that mean business (and 10 that don&#39;t)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Contemporary baby names have gone from celebrity cardinal directions like North West to social media labels like Hashtag. Yes, #really. It seems people think odder names are more creatively cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if you want your little Georgia-based bundle of joy to break into enterprising fields in the future, you may want to avoid giving him or her any names that are too “creative.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Academic studies such as Marquette University’s “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.emeraldinsight.com/doi/abs/10.1108/02683940810849648&quot;&gt;The ‘name game’: affective and hiring reactions to first names&lt;/a&gt;” claim staying common counts to nailing professional posts. From the study:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Results indicated that Common names were seen as least unique, best liked, and most likely to be hired. Unusual names were seen as most unique, least liked, and least likely to be hired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Names like Elizabeth, Edward and Michael may not stand out, but they’ll help your kid get hired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Social Security Administration, these are some of the most common baby names given to children born in 2014 in Georgia:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;William: From Germanic Willahelm, meaning “will” and “helm” (helmet). Subtle way to make sure your son wears a helmet on his bike?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mason: English, meaning stoneworker.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Noah: Derived from a Hebrew word meaning “rest.” Great for ensuring your child becomes a shipwright.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;James: Descended from the Hebrew word Ya’aqov, the name of two apostles in the New Testament.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Jacob: Another descendent of the same Hebrew word for James.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RELATED: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ajc.com/news/news/local/most-popular-baby-name-georgia-ever/npznD/&quot;&gt;Georgia’s most popular baby name ever is …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For girls:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Olivia: First used in this spelling by Shakespeare in “Twelfth Night” for a noblewoman character. As the most common female name of 2014, it may help your daughter in the job market but it will probably not make her a noble as well.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ava: A variant of Eve. Also used for suspicious AI creations.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Emma: A Germanic mainstay of Jane Austen novels.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Madison: Rarely used as a woman’s name until after the 1984 film “Splash,” in which the female protagonist takes it as her name off of the sign for Madison Avenue in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Isabella: Common among medieval royalty. As the number-five most common girls’ name in Georgia, though, it seems the people have taken it back.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SSA list also categorizes some less common names at the bottom of the list. These aren’t the least common names in all of Georgia — that list would be names that literally only one person has, making them difficult to track — but they are slightly less common names that may not give your kid as big a “commonality boost” in the workplace as those in the top 10. The bottom five, for boys:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Xavier: Gets to share a name with an X-man!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Jase: Related to Jason and Jay.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Julian: Roman, common among the early saints.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Sawyer: Think Mark Twain, or Lost. Means “sawer of wood.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Brody: From an Irish surname descended from a Gaelic word for “ditch.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Cayden: Variant of Caden, an Irish surname.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Girls:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ryleigh: Different spelling of Riley, which comes from the Irish name Reilly and an English name meaning “rye clearing” in English. Good for a career in… clearing rye?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Eleanor: Popular among queens and First Ladies. Not the most popular name for Georgia babies but recommended if your baby seems interested in charity work.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Paris: Also works for boys, though the Paris of Greek mythology isn’t exactly hero material.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Melanie: An old French name that was revived by “Gone With the Wind.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Harmony: Will do nothing to stop fighting among siblings, sadly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Brianna: A variant of Briana, which is the feminine form of Brian.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/04/common-baby-names-georgia.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/04/common-baby-names-georgia.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>parenting,</category>
        
        <category>sap,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Braves fans can say farewell to Turner Field at the Braves Country 5K</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Braves fans and runners can &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.atlantatrackclub.org/2016-braves-country-5k?utm_source=Facebook&amp;amp;utm_medium=event&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Braves&quot;&gt;sign up for&lt;/a&gt; the team’s final season at Turner Field with a 5K, 1-mile run and 50-meter dash. According to the event description on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/572852369552529/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, “5K and One Mile participants will run or walk around the stadium before crossing the finish line at center field.” This is just one of several races that the Atlanta Track Club organizes in addition to the annual &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ajc.com/s/peachtree/#running-news&quot;&gt;AJC Peachtree Road Race&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Runners in the 5K race will receive tickets to one Braves home game with the option of buying another at a discount. The games available for this promotion include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;June 11 vs. Chicago Cubs, including a postgame showing of “Ferris Bueller’s Day Off” on the big screen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;June 12 vs. Chicago Cubs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;June 25 vs. New York Mets, including a postgame concert from Flo Rida&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.accessatlanta.com/news/events/8-races-run-may-around-atlanta/nrFZW/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;[8 can’t-miss races to run in May around Atlanta]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants who attend the June 11 game against the Cubs may also join the pregame parade around the warning track. Lineup for the parade is at 2:30 p.m. at the Hank Aaron Ramp across from aisle 129.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-registration ends on June 8 at 11:59 p.m. The deadline to register on race day is be timed is 7 a.m. Unofficial race times will be posted online the afternoon of the event, with the official numbers to come two weeks later. The event is rain or shine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Braves announced a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ajc.com/news/sports/baseball/braves-plan-to-build-new-stadium-in-cobb/nbpNQ/&quot;&gt;new park&lt;/a&gt;, SunTrust Stadium, in 2013. The new stadium will become the home of the Braves after the 2016 season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;braves-country-5k&quot;&gt;Braves Country 5K&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Saturday, June 11, 7:30 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Turner Field (755 Hank Aaron Drive SE, Atlanta, GA, 30315)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distance&lt;/strong&gt;: 5K for ages 8 and older, 1 mile for 7 and older, 50m dash for 6 and older&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5K Upper box ticket package: $39, $17 per additional upper box ticket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5K Outfield ticket package: $49, $27 per additional outfield ticket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 mile race: $15 ($20 on race day)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;50-meter dash: $10 ($15 on race day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swag&lt;/strong&gt;: Short-sleeve Mizuno shirt, ticket to a Braves game, free parking, Chick-fil-A chicken sandwich&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/03/braves-country-5k-turner-field.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/05/03/braves-country-5k-turner-field.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>todo,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>running,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>See the Georgia tree that owns itself</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s no better way to mark Arbor Day than by visiting one of Georgia’s finest trees, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tree_That_Owns_Itself&quot;&gt;The Tree That Owns Itself&lt;/a&gt;. Tourists have come for more than 100 years to see a white oak with the unusual distinction of owning itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tree lives in a shaded neighborhood at the corner of South Finley and Dearing Streets in Athens. The tree is inside a small fenced-in circle of land that juts into the middle of the street, cutting off one lane of traffic along South Finley. There are two engraved stones dedicated to the tree, one of which is more faded than the other. According to Billy Paugh, community forestry coordinator for Athens-Clarke County, The Tree That Owns Itself stands 70 feet tall and is 35 inches wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the legend goes, Col. William Henry Jackson, reportedly a professor at UGA, had fond childhood memories of the tree and wanted to protect it. According to a newspaper story from 1890, Jackson wrote a will that read:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I, W. H. Jackson, of the county of Clarke… do convey unto the said oak tree entire possession of itself and of all land within eight feet of it on all sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite its vague origin, the tree’s status is accepted in Athens. As one writer put it, “However defective this title may be in law, the public recognized it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roger Cauthen, Athens-Clarke County’s landscape management administrator, told the Atlanta Journal-Constitution the city considers the tree part of the right of way on South Finley Street and takes care of it, despite the folklore of its self-ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite a story, but we treat it as kind of a public street tree,” Cauthen said. “If there was outside damage, like from a storm, we would prune the damage. It has little to no signs of damage or stress.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weather has proved troublesome for Athens’ most famous tree in the past. The tree that stands today is actually The Son of The Tree That Owns Itself. The original suffered from erosion and an ice storm in 1907. It fell by 1942 because of infected roots. Estimates from the time say it was 150-400 years old and more than 100 feet tall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new tree was &lt;a href=&quot;http://onlineathens.com/stories/121399/new_1213990025.shtml&quot;&gt;planted in 1946&lt;/a&gt; in the same spot using acorns from the original. It is generally known by the same name as its father and accorded the same self-ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time, Mrs. Dudley of the Junior Ladies Garden Club told the Athens Banner-Herald, “(The Club) believes that Athens needs another Tree That Owns Itself, to perpetuate the romantic tradition, and to satisfy the many tourists, who come searching for it annually.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/04/29/tree-owns-itself-athens.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/04/29/tree-owns-itself-athens.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>athens,</category>
        
        <category>travel,</category>
        
        <category>ga,</category>
        
        <category>ajc,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meriwether County teen arrested for alleged death threats against Donald Trump</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Meriwether County Sheriff’s Office said it and agents of the U.S. Secret Service took a 15-year-old juvenile male into custody for terroristic threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The teen made death threats against presidential candidate Donald Trump, according to the release. Police said the teen is being detained at the Columbus Regional Youth Detention Center pending a hearing in juvenile court. The release noted that the Department of Juvenile Justice decided to detain the youth because of this incident and “previous law enforcement-related information.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meriwether County Sheriff Chuck Smith noted said there was another similar incident that happened recently in Troup County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I strongly suggest that parents monitor their kids’ activities on social media,” Smith said. “Hopefully parents can at least sit down and talk with their kids about the consequences of their actions. Use this as a prime example of what they should not be doing. It takes all of us working together to make our community stronger.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/25/meriwether-county-teen-trump-death-threat.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/25/meriwether-county-teen-trump-death-threat.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>trump,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phenix City police, U.S. Marshals arrest alleged fugitive sex offender</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police and the U.S. Marshals Service announced the arrest of David Bauman on the 280 bypass in Phenix City on March 22.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a release, Bauman was a fugitive wanted in Illinois for failure to register as a sex offender and state probation violation. Police said they found a small amount of methamphetamines during the arrest and charged him accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phenix City police said the arrest happened because a “concerned citizen” suspected something was wrong and called the Marshals Service. The police would like to remind people to report suspicious activity to law enforcement agencies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/23/phenix-city-police-david-bauman.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/23/phenix-city-police-david-bauman.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>sexcrime,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No, Scarlett Johansson is not moving to Columbus, Ga.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A bit of viral fluff content has been making the rounds on Facebook claiming that Scarlett Johansson, star of “The Avengers” and “Her,” is moving to Columbus. From the “article:”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a surprise to everyone in Los Angeles and certainly everyone in Columbus, Georgia, Hollywood actress Scarlett Johansson announced today in an interview that she was moving to Columbus.  Scarlett said that she was “tired of the L.A. lifestyle” and wanted to “live in a place where people are just people and whose sincerity you don’t have to always question”.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Johansson recently visited the area for a few days and, according to her publicist, “Scarlett immediately fell in love with the relaxed southern lifestyle, the friendly people, and the beautiful scenery of the Columbus area and was telling everyone that she was going to move there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This story is completely false. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.snopes.com/celebrity-moving-small-towns/&quot;&gt;Snopes.com&lt;/a&gt;, a mythbusting website, noted that a ring of “fantasy news” websites has been churning out these stories for small towns across the country. Here’s one made-up brief about Tom Cruise moving to Beaver Falls, Pennsylvania:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In a surprise to everyone in Hollywood and certainly everyone in Beaver Falls, Tom Cruise announced today in an interview that he was “tired of the Hollywood lifestyle” and that he wanted to “live in a place where people were people and whose sincerity you didn’t have to question”. He recently visited Beaver Falls while scouting out a film location with producer Jerry Bruckheimer and, according to Bruckheimer, “Tom immediately fell in love with the relaxed lifestyle and the tranquil beauty of the surrounding countryside and was telling everyone that he was going to move there.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also stories about Brad Pitt &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mckenziepost.com/new-orleans/brad-pitt-and-angelina-moving-to-breaux-bridge-louisiana/&quot;&gt;moving to Breaux Bridge, La.&lt;/a&gt;, Leonardo DiCaprio &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.snopes.com/leonardo-dicaprio-woodstock-illinois/&quot;&gt;moving to Woodstock, Ill.&lt;/a&gt;, and Justin Bieber &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thatsfake.com/is-pop-star-justin-bieber-moving-to-sandy-in-oregon/&quot;&gt;moving to Sandy, Ore.&lt;/a&gt;, that have remarkably similar formats. Whoever is running these sites uses the same template and fills in the quotes with facts about the town they find on Google, apparently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The websites seem designed to trick readers into sharing the story so the sites collect pageviews. They have generic names like “Local News 33” or “The McKenzie Post” to make the celebrity stories seem more legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only overt admittances of making things up are on the “About Us” pages of these content factories. The one running the fake Scarlett Johansson story says “All news articles on localnews33.com are satire or pure fantasy,” but of course the site doesn’t put that on the article itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So next time you see an incredible story about a celebrity moving to a small town, just remember: If it sounds too good to be true, it probably is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/21/scarlett-johansson-move-columbus-ga.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/21/scarlett-johansson-move-columbus-ga.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>columbus,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
