<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 22:32:42 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 22:32:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>6 Videos from 2015&#39;s biggest stories</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ledger-Enquirer staffers took a lot of video in 2015, from Sunday Interviews to breaking news. These were the six videos that turned the most heads. &lt;style&gt;
#footnote_1 {
	-webkit-animation-duration: .3s;
	-moz-animation-duration: .3s;
	animation-duration: .3s;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;sup&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fn_button&quot; onclick=&quot;showDiv_1()&quot; style=&quot;position: relative; left: 0px;&quot;&gt;•••
&lt;span class=&quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot; id=&quot;footnote_1&quot; style=&quot;display: none;&quot;&gt;For clarity, I did not create any of these videos but did write the recap.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
	var shown_1 = false;
	function showDiv_1() {
		if (document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
			== &quot;none&quot;) {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
				= &quot;inline&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.position 
				= &quot;absolute&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.top = &quot;30px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.right = &quot;0px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.left = &quot;-120px&quot;;
			shown_1 = true;
		}
		else {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display = &quot;none&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).className 
				= &quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot;;
			shown_1 = false;
		}
	}
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;video-police-officer-body-cam-shows-him-shooting-suspect&quot;&gt;Video: Police officer body cam shows him shooting suspect&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By far the most popular video this year was the raw footage showing a Columbus police officer shooting Towon Earl on Nov. 2. Earl was arrested after injuring three officers when he put his car into drive, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article43373514.html&quot;&gt;striking two and injuring a third&lt;/a&gt;. Four different police cameras captured Earl’s actions before he was shot. The Columbus Police Department says it is equipping more officers with the cameras in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article44944272.html&quot;&gt;three-month test program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/crime/article44936805.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;muscogee-county-jail-officials-inmate-get-in-fight&quot;&gt;Muscogee County jail officials, inmate get in fight&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Columbus branch of the NAACP &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29450245.html&quot;&gt;released video&lt;/a&gt; in May of a fight that happened on July 13, 2013, between an inmate of Muscogee County Jail and two officers. Christopher Russell, a diabetic, had complained to deputies about his meals arriving late, according to those involved. The two officers who allegedly attacked him, Deputy Anthony Ermi and Correctional Officer Anthony Merritt, were investigated. Ermi was suspended for 36 hours without pay. Merritt was terminated after being charged with an unrelated crime before the investigation was completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;420&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dJ_QQVFScYs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;home-owners-say-john-rusty-houser-destroyed-their-house&quot;&gt;Home owners say John ‘Rusty’ Houser destroyed their house&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gunman who &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29489611.html&quot;&gt;killed two women and himself in a Louisiana movie theater&lt;/a&gt; in July was the same John Russell “Rusty” Houser who &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/crime/article29490280.html&quot;&gt;vandalized and bobby-trapped the Phenix City house&lt;/a&gt; a Columbus man bought 18 months ago for his daughter out of foreclosure – years after they went to church with Houser and considered him incapable of such horror. Norman Bone, 77, and his daughter, Beth Bone, said the 32nd Street home still isn’t fit to be occupied a year and a half after police accompanied them to seize the house and evict Houser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BJfVrJaUsfY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rangers-help-8-year-old-boy-with-cystic-fibrosis-fulfill-dream-at-fort-benning&quot;&gt;Rangers help 8-year-old boy with cystic fibrosis fulfill dream at Fort Benning&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8-year-old Eleck Stone donned his Army Combat Uniform and boots to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article29435566.html&quot;&gt;spend time with the 3rd Battalion of the 75th Ranger Regiment in March&lt;/a&gt;. Eleck, who has cystic fibrosis, was granted a two-day visit with the elite soldiers through the Make-A-Wish Foundation. Although cystic fibrosis is a life-threatening disorder that causes severe damage to the lungs and digestive system, Eleck joined the Rangers on Thursday and Friday to fire weapons, wear night-vision equipment on a raid, ride in vehicles and take part in other activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VvO5ifDC3fQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;big-smoove-curses-superior-court&quot;&gt;Big Smoove curses Superior Court&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Michael Jerome Johnson, better known as Big Smoove, let Superior Court Judge William Rumer have a piece of his mind before being sentenced for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29462842.html&quot;&gt;2011 murder of Steve Toms&lt;/a&gt;. Johnson showed no remorse and refused to apologize to Toms’ family and friends. He was sentenced to life without parole plus 10 years for the murder of Toms, manager of the Gold &amp;amp; Silver Trading Center, and a strong of armed robberies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IoDYoIm80wM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;female-ranger-candidates-tackle-darby-queen-obstacle-course&quot;&gt;Female ranger candidates tackle Darby Queen obstacle course&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before 1st Lt. Shaye Haver and Capt. Kristen Griest became &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article31477890.html&quot;&gt;the first two women to graduate Ranger School&lt;/a&gt; (followed quickly by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article39408834.html&quot;&gt;Maj. Lisa Jaster&lt;/a&gt;), they had to tackle the infamous Darby Queen obstacle course during the Camp Darby phase of Ranger School.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article31373627.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;honorable-mentions&quot;&gt;Honorable mentions:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/article48602655.html&quot;&gt;Young ballerina dances The Nutcracker following a liver transplant&lt;/a&gt; for being incredibly adorable&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nl4xOArXwLs&quot;&gt;Maj. Gen. Scott Miller answers questions about Ranger School class with two female graduates&lt;/a&gt; because of the subtext of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article44300643.html&quot;&gt;people questioning Ranger School&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/28/best-videos-2015.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/28/best-videos-2015.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>2015,</category>
        
        <category>recap,</category>
        
        <category>video,</category>
        
        <category>rangerwomen,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>ledger</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The University of Alabama is testing fraternity brothers for drug use</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The University of Alabama has quietly started testing members of Greek organizations as part of an extensive mandatory screening program, according to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2015/12/university_of_alabama_quietly.html#incart_big-photo&quot;&gt;AL.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Six current and former members of organizations such as Sigma Nu and Sigma Alpha Epsilon told the site the groups’ Alabama chapters require members to undergo periodic urinalysis “in order to maintain good standing with organizations and the school.” UA administration confirmed to AL.com that it is testing some Greek organizations without saying which ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brothers who fail or miss tests receive escalating warnings from their fraternity. If they fail or miss enough tests they can be kicked out of the organization and have the school notified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2015/12/university_of_alabama_quietly.html#incart_big-photo&quot;&gt;Read the full story&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/18/bama-frat-drug-test.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/18/bama-frat-drug-test.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bama,</category>
        
        <category>drugs,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to track when someone links to your website on Twitter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s always useful to keep track of who’s mentioning your website on Twitter. You can see where the buzz is and engage with your fans, building community and hopefully driving more traffic to your brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can keep track of anytime someone links to your website with some free web tools- it’s just a matter of connecting them together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter has a lot of advanced features under the hood. If you know where to look there’s a lot of great ways to find content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter accepts special search terms to narrow down content. You can search for tweets in a specific geographic area, tweets mentioning a topic, tweets to a person or tweets with a link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last bit is how you can track any time someone links to your website. Open TweetDeck and create a new column. Search for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“domain.com” filter:links -from:yourTwitterNameWithNo@ -from:yourWriters&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “-from:name” can be repeated as many times as you’d like to filter out your own writers or employees. Obviously it’s not as big a deal if they’re tweeting out your content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The domain and link bit cuts it down to only tweets that include a link to your website. Twitter stores all links secretly as t.co links, but it still knows where they all link to and searches that. This search works across all link shorteners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-get-notified-when-someone-links-to-your-site-on-twitter&quot;&gt;How to get notified when someone links to your site on Twitter&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you don’t use TweetDeck, or maybe you’d rather have them notify you and not have to check a column yourself. To do that, we’re going to string together &lt;a href=&quot;https://warble.co/&quot;&gt;Warble&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com/&quot;&gt;IFTTT&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may want to set up a new email account to avoid having your email flooded with notifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, sign into Warble and create a new alert. Input the same search as above. Whenever the results for that search change, Warble will email you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next-level system involved IFTTT. You can connect your email account within the system and set it to do something else whenever you get a new email from Warble. Check out our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/20934/create-powerful-connections-with-ifttt&quot;&gt;review of IFTTT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/43294/10-clever-recipes-ifttt-do-apps&quot;&gt;10 clever recipes for the service&lt;/a&gt;. IFTTT is genius because you can have it do whatever you want when you get an email from Warble: text message, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pushbullet.com&quot;&gt;Pushbullet&lt;/a&gt;, another email (not sure why you’d want that), an Android or iPhone notification or a tweet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;think-before-you-retweet&quot;&gt;Think before you retweet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fair warning: I have found that you need to be careful with who you interact with on Twitter. They may have tweeted your story but they may not be someone you want associated with your brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to also check the links they tweet to be sure they work- I saw one guy tweeting a “story” from us that was just a 404.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s fascinating to see who tweets your stories and what they think of them. Hopefully this helps you grow your site and interact with your users.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/16/twitter-link-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/16/twitter-link-blog.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>twitter,</category>
        
        <category>social,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>technorms,</category>
        
        <category>guide</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus rated sixth-worst city for dating in America</title>
        <description>&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_dating_in_columbus&quot; title=&quot;Dating in Columbus&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?aL7&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/dating_in_columbus&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;Dating in Columbus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/16/columbus-worst-city-dating.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/16/columbus-worst-city-dating.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating,</category>
        
        <category>columbus,</category>
        
        <category>living,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to &#39;Y&#39;allywood&#39; (also known as Columbus, Georgia)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If all goes well, Columbus is going into show business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus State, the Springer Opera House and the state of Georgia are starting a special program to train Georgians to work on the sets of movies and TV shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Springer artistic director Paul Pierce said film has become a $6 billion industry in Georgia because of the state’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/opinion/opn-columns-blogs/article29456854.html&quot;&gt;generous tax credits&lt;/a&gt;. With 157 feature films produced in this state in fiscal year 2015, Pierce said, there are more jobs in the movie industry than ever before. However, there aren’t enough Georgians to fill these jobs.&lt;style&gt;
#footnote_1 {
	-webkit-animation-duration: .3s;
	-moz-animation-duration: .3s;
	animation-duration: .3s;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;sup&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fn_button&quot; onclick=&quot;showDiv_1()&quot; style=&quot;position: relative; left: 0px;&quot;&gt;•••
&lt;span class=&quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot; id=&quot;footnote_1&quot; style=&quot;display: none;&quot;&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.boston.com/news/opinion/2015/03/06/what-wrong-with-film-industry-tax-incentives-they-don-work/wRzsGm3OegxBjDCgINEj9L/story.html&quot;&gt;major debate&lt;/a&gt; over whether these things actually work. I would love to explore that, but this story was already pushing it at a thousand words.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
	var shown_1 = false;
	function showDiv_1() {
		if (document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
			== &quot;none&quot;) {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
				= &quot;inline&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.position 
				= &quot;absolute&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.top = &quot;30px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.right = &quot;0px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.left = &quot;-120px&quot;;
			shown_1 = true;
		}
		else {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display = &quot;none&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).className 
				= &quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot;;
			shown_1 = false;
		}
	}
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Georgia just doesn’t have the volume of scenic carpenters, scene painters, set decorators, lighting electricians, grips, prop masters, audio engineers or wardrobe professionals to crew all these films,” Pierce said. “Jets are landing in Hartsfield-Jackson every day with film workers from other states who are going directly to work sites. Gov. Deal is determined to put a stop to that, and we are determined to help him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deal invited Pierce to bring the Georgia Film Academy to Columbus. In just four weeks, a task force with representatives from CSU, the Springer, Columbus Tech, Columbus CVB, the Columbus Film Office and the Muscogee County School district put together a plan to meet the need for film-trained workers, according to Richard Baxter, dean of the College of the Arts at Columbus State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In January, CSU will offer a six-credit hour class starting Jan. 11 training 60 students in the basics of the film business. The class will use the Springer facilities. When students have learned about working on a set and know some of the equipment, they’ll spend a second 12-credit hour class working at Pinewood Studios in Fayette County on an actual film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baxter said students could put the credits toward their baccalaureate or take just those two semesters and leave with a certification. Students can take that certification to the Georgia Film Academy and get certified to work within a union on films anywhere in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“More and more film is coming to Georgia, and we’re happy to announce Columbus is going to be ground zero in the training of these new workers for these lucrative jobs,” Pierce said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSU will be one of only three schools in Georgia tasked by the Georgia Film Academy to offer these certifications (the other two are Clayton State University and Gwinnett Technical College).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baxter said the waiting list for this uncommon program is long enough that they’re working on a second section that will use Springer’s facilities on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the program will take advantage of Columbus’ capabilities to train students, working in most of Georgia’s film industry will take them outside the Chattahoochee Valley. There is no Columbus equivalent to the sound stages for movie-making like the ones in production in Effingham and Gwinnett Counties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We recognize this opportunity for Columbus means that we’re going to be training workers for the production studios outside of Columbus initially, but our hope is this cadre of talented students in the motion picture business will get the attention of those studios who will look to Columbus for their next project,” said Bill Murphy, executive vice president of economic development for the Greater Columbus Chamber of Commerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kevin Flowers, a music producer better known as Kevin Gr8 Trakz Lamar, tentatively guessed Columbus could get its own sound stage within a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They’ve been talking about this for the last year or so,” he said. “It’s going to be taken care of.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flowers said he was interested in working with students from the program. He said he already uses the CSU orchestra for producing film scores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terrence Manns, an independent filmmaker who works in Columbus, said he’s used Columbus State students for his job as well. He told the Ledger-Enquirer he wouldn’t mind hiring people straight out of the new program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking of taking the program myself,” Manns said. “As a filmmaker, you can never stop learning.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little bit of learning could result in a big payoff. Pierce said the jobs are so lucrative that even an entry-level position could pay $45 per hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flowers confirmed the pay scale, saying he’s charged $100 per hour on some projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like other industries, the money depends on the specific job and hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Payden Evans is a senior at Auburn University who works in the film industry. He’s worked as an extra and production assistant on shows like “The Vampire Diaries” and “Sleepy Hollow” and movies in the “Divergent” series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans said as a production assistant, he makes about $120 for a 12-hour shift. He said salaries in the movie industry vary by department and whether the person is in a union. Union rules mandate things like time-and-a-half pay for hours worked past a certain point and double pay on Saturdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans said it while a program like CSU’s is not mandatory for joining the movie business, it can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think it’s smart to have a working idea of set lingo and how things flow,” he said. “You don’t need it, but it’s not a bad idea. My learning curve was a lot steeper because I had a lot of lingo thrown at me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior, who graduates Saturday with a degree in media studies, said breaking into the industry was tough. He attributes his chance to a fraternity brother with a family friend in the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie industry is great for those who want to get in, Evans said. It just requires an incredible amount of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s not the glitz and the glamor that’s on the screen,” he said. “It’s early mornings and late nights. I was on set at 4 a.m. and I wouldn’t get off until 6 to 8 at night.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job isn’t regular like a 9-5 either. Evans said working on a TV show could mean nine months of work. A movie could be anywhere from a few weeks to a few months, depending on the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To students who want to get into that business, Evans advised persistence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do what is asked of you and do more if you can,” Evans said. “People take note of hard work… Georgia is a great place to be if (film is) something you’re into. Go for it. The opportunity is there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Credit to the Columbus, Georgia Film Office for the title. They claim “industry insiders” call Georgia’s burgeoning film industry ‘Y’allywood.’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a big story for our area. Georgia’s film industry is big business. However, we need to ask who is getting the benefit of that business. CSU and Springer are selling this program on $45/hr for entry-level jobs, and that’s just not what everyone will get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I consider this a good story because it covers an important event while offering another perspective for some realism. Maybe these kids really will get $45/hr, I don’t know. But they do deserve to hear what it’s really like from someone who’s not trying to sell them an 18-credit hour class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/10/columbus-movie-training.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/10/columbus-movie-training.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movies,</category>
        
        <category>csu,</category>
        
        <category>columbus,</category>
        
        <category>georgia,</category>
        
        <category>education,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This song about Georgia Sen. Johnny Isakson is awful and amazing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Georgia Senator Johnny Isakson drew my attention this morning when he tweeted his thanks to a band for writing a song about… Sen. Johnny Isakson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Wow, never had a song written about me. Thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PapaRazziAndThePhotogs?src=hash&quot;&gt;#PapaRazziAndThePhotogs&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;m undeserving but flattered nonetheless. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/SdPaMKVgOI&quot;&gt;https://t.co/SdPaMKVgOI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Johnny Isakson (@SenatorIsakson) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SenatorIsakson/status/672423470349832192&quot;&gt;December 3, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve linked another copy of the song below, and it is… something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p8f1ysdH3GQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The singer is an odd duck. From &lt;a href=&quot;http://noisey.vice.com/blog/This-Genius-Lunatic-Has-Recorded-16000-Songs-About-Everything-from-Poop-to-Ellen-Degeneres&quot;&gt;Vice&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Matt Farley is a guy in his mid-30s living in Northeastern Massachusetts. He runs an entertainment company called Motern Media that manages about 70 bands that together have recorded just over 16,000 songs. The thing is, he also plays in all of the bands and sings in all of the bands and is the only person in all of them. Motern Media is Matt Farley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This guy churns out an average of 20 songs per day. It’s all weird stuff designed to pick up people searching weird terms for very specific songs. He makes a little bit of money every time you search for a song about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-SLX_qO1uvQ&quot;&gt;knowing how to tie a tie&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBfX9ucGXNU&quot;&gt;how great Robert Downey, Jr. is&lt;/a&gt;. It works, too- &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/media/media-blog/2014/jan/29/spotify-how-a-busy-songwriter-youve-never-heard-of-makes-it-work-for-him&quot;&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt; said Farley makes $23,000 a year from his entire catalogue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This song about Johnny Isakson comes from &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/u.s.-senators/id954900502&quot;&gt;an album of songs about U.S. Senators&lt;/a&gt;. Why does that exist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/johnny-isakson-song.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/johnny-isakson-song.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>music,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mixed reaction among Columbus residents to women in combat</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Women are joining men on the front lines of combat, and some people in Columbus are okay with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An informal poll revealed support for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/article47724225.html#storylink=mainstage&quot;&gt;the decision&lt;/a&gt;, with a few qualifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Women should be allowed to do anything that they can,” said Margie Watson, of Columbus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watson said she hopes the military holds men and women to the same standards and doesn’t change them just because women are allowed in combat positions. She said she was also concerned about the physical ability of women to fight on the frontlines because they are not as strong as men “for the most part.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Manzi, who was visiting from Denver, said he could think of a few women who were strong enough to meet the combat standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I work out twice a day, five days a week, and some of the women [in the gym] are impressive,” Manzi said. “If they want to do it and they can do it, that’s great.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manzi said he supported the decision and would not change anything about it. He pointed to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article39389271.html&quot;&gt;first three women to graduate Ranger School&lt;/a&gt; as an example of what female soldiers can do if given the opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Meadows, a master’s student in history at Columbus State, said she approved of opening combat positions to women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a huge, huge step,” she said. “It is equal to women earning the right to vote.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meadows qualified her support as well, citing concerns about physiology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are built different,” she said. “There’s no denying that one.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Meadows said she expected female soldiers would overcome physical limitations through training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lester Mahone said he did not approve of women being on the front lines. He told the Ledger-Enquirer it would be better to keep them in non-combat support roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s too dangerous for a woman,” he said. “It’s really not a lady thing. It’s not.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His wife Lisa Mahone agreed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let the men do the fighting,” she said. “We need our women out here to help our men.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/army-women-combat-reactions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/army-women-combat-reactions.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>rangerwomen,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opelika woman hikes more than 2,000 miles from Georgia to Maine</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auburn graduate and Opelika resident Jessica Mills recently completed a hike of 2,189.2 miles along the Appalachian Trail from Springer Mountain, Ga., to Mount Katahdin in Maine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;The Auburn Plainsman&lt;/a&gt; reported Mills’ trip, which began at Amicalola Falls State Park in Georgia on March 29. Mills told The Plainsman she planned to hike it in 2012 but took a job in Colorado instead. After returning to Auburn in the fall of 2014, she tackled the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When Jessica left for the trail, I was naturally afraid for her safety,” said her mother Rhonda. “Although I would have felt better if she wasn’t starting out by herself, I knew she would soon make friends and wouldn’t be hiking alone for long.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills kept a journal along the trail, recording her thoughts in &lt;a href=&quot;http://homemadewanderlust.com/cross-the-line/&quot;&gt;text&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQhqmV26773qZhzqJz4VFcw&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. She has a great eye for capturing the local color in an area. It’s worth reading for anyone curious about the experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills recommended hiking the trail to any Auburn student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re going to be an expert at hanging a bear bag because you have so much experience throwing paper towel rolls,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;Read the full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TSWTjQ0p3nU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>hiking,</category>
        
        <category>environment,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling &#39;politically incorrect&#39; T-shirts for charity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Harris County Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling T-shirts with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/news-columns-blogs/chuck-williams/article47197945.html&quot;&gt;the sign that broke the internet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For $12-19 (depending on size), you can buy a politically incorrect T-shirt with “Harris County Georgia” on the front and “WARNING: Harris County is politically incorrect. We say: Merry Christmas, God Bless America and In God We Trust. We salute our troops and our flag. If this offends you… LEAVE!” on the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Harris County &lt;a href=&quot;http://harris-county.com/pc/&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; selling the shirts said all profits from the sales will go to Jolley’s favorite charities, Georgia Sheriffs’ Youth Homes and Scott’s Miracle Riders. Buyers can also get the shirts from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Boutiqueonthesquare/&quot;&gt;Boutique on the Square&lt;/a&gt; in Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jolley’s decision to sell shirts showing his &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article46241055.html&quot;&gt;controversial sign&lt;/a&gt; drew a condemnation from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://americanhumanist.org/&quot;&gt;American Humanist Association&lt;/a&gt;, a group headquartered in Washington, D.C., which works to protects the rights of humanists, atheists and Americans who don’t believe in a god.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Far from being a politically incorrect joke, the Harris County sheriff’s sign and t-shirts are an egregious violation of the Establishment Clause [of the Constitution],” said Monica Miller, senior counsel at the Appignani Humanist Legal Center. “Many local citizens object to the divisive message of the sign and t-shirts, which send a disturbing message of intolerance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Association asked Harris County stop selling the T-shirts on a government website and move the sign to private property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AHA gave legal reasoning to support its claim that the original sign was unconstitutional in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://aha-files.s3.amazonaws.com/2/3b/6/5831/20151125_Harris_County_-_Georgia_Sheriff_Sign_-_AHA_Letter.pdf&quot;&gt;letter sent on Nov. 25&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If it truly offends someone, they’re more than welcome to leave,” Jolley &lt;a href=&quot;http://insider.foxnews.com/2015/11/27/georgia-sheriff-mike-jolley-proud-be-politically-incorrect&quot;&gt;told Fox &amp;amp; Friends&lt;/a&gt; in response to the AHA. “I spent 20 years in the Army to give everyone the right to disagree with me or anyone else. If they disagree, they can voice that opinion. But if it offends them, truly offends them, then maybe they’re in the wrong country.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>christianity,</category>
        
        <category>christmas,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check out these UFO reports from around the Chattahoochee Valley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, there have been a half-dozen UFO sightings around Columbus and Phenix City over the past two years according to an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/webreports/ndxloc.html&quot;&gt;online database&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center collects anonymous reports from around the country on strange and unexplainable sights. They have reports of sightings going back to the ’60s, and from every state. We put together an infographic of reports from the Chattahoochee Valley over the last two years, as well as Alabama and Georgia for the previous seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take all of this with a huge grain of salt&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; These are unconfirmed, anonymous reports about things that sound a lot like military aircraft. The CIA &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.popularmechanics.com/space/a3995/4304207/&quot;&gt;estimated&lt;/a&gt; that more than half of all UFO sightings in the ’50s and ’60s were actually secret U-2 and SR-71 spy planes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One British journalist who produced “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Mirage-Men-Adventure-Espionage-Psychological/dp/1602398003&quot;&gt;Mirage Men: An Adventure into Paranoia, Espionage, Psychological Warfare, and UFOs&lt;/a&gt;” said the government actually encouraged UFO theories and conspiracies to cover up experimental aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“UFO stories are used as a cover story for the flight-testing of experimental and clandestine aircraft,” &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.usnews.com/opinion/articles/2010/09/16/the-truth-behind-ufo-sightings-and-the-us-air-force&quot;&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; author Mark Pilkington. “If you look at the places where UFO sightings are frequent, they are also the places where the military tests its experimental aircraft.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_ufo_sightings-120&quot; title=&quot;UFO Sightings&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?Zer&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/ufo_sightings-120&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;UFO Sightings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center was founded in 1974 by UFO investigator Robert J. Gribble. The Center’s primary purpose, according to its &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/General.html&quot;&gt;biography&lt;/a&gt;, is to record and document reports from individuals who have witnessed unusual or UFO-related events. Its data has been used by other outlets to create products like &lt;a href=&quot;http://metrocosm.com/ufo-sightings-map.html&quot;&gt;this US map of sightings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I considered trying to make excuses for the quality of this database but quickly realized that was impossible. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>ufo,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
