<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:17:03 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:17:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opelika woman hikes more than 2,000 miles from Georgia to Maine</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auburn graduate and Opelika resident Jessica Mills recently completed a hike of 2,189.2 miles along the Appalachian Trail from Springer Mountain, Ga., to Mount Katahdin in Maine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;The Auburn Plainsman&lt;/a&gt; reported Mills’ trip, which began at Amicalola Falls State Park in Georgia on March 29. Mills told The Plainsman she planned to hike it in 2012 but took a job in Colorado instead. After returning to Auburn in the fall of 2014, she tackled the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When Jessica left for the trail, I was naturally afraid for her safety,” said her mother Rhonda. “Although I would have felt better if she wasn’t starting out by herself, I knew she would soon make friends and wouldn’t be hiking alone for long.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills kept a journal along the trail, recording her thoughts in &lt;a href=&quot;http://homemadewanderlust.com/cross-the-line/&quot;&gt;text&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQhqmV26773qZhzqJz4VFcw&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. She has a great eye for capturing the local color in an area. It’s worth reading for anyone curious about the experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills recommended hiking the trail to any Auburn student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re going to be an expert at hanging a bear bag because you have so much experience throwing paper towel rolls,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;Read the full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TSWTjQ0p3nU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>hiking,</category>
        
        <category>environment,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling &#39;politically incorrect&#39; T-shirts for charity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Harris County Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling T-shirts with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/news-columns-blogs/chuck-williams/article47197945.html&quot;&gt;the sign that broke the internet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For $12-19 (depending on size), you can buy a politically incorrect T-shirt with “Harris County Georgia” on the front and “WARNING: Harris County is politically incorrect. We say: Merry Christmas, God Bless America and In God We Trust. We salute our troops and our flag. If this offends you… LEAVE!” on the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Harris County &lt;a href=&quot;http://harris-county.com/pc/&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; selling the shirts said all profits from the sales will go to Jolley’s favorite charities, Georgia Sheriffs’ Youth Homes and Scott’s Miracle Riders. Buyers can also get the shirts from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Boutiqueonthesquare/&quot;&gt;Boutique on the Square&lt;/a&gt; in Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jolley’s decision to sell shirts showing his &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article46241055.html&quot;&gt;controversial sign&lt;/a&gt; drew a condemnation from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://americanhumanist.org/&quot;&gt;American Humanist Association&lt;/a&gt;, a group headquartered in Washington, D.C., which works to protects the rights of humanists, atheists and Americans who don’t believe in a god.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Far from being a politically incorrect joke, the Harris County sheriff’s sign and t-shirts are an egregious violation of the Establishment Clause [of the Constitution],” said Monica Miller, senior counsel at the Appignani Humanist Legal Center. “Many local citizens object to the divisive message of the sign and t-shirts, which send a disturbing message of intolerance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Association asked Harris County stop selling the T-shirts on a government website and move the sign to private property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AHA gave legal reasoning to support its claim that the original sign was unconstitutional in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://aha-files.s3.amazonaws.com/2/3b/6/5831/20151125_Harris_County_-_Georgia_Sheriff_Sign_-_AHA_Letter.pdf&quot;&gt;letter sent on Nov. 25&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If it truly offends someone, they’re more than welcome to leave,” Jolley &lt;a href=&quot;http://insider.foxnews.com/2015/11/27/georgia-sheriff-mike-jolley-proud-be-politically-incorrect&quot;&gt;told Fox &amp;amp; Friends&lt;/a&gt; in response to the AHA. “I spent 20 years in the Army to give everyone the right to disagree with me or anyone else. If they disagree, they can voice that opinion. But if it offends them, truly offends them, then maybe they’re in the wrong country.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>christianity,</category>
        
        <category>christmas,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check out these UFO reports from around the Chattahoochee Valley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, there have been a half-dozen UFO sightings around Columbus and Phenix City over the past two years according to an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/webreports/ndxloc.html&quot;&gt;online database&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center collects anonymous reports from around the country on strange and unexplainable sights. They have reports of sightings going back to the ’60s, and from every state. We put together an infographic of reports from the Chattahoochee Valley over the last two years, as well as Alabama and Georgia for the previous seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take all of this with a huge grain of salt&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; These are unconfirmed, anonymous reports about things that sound a lot like military aircraft. The CIA &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.popularmechanics.com/space/a3995/4304207/&quot;&gt;estimated&lt;/a&gt; that more than half of all UFO sightings in the ’50s and ’60s were actually secret U-2 and SR-71 spy planes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One British journalist who produced “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Mirage-Men-Adventure-Espionage-Psychological/dp/1602398003&quot;&gt;Mirage Men: An Adventure into Paranoia, Espionage, Psychological Warfare, and UFOs&lt;/a&gt;” said the government actually encouraged UFO theories and conspiracies to cover up experimental aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“UFO stories are used as a cover story for the flight-testing of experimental and clandestine aircraft,” &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.usnews.com/opinion/articles/2010/09/16/the-truth-behind-ufo-sightings-and-the-us-air-force&quot;&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; author Mark Pilkington. “If you look at the places where UFO sightings are frequent, they are also the places where the military tests its experimental aircraft.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_ufo_sightings-120&quot; title=&quot;UFO Sightings&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?Zer&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/ufo_sightings-120&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;UFO Sightings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center was founded in 1974 by UFO investigator Robert J. Gribble. The Center’s primary purpose, according to its &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/General.html&quot;&gt;biography&lt;/a&gt;, is to record and document reports from individuals who have witnessed unusual or UFO-related events. Its data has been used by other outlets to create products like &lt;a href=&quot;http://metrocosm.com/ufo-sightings-map.html&quot;&gt;this US map of sightings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I considered trying to make excuses for the quality of this database but quickly realized that was impossible. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>ufo,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sergeant in marshals honored for rushing into house fire while injured</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Kurt Weathered of the Muscogee County Marshals was honored with the department’s first-ever Medal of Bravery at the Government Center Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/1125_COLO_fire2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kevin Flowers, left, lost his home to a fire. Kurt Weatherd, right, said he rushed inside the home to make sure Flowers wasn&#39;t asleep inside.&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Kevin Flowers, left, lost his home to a fire. Kurt Weatherd, right, said he rushed inside the home to make sure Flowers wasn&#39;t asleep inside.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he was on his couch at home, recovering from surgery on his Achilles tendon and about to watch “Gunsmoke,” when he saw smoke coming from his neighbor’s house. He said he put his boot on his bad foot and &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/11/25/man-rushes-burning-house.html&quot;&gt;hopped across the street without crutches into the house&lt;/a&gt;. He said he was afraid his neighbor Kevin Flowers was asleep inside the burning house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are here because Sergeant Weathered saw the need to lay down his own life and go into a burning house to save the life of his friend and neighbor,” said Muscogee County Marshal Greg Countryman. “He did not know if he would come out of that burning house. This was a very heroic act.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For his bravery, Weathered received the Medal of Bravery. Countryman said the department has had the award but never given it before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We never do anything expecting to get anything in return,” Weathered said. “It means a lot to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he tried to open the door by smashing a window with his ASP baton. When he saw the door had a chain on it, he hopped in front of it, stood on his boot and used his good foot to smash open the front door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quick search of the living room revealed a collapsing ceiling but not Flowers. Weathered ran back outside, got a flashlight from his wife Angela and went back into the house. He said he kicked down the bedroom door looking for Flowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My heart dropped because I thought he was on the bed,” Weathered said, choking up as he spoke at the ceremony. “He wasn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Weathered saw Flowers’ car was not in the garage, he left the house. Flowers told the Ledger-Enquirer he was at the bank at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just thank God for giving me the courage not to follow my mind saying, ‘Man, get out of here. It’s hot,’” Weathered said. “Thank god for my training. I’m just glad (Flowers) is safe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he was also glad to provide a &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/10/09/stickers.html&quot;&gt;positive example of public service&lt;/a&gt; to contrast with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/article46184715.html&quot;&gt;negative news about law enforcement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to do some good because that’s what you signed up for,” he said. “The badge that you wear don’t make you a god. It sets you out to be that example and be that one to help when someone’s in need.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/01/marshal-medal-bravery-fire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/01/marshal-medal-bravery-fire.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>localhero,</category>
        
        <category>fire,</category>
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hundreds fed at Valley Rescue Mission</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Volunteers and needy families filled the large white tent by Valley Rescue Mission on Thanksgiving to both give and be served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just really wanted to serve the Lord,” said Kathy Hutto, who drove in from LaGrange to help. “He’s been really good to me lately and I wanted to serve Him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mitzi Oxford, the Mission’s development director, estimates that they served more than 800 people at the tent. The women and children’s center, Damascus Way, also fed everyone at the shelter and delivered meals to more than 300 elderly shut-ins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event required more than 100 volunteers, donations from around the community and a great deal of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_thanksgiving_charity&quot; title=&quot;Thanksgiving charity&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?y1o&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/thanksgiving_charity&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;Thanksgiving charity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterbuilt smoked more than 100 turkeys so the Downtown Rotary Club could de-bone them. Summerville Road Baptist Church delivered desserts, and St. Luke School made the table centerpieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abigail Pritchett, 10, came with her grandparents Christopher and Debbie Kearns from Ellersly to help serve others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just love to see their happy faces,” Pritchett said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hutto agreed, calling it “a worthwhile trip.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/valley-rescue-mission-thanksgiving.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/valley-rescue-mission-thanksgiving.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thanksgiving,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>charity,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lonely, poor and addicted invited to charitable Thanksgiving</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Trevor Morris just wanted to help some people for Thanksgiving. On Monday, he posted to Facebook that his restaurant, the Trevioli Artisan Pasta Company, would close to the public and instead open to people who needed a good Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trevioli will be closed to the public this Thursday, November 26th. Conversely, we will be opening our doors to the less...&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Trevioli-artisan-pasta-company-648844985150099/&quot;&gt;Trevioli artisan pasta company&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot;&gt;Monday, November 23, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post, which Facebook said was viewed by more than 50,000 people, attracted around a dozen customers and 20-25 volunteers in the first hour. The event was Thursday from 3 p.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company gave away food donated by groups around the Valley. Morris estimated he could feed up to 500 with everything he had received. He said he wasn’t sure what to do with the extra food, but would probably give it to another charity or hand it out to the needy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the first time Morris has tried something like this charitable Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said it was just something good he wanted to try, especially after experiencing the other end of charity as a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There was a time in my life when I was on the other side of the coin, when I was in line to get a free meal,” Morris said. “I was thankful to whoever did it. So I feel like if you can, you should.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The restaurant owner said he grew up in a family with a lot of kids and little money. Welfare, food stamps and free lunches at school were what Morris said got his family by. In a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29435938.html&quot;&gt;Job Spotlight from March 2015&lt;/a&gt;, he also told the Ledger-Enquirer his upbringing included a mother addicted to drugs and his own depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I remember that there was a local bakery that would find needy families like ours and they would bring stuff by all the time,” Morris said. “I always thought that was super cool as a kid.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Natalie Blackwell, 26, said she volunteered to help the dinner as part of a joint decision with her mother. Her brother is in Atlanta and her mother is in South Carolina and they could not get together for Thanksgiving. Instead, Blackwell and her mother decided to do charity for the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s the whole purpose of Thanksgiving,” Blackwell said. “What better way is there to give back?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morris said he asked for the lonely and anxious to visit as well because of the problems associated with the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is the time of the year where your suicide rate goes up,” he said. “If there’s a chance that somebody came in today who needed just one more day of being around people to save them from going over the edge or relapsing or suicide or whatever, it would be so awesome if we could be something that prevents that from happening.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/trevioli-thanksgiving-meal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/trevioli-thanksgiving-meal.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thanksgiving,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>charity,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime briefs for 11/26/15</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;An unknown suspect robbed the Mystik Gas Station at 645 Brown Ave., according to a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said a young black man in a black hoodie with a white emblem and red mask, blue gloves, dark jeans and black and white shoes entered through the east-facing door. The report said the suspect used a black semi-automatic handgun to rob the store between 6 p.m. and 6:18 p.m. Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police did not list what was taken and are still investigating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;man-arrested-for-possession-of-crack-cocaine-and-pills&quot;&gt;Man arrested for possession of crack cocaine and pills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/gardner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Antoine Gardner, 31&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Antoine Gardner, 31&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police arrested a man for possession of multiple types of drugs, a report said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several officers were at 947 Illges Road in an attempt to locate a wanted person. Police said at the residence they found .1 grams of crack cocaine (street value $10) and 5 Zolpidem Tartrate pills, also known as Ambien (street value $50).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Antoine Gardner, 31, was arrested and charged with possession of Schedule IV and II drugs and possession of a Walther .22 pistol, the report said. Police are not planning a follow-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;police-4-year-old-girl-molested&quot;&gt;Police: 4-year-old girl molested&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police responded to a call about an alleged molestation of a 4-year-old girl, according to a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victim’s mother called police around 1 p.m. Wednesday to report an incident that happened between 8 p.m. Nov. 20 and 8 p.m. Nov. 22, according to police. The report does not list any suspects, only that the assailant was not a stranger and the incident occurred somewhere on Avery Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case remains under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chevy-malibu-reported-stolen-from-woodruff-farm-road&quot;&gt;Chevy Malibu reported stolen from Woodruff Farm Road&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A car was stolen in the 3000 block of Woodruff Farm Road, according to a police report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police said a gold four-door 2007 Chevy Malibu with the temporary tag 14944327 was stolen between 12 a.m. and 7 a.m. Wednesday morning. The report does not list how much the car is worth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police are investigating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/drug-arrest-cocaine-pills-robbery.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/drug-arrest-cocaine-pills-robbery.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Missing 13-year-old and 14-year-old girls found, police say (Crime briefs for 11/25/15)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus police in a news release said they have found two missing local girls who reportedly were headed to Panama City Beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/holloway.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jillian Holloway&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Jillian Holloway&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police were looking for Jillian Holloway, 13, and Jessica Hardie, 14.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a statement emailed this afternoon, Detective Richard Campbell of the special victims unit reported:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They were located in Panama City Beach. They are fine. Their parents are on their way to Florida to pick them up.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Florida NBC TV affiliate WJHG reported Wednesday afternoon the teenage girls were found at Reid’s Court on Front Beach Road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;man-arrested-for-possession-of-methamphetamine-and-cocaine-report-says&quot;&gt;Man arrested for possession of methamphetamine and cocaine, report says&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police reported that they went to a home in the 900 block of 42nd Street to serve a violation of parole warrant to Darren Rathel, 47. Police said they were let into the residence by Rathel’s mother and found Rathel hiding inside a closet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When an officer searched Rathel’s bedroom, he found 2 grams of suspected crystal methamphetamines, 0.5 grams of suspected cocaine, 1 gram of suspected marijuana, a digital scale, marijuana grinder and a glass smoking device, according to the report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said Rathel was arrested and charged with possession of Schedule II drugs, possession of marijuana and drug-related items.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/missing-girls-drugs-arrest.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/missing-girls-drugs-arrest.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man rushes into neighbor&#39;s burning house on one foot</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A house at the corner of Lantern Lane and Lantern Court caught fire Wednesday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kevin Flowers, who lives in the house, said he was at the bank for less than an hour when he started getting “a whole lotta calls.” He said he does not know why or how the fire began.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kurt Weatherd, a sergeant in the Muscogee County Marshals, said he called 911 at 12:49 p.m. when he saw a lot of smoke coming from Flowers’ house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weatherd said he recently had surgery on his achilles tendon and could put a little pressire on his right foot, but not much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This did not stop Weatherd from going across the street to open Flowers’ door and rushing inside to look for him, even when it meant hopping on one leg. He said he had to bust down a few doors with his good leg to check the bedroom and garage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My main concern was whether (Flowers) was inside asleep,” Weatherd said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weatherd, who is ex-military, said he didn’t hesitate to go into the burning building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Stuff like this, it’s our job to run one way when everyone else is running the other,” he said. “When you got family, you don’t think about yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Battalion Chief Bobby Dutton said it took the fire department an hour to put after it got into the attic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dutton said the cause of the fire was still under investigation. He couldn’t put a number on the cost of the damages, only that the house was a total loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s bad that it happened the day before Thanksgiving, but we’re just glad nobody got hurt,” Dutton said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgMiddle capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/1125_COLO_fire3.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;The fire department said the house was a total loss.&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The fire department said the house was a total loss.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/man-rushes-burning-house.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/man-rushes-burning-house.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>localhero,</category>
        
        <category>fire,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Columbus police searching for murder suspect</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus police have released the name of the man suspected of &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/11/24/shooting-murder-cusseta.html&quot;&gt;Monday’s fatal shooting of Marcus Bowden&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said a murder warrant has been issued for Demartre Trevon Harris, 22. He is a 5-foot-10, 170-pound black male with brown eyes and black hair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This suspect should be considered armed and dangerous,” Lt. John R. McMichael of the Robbery and Homicide Division of Columbus police said in a release. “Anyone with information about this suspect or about the incident is asked to contact Robbery/Homicide at 706-653-3400.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marcus Bowden, 30, was shot in the stomach multiple times Monday morning around 11:24 a.m. Bowden was taken to Midtown Medical Center and pronounced dead at 12:35 p.m. He had multiple gunshots to his lower body. Chief Deputy Coroner Freeman Worley told the Ledger-Enquirer he could not say the official cause of death before an autopsy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McMichael said Bowden’s body will be taken to the State Crime Lab for an autopsy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/bowden-suspect-search.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/25/bowden-suspect-search.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>marcusbowden,</category>
        
        <category>murder,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
