<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 13:12:33 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 13:12:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Morning brief- Lesley Vance&#39;s replacement election and the state of the city</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today’s news to watch includes a special election for Alabama residents and an address from Mayor Teresa Tomlinson on the state of the city. Here are some stories to keep an eye on during the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-state-of-city-speech&quot;&gt;The State of City speech&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayor Teresa Tomlinson will present her &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/article55289805.html&quot;&gt;fifth State of the City address&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday during a luncheon held by the Greater Columbus Chamber of Commerce at the Columbus Convention and Trade Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In past State of the City addresses, Tomlinson has spoken of accomplishments in her administration’s past and plans for the city’s future. This year she may touch on thawing the “tax freeze” and the city’s budget. We could also see some more results from the city’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/article45294375.html&quot;&gt;program to reduce jail population&lt;/a&gt;, a system the Ledger-Enquirer editorial board &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/opinion/article51941870.html&quot;&gt;approves of.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;phenix-city-special-election&quot;&gt;Phenix City special election&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgMiddle capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/blackshear.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Phenix City councilman Chris Blackshear is running to replace Lesley Vance in District 80 of the Alabama House.&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Phenix City councilman Chris Blackshear is running to replace Lesley Vance in District 80 of the Alabama House.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article42725541.html&quot;&gt;sad passing of Lesley Vance&lt;/a&gt; last November, three Republicans are &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article55235195.html&quot;&gt;vying to take his place&lt;/a&gt; to represent District 80 in the Alabama House of Representatives. Today is the vote between civil engineer James McGill, Phenix City councilman Chris Blackshear and Russell County School Board representative Tommy Pugh. Polls will be open 8 a.m.-8 p.m. EST in Phenix City and Smiths Station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should no candidate get more than 50 percent of the vote, a runoff will coincide with Alabama’s March 1 primaries, which may confuse voters again as two separate elections coincide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/18/lesley-vance-election-state-city.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/18/lesley-vance-election-state-city.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>morning,</category>
        
        <category>elections,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Great Mac Games (January 2016)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Windows is undeniably the best way to play games on a PC, but that doesn’t mean you’re left out in the cold on an Apple computer. With &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/46674/games-porting-to-mac&quot;&gt;more games ported to Mac than ever&lt;/a&gt; and a good &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/35226/use-only-an-external-display-with-a-macbook&quot;&gt;external display&lt;/a&gt;, it’s a great time to be a Mac gamer. Here are a few games (as of January 2016) you should try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;team-fortress-2&quot;&gt;Team Fortress 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you love multiplayer shooters but feel like you don’t have the twitch reflexes and mouse-and-keyboard skills to keep up with the pros? Team Fortress 2 is for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valve’s long-running shooter is constantly updated with new free content on top of a rock-solid multiplayer base. That base is like nothing else in multiplayer gaming- it was designed to be a competitive shooter for people bad at shooters. Even if you’re not great at pulling headshots with the Sniper (and don’t play Sniper), you can still contribute to the team as a Medic or Engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interplay between the classes and best-in-class maps make TF2 a must-play for any PC gamer. TF2 is also our stand-in for basically every Valve game. They’re all on Mac, and they’re all worth playing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://store.steampowered.com/app/440/&quot;&gt;Download Team Fortress 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ftl-faster-than-light&quot;&gt;FTL: Faster Than Light&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FTL: Faster Than Light is best described as a &lt;em&gt;Firefly&lt;/em&gt; simulator. You captain a ship on a voyage across the universe, dodging space pirates and the forces chasing you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FTL is set up as a roguelike. Each run starts you from the beginning, with a new crew, ship and randomized universe. Exploring the galaxy and trying to survive in this tough game is a great fun for any sci-fi fan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mac port is alright. It’s a fun game that’ll also heat your your computer for free. Power consumption could be better. Still, FTL is a good time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://store.steampowered.com/app/212680/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Download FTL: Faster Than Light&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tomb-raider-2013&quot;&gt;Tomb Raider (2013)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tomb Raider reboot from 2013 made its way to Mac! The newest take on Lara Croft’s adventures leaves her stranded on a strange island with homicidal natives. Exploring the island while trying to survive makes for a gripping game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tomb Raider reboot is notable because it gets Lara Croft right for the first time in years. It focuses on solving puzzles, fighting bad guys and exploring unknown areas. It’s a well-polished adventure that anyone with the graphics card to handle should try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://store.steampowered.com/app/203160/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Download Tomb Raider&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;undertale&quot;&gt;Undertale&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining why so many people love Undertale would be nearly impossible. The best summary is that if you like old-school RPGs like Earthbound and Final Fantasy, you need to play Undertale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game is $10 and 5 hours of clever, subversive RPG gameplay. Undertale is warm and funny and dark all at the same time. It happily upends your expectations and leaves you with a profound sense of affection for its world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mac port is excellent. Undertale doesn’t use too much power and runs in a resizable window (or full screen). It stays simple and avoids problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://store.steampowered.com/app/391540/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Download Undertale&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hearthstone-heroes-of-warcraft&quot;&gt;Hearthstone: Heroes of Warcraft&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blizzard’s digital collectable card game has earned a legion of fans for its approachable gameplay that hides a long skill curve. It’s so simple until you realize everything going on behind every play and reach the upper levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hearthstone deserves a special not as well for living on multiple platforms. You can play the game with your same card collection on Mac, iPad and iPhone. I would highly recommend Hearthstone on an iPad- it is a fantastic tablet game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mac port works well. It runs fast and doesn’t drain your battery unless you turn up the graphics to high. At that point you’ll get buttery smooth 60fps, albeit at the cost of battery life on a MacBook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://us.battle.net/login/en/?ref=http://us.battle.net/hearthstone/en/&amp;amp;app=com-hearthstone&amp;amp;opt&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Download Hearthstone&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hall-of-shame&quot;&gt;Hall of Shame&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soma&lt;/strong&gt;: Awful Mac port that does not support Intel graphics cards, which is most of them. Very few Macs still have a dedicated GPU.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hotline Miami&lt;/strong&gt;: Bad Mac port that requires modifying the app wrapper to play in full-screen correctly, and even that doesn’t work perfectly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Walking Dead&lt;/strong&gt;: Bugtacular Mac port that crashes constantly. It’s hard to feel the emotional weight of a scene when one character vanishes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wrappers&lt;/strong&gt;: If it’s in Cider or Wineskin, don’t.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, Windows is your best bet for serious PC gaming. If you’d like to keep working on a Mac, though, these are some good options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/16/great-mac-games-try.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/16/great-mac-games-try.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>gaming,</category>
        
        <category>mac,</category>
        
        <category>apple,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>technorms,</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boy with tumor lives tank commander dream</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It took only 6 tank rounds, two tanks and one tank simulator to make Mason Giove’s day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason doesn’t say much. He’s 12 years old, pale, and has trouble lifting his right leg. His father Mark Giove, who helped him walk from the car to the Abrams M1A2 Main Battle Tank and Bradley A3 tank, said Mason can’t lift his right arm because of a partial paralysis on his right side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wow,” Mason said as he approached the tanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason has been fighting a brain tumor since he was 15 months old. He’s two months into his fourth round of chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason traveled from Whitman, Mass. (25 miles south of Boston), to Fort Benning on a chilly Friday on a special visit to see real tanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t really know exactly what the love of tanks comes from, but from a very early age he’s been very interested in all aspects of the military,” Mark said. “When other kids are playing these games, he’s there watching a movie about D-day or about Vietnam.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark said his son’s nickname at the Dana-Farber Cancer Institute, where he’s treated, is “Mr. Tank.” Mark has called Mason that ever since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/tanker2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mason Giove, 12, is fitted with tank headgear while inside a M1A2 Abrahms during a visit with soldiers from Alpha Troop, 1-16 Squadron, 316th Cavalry Brigade Friday.&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Mason Giove, 12, is fitted with tank headgear while inside a M1A2 Abrahms during a visit with soldiers from Alpha Troop, 1-16 Squadron, 316th Cavalry Brigade Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mark said he and Mr. Tank had no idea what they were in for when they visited Fort Benning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The visit began in the morning when soldiers under the command of Lt. Col. Jeff Paine, squadron commander of the 1st Squadron in the 16th Cavalry Regiment, got Mason into uniform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We told him, ‘Hey, you’re going to be a soldier for the day, I need you to get into the proper uniform,’” said Sgt. 1st Class Chad Nebergall. “I brought out a uniform for him. He loved that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nebergall said they put a general’s patch on Mason’s uniform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He’s the only one-star general in the brigade level,” said Capt. Bryce Land, Alpha Troop commander of the 1st Squadron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The soldiers took Mason and his family out to the Hastings Range and let them stand nearby as they fired six rounds from an Abrams tank. They shot three HEAT (high-explosive anti-tank) rounds, three sabot rounds and the machine gun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I had no idea this was going to happen,” Mark said. “I had no idea I was going to be standing 30 yards away from a tank and having my chest reverberate.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Land said he jumped at the chance to help plan the visit, including seeing the range.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sharing something I love, something that I do every day, with somebody who probably loves it even more, I couldn’t help it,” Land said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paine and Land said they wanted to make sure the trip from Massachusetts was more than seeing a static display of a tank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You can’t come down here and see tanks and not see the boom,” Land said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Giove family connected with Paine and Land through a network of family friends. Mark Giove is friends with Eric Runci, a Massachusetts native who works in Atlanta for Aflac. Runci knows Andrew Kloster, a veteran who works as a manager at Fort Benning. Kloster is Paine’s neighbor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“In the military, so often we spend so much time behind fences on post at Fort Benning or somewhere else,” Paine said. “There’s a whole huge country out there with people that we’re part of and responsible to and here to defend. When we get an opportunity like this to come reach out to them, it’s something we just love to do.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Kloster, Mason has a juvenile pilocytic astrocytoma, a rare childhood brain tumor that sits in the middle of his brain next to his thalmus. He struggles with communication, feeding and muscle weakness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason’s tumor grows slowly and in strange directions. Mark said the doctors are fighting the tumor the same way it grows: with slow rounds of chemotherapy that last all year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(Fighting cancer is) all he’s known his entire life,” Mark said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The constant struggle has been hard on his family, according to Mark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s really tough on my wife,” he said. “He’s a tough little kid. I get a lot of inspiration from him but it’s not easy at all. Taking care of him, it’s like we have another 3-year-old.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Mark said he can see some where Mason’s cancer has forced their family to become closer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I tell people all the time that I would take his cancer away in a heartbeat if I could, but I wouldn’t take what it’s given my family and me,” Mark said. “It made me who I am.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason’s friends and family express great admiration for him as well. Kloster called him “smart and inquisitive” and “loving and fun.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That day at Fort Benning, Mason’s cancer meant helping him into and out of the tanks. He explored the insides, tried on the helmets with noise-canceling headphones and got a tour of the equipment from the members of the 16th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they were done, the soldiers presented him with several gifts, including a Class A jacket from Staff Sgt. Dennis Mathews, a t-shirt with the phrase “Keep Calm and Load Sabot” and the metal core of a HEAT round that had been fired earlier that day on the range.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mason who reacted mostly through wide smiles, summed up his feelings about the day afterwards in the tank simulator in three words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I loved it.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/15/boy-tumor-tank-commander.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/15/boy-tumor-tank-commander.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>charity,</category>
        
        <category>fortbenning,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Useful Tips for Using a Slow, Low-End Windows PC</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Computers are never perfect. We’ve all been stuck with that annoyingly slow work computer, the one loaded down with way too many unwieldy enterprise programs and not enough memory. You might be able to build the sleekest rig in existence but your company probably won’t let you use it for work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working with a Windows PC for my day job that could definitely be faster. 2 GB of RAM and an older processor means there is only so much I can run at a time before it starts locking up. Here are some quick tips I found to manage system resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tips-for-using-a-slow-low-end-work-pc&quot;&gt;4 Tips for Using a Slow, Low-End Work PC&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;no-more-chrome&quot;&gt;No more Chrome&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look, Chrome is great. It’s incredibly popular among power users because of its fast development time, modern interface, ease of use and deep library of extensions. I use Chrome on my personal computer because it’s fast and my MacBook Air’s 8 GB of RAM can handle it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But here’s the thing. Chrome uses a lot of memory. &lt;a href=&quot;http://lifehacker.com/why-chrome-uses-so-much-freaking-ram-1702537477&quot;&gt;Seriously, a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of memory&lt;/a&gt;. From Lifehacker:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Chrome splits every tab, plugin, and extension into its own process, so that if one thing crashes—like Flash—it doesn’t bring down the whole web page, or all your tabs at once. This can lead to higher memory (aka RAM) usage, since it has to &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.chromium.org/2008/09/google-chrome-memory-usage-good-and-bad.html&quot;&gt;duplicate some tasks for every tab&lt;/a&gt;. But it also makes things a lot more convenient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that plus pre-rendering pages in the background means Chrome takes up a boatload of memory that you probably can’t spare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution? Use &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/?product=firefox-3.6.8&amp;amp;os=osx%E2%8C%A9=en-US&quot;&gt;Firefox&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my experience, Firefox tends to be jankier and less sleek than Chrome. However, it also uses a hell of a lot less memory. It doesn’t even load tabs into your PC’s memory until you click on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;no-more-flash&quot;&gt;No more Flash&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mistakenly thought the best way to listen to Spotify on a slow PC was to do it through the browser. Then it’s just a tab, and that takes up less memory than a desktop app, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wrong. Internet Spotify runs on Flash, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.extremetech.com/computing/209888-mozilla-firefox-kills-flash-by-default-security-chief-calls-for-adobe-to-issue-an-end-of-life-date&quot;&gt;Flash is the worst&lt;/a&gt;. You are far better off just not using Flash (my build of Firefox seems to have it disabled by default) for power, memory, security and sanity reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;use-small-portable-apps&quot;&gt;Use small, portable apps&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a win for sanity, security and memory. Once again, it means (in one case) avoiding an Adobe product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of all the things you use your PC for. Opening a PDF. Composing a document. Editing a spreadsheet. Email. Now find programs that do those things while using the bare minimum of memory. Think of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sumatrapdfreader.org/free-pdf-reader.html&quot;&gt;Sumatra PDF&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WordPad&quot;&gt;WordPad&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/sheets/about/&quot;&gt;Google Sheets&lt;/a&gt; and a Gmail tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These programs have twin advantages of being easy on your computer and easy to install, even if you don’t have administrative access to your work PC. Avoid big, heavy programs like Adobe Reader and Microsoft Excel (unless you’re doing serious spreadsheet work). They are less safe, take up more memory and are just worse in a lot of cases than the simple alternatives. If you’re composing unformatted text, why bother with all of Microsoft Word?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;switch-windows-theme&quot;&gt;Switch Windows theme&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Windows 7 and up in particular have partially transparent windows that look nice but require a good bit of processing power. You can switch it off to save a little speed when rendering windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To switch it off, right-click on the desktop &amp;gt; Personalize &amp;gt; Themes &amp;gt; Windows 7 Basic. This switches all the windows to a flat color. It doesn’t look as nice but it is a little faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest thing to do with a computer that doesn’t have a lot of memory is to use the right program. Firefox over Chrome, Sumatra over Adobe Reader, etc. Pick the program that does the bare minimum and stick to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, be sure to restart your PC every once in a while. &lt;a href=&quot;http://giphy.com/search/hello-it-have-you-tried-turning-it-off-and-on-again&quot;&gt;Turning it off and back on again&lt;/a&gt; is the universal solution to most computer problems and can solve even most slowdowns.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/11/useful-tips-low-end-pc.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/11/useful-tips-low-end-pc.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>windows,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>technorms,</category>
        
        <category>guide</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Watch this Phenix City girl play Adele backwards and in Spanish</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Katlin Hill won $20 like you’ve never seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her father, Felix Omar Hill of Phenix City, bet Katlin a Jackson that she could not play Adele backwards and in Spanish. Katlin won.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-video&quot; data-allowfullscreen=&quot;1&quot; data-href=&quot;/100010640376533/videos/vb.100010640376533/147770212254324/?type=3&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/100010640376533/videos/147770212254324/&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/100010640376533/videos/147770212254324/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;20$ just gone.............Tell Katlin ur opinion/purchase Cd at teamkatlin.org or Donate/please share this Video ( Katlin is 15 years old )&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/people/Felix-Omar-Hill/100010640376533&quot;&gt;Felix Omar Hill&lt;/a&gt; on Sunday, December 13, 2015&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It wasn’t my idea,” she said. “I thought it was insanely crazy… (Playing the keyboard backwards and in Spanish) just comes to me, I guess.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katlin is 15 years old, and her voice has touched millions. When Felix uploaded the video to Facebook, it was viewed more than 6.9 million times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I went from 70 fans to 7 million overnight,” Katlin said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katlin has been playing music since she was 10. She performed at The Loft at age 12, the youngest person to ever play there. However, she said she didn’t realize the extent of her gifts until the last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Phenix City resident said she left Central High School after 10th grade to become homeschooled. She said she loves it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katlin said she hopes to pursue a full-time career as a solo artist. She’d love to sing full-time and perform at Carnegie Hall, the famous New York City concert venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her biggest musical influence is her favorite artist, Alicia Keys, especially Keys’ song “Fallin’.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the viral video, Felix said she is booked to play a show every weekend for the rest of the year. They’re planning shows in the Dallas and Jacksonville, Fla., area and even as far away as Uganda, where Felix has connections through his work as a minister for Greater Grace Ministries. On Jan. 30, Katlin will play an even higher-profile gig when she tries out for “America’s Got Talent” in Atlanta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performing has its highlights (singing the national anthem at the Columbus Civic Center) and its troubles (losing a microphone mid-performance), according to Katlin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She loves doing this,” Felix said. “It’s nothing that could force her to do.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The experience is its own reward, especially when she can see people’s reactions. Audiences show different feelings when they see her sing, from astonishment to apathy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Without sounding prideful, this is where I was supposed to be in life,” Katlin said. “If I were to not do this, I would not be content.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/11/adele-backwards-spanish-kaitlin-hill.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/11/adele-backwards-spanish-kaitlin-hill.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>music,</category>
        
        <category>arts,</category>
        
        <category>humaninterest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>features</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Things You Should Know Before Building a Gaming PC</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m shopping for a gaming PC, and it’s been a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/31561/windows-users-impressions-macbook-air&quot;&gt;owning a MacBook Air is great&lt;/a&gt;. But &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.technorms.com/46674/games-porting-to-mac&quot;&gt;OS X has never been great about gaming&lt;/a&gt;. Apple’s sleek machines just aren’t built to be power-hungry graphics powerhouses (outside of Mac Pros). Thus, the gaming PC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shopping for a gaming PC has taught me a lot. It’s not easy to get into building your own computer, especially if you don’t know how to do it right. Here’s what I’ve learned so far. Take it with a grain of salt, as I am a total newbie. Veterans, feel free to sound off in the comments below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;research-and-read-before-buying&quot;&gt;Research and read before buying&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the three biggest things you can do to make your search for the perfect gaming PC easier- read, read, read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PC gamers are passionate about their hobby and they love to share it with others. After all, the only thing more fun than building a gaming PC is posting your build online to show it off to everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc&quot;&gt;/r/BuildAPC&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tomshardware.com&quot;&gt;Tom’s Hardware&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://pcpartpicker.com&quot;&gt;PCPartPicker&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly helpful resources for people who are getting started and don’t know where to look. Part manufacturers seem to have taken it upon themselves to make naming and research as confusing as possible (more on that in a minute), so having someone help you through the process is a godsend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve settled on a build that seems reasonable and is rated to play your favorite games, toss it out on one of the forums for help. Just be honest that you’re a first-timer and people should help you. Probably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;researching-parts-is-comparing-apples-and-horses&quot;&gt;Researching parts is comparing apples and horses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of the most annoying parts of learning about PC components. They all use long, confusing names that sounded cool on paper to some marketing department but mean nothing to a layman. How am I supposed to compare an AMD Athlon X4 860K 3.7GHz quad-core processor to an Intel Core i3-4170 3.7GHz dual-core processor without an engineering degree?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best way is to find reviews for each product and compare benchmarks. You can also make an educated guess based on the brand and when it was made (newer chips tend to be faster… I think).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tomshardware.com/answers/id-1986387/intel-amd-gaming.html&quot;&gt;this helpful guide&lt;/a&gt;, Intel chips tend to have fewer cores, but these cores are pound-for-pound more powerful than an AMD equivalent. AMD processors tend to use more cores that are less powerful. Newer games that are built to take advantage of multi-threaded computing can take advantage of this, but a lot of older titles tend toward the single-threaded life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Single-threaded means they only use one core at a time, and if we’re getting into single-core performance then Intel comes out on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing to look out for is the difference between generations. An i3 isn’t the same as an i3 released several years before because of Intel’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Intel_CPU_microarchitectures&quot;&gt;chip generations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really, the whole thing is a confusing mess for newcomers. There’s just no quick-and-dirty way to compare parts that I’ve found. If there is, please let me know in the comments. I could use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;you-may-be-better-off-on-console&quot;&gt;You may be better off on console&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something I considered long and hard before keeping on with an attempt to purchase a PC. Consoles are plug-and-play. They offer (mostly) seamless gaming without any of the hassle of checking system requirements and downloading drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say that with a grain of salt because consoles seem to be emulating the worst of PCs in the last few years. Constant updates and patches used to only be something you saw on bad PC games. Using a console is not frictionless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your choice of platform is a personal one, in the end. If your friends are on Xbox Live and want you there so everyone can play &lt;em&gt;Destiny&lt;/em&gt; together, the answer is obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I value my Steam library and certain PC games (Hearthstone, Civilization V, Undertale) too much to leave that ecosystem. But really think about whether going PC is the best choice for you before buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you have tips for building a good gaming PC? Let us know in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/06/lessons-learned-gaming-pc.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/06/lessons-learned-gaming-pc.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>buildapc,</category>
        
        <category>gaming,</category>
        
        <category>windows,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>technorms,</category>
        
        <category>guide</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get excited for the national championship with this hype video</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Alabama Crimson Tide are taking on the Clemson Tigers in the national championship game on Jan. 11. Before that game starts, it’s never too early to get pumped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video comes courtesy of Campus Insiders. It’s a little heavy on Clemson highlights (and light on Derrick Henry smashing through players or &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/10/29/derrick-henry-squat-weight.html&quot;&gt;lifting ridiculous amounts of weight&lt;/a&gt;), but it’s a good start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;590&quot; height=&quot;332&quot; src=&quot;http://launch.newsinc.com/?type=VideoPlayer/Single&amp;amp;widgetId=1&amp;amp;trackingGroup=69016&amp;amp;siteSection=islandpacket&amp;amp;videoId=30142112&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; noresize=&quot;&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/05/alabama-hype-video.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/01/05/alabama-hype-video.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bama,</category>
        
        <category>cfl,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything open on New Year&#39;s in the Chattahoochee Valley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re collecting everything fun to do in the Chattahoochee Valley for New Year’s Eve. Are we missing something? Let us know in the comments!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/646615912145594/&quot;&gt;Dawg House&lt;/a&gt; - Haywire plays at 9pm. No cover, closes around 2-3 a.m.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/sportspage.columbus/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;The Sports Page&lt;/a&gt; - No cover, two live bands, prizes and giveaways from Jim Beam and Bud Light. Breakfast menu starting at 1 a.m. after free champagne toast at midnight.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1085423691470227/&quot;&gt;Soho Bar and Grill&lt;/a&gt; - $10 cover, live music from Doublewide Revival, free champaign toast at midnight and free food.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/martinis.broadway/&quot;&gt;Martinis on Broadway&lt;/a&gt; - $10 admission, free wings, Alabama game, live music from DJ Truz, champagne toast at midnight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/162081850821786/&quot;&gt;Uptown Tap&lt;/a&gt; - $5 cover, live DJ, free party favors, free champagne toast, prize balloon drop, a ball drop in the courtyard, prizes and giveaways.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/theloft.columbus/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;The Loft&lt;/a&gt; - $20 tickets at the door to see &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.laurareed.com/&quot;&gt;Laura Reed&lt;/a&gt; at 8:30 p.m. The Garry Land Band performs with Alia Torres at 8 p.m. Breakfast buffet, $39 petit filet with grilled lobster tail, $27 special with grilled grouper. Tickets go on sale at 7:30 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Bobbys-Bar/113449252021511?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Bobby’s Bar&lt;/a&gt; - No cover. People are bringing snacks, there will be champagne. “Beer bar, cash only.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/WildWingCafeColumbusParkCrossing/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Wild Wing Cafe&lt;/a&gt; - Alabama game, countdown to midnight and champagne.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/pages/Marios-Restaurant-Pub/567516923355691?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Mario’s Restaurant and Pub&lt;/a&gt; - Free admission. Free champagne and dessert with any dinner, lamb special.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/raftersofcolumbus/?fref=ts&quot;&gt;Rafters Bar and Nightclub&lt;/a&gt; - Opens at 8 p.m., free entry before 11 p.m., Alabama game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/31/new-years-open-valley.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/31/new-years-open-valley.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>newyears,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>living,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chattahoochee flooding the highest in 12 years</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chattahoochee River is overflowing, but not as much as it has before, according to &lt;a href=&quot;http://water.weather.gov/ahps2/river.php?wfo=ffc&amp;amp;wfoid=18694&amp;amp;riverid=204159&amp;amp;pt[]=151303&amp;amp;allpoints=144009%2C145755%2C146347%2C146046%2C148265%2C141510%2C144017%2C146057%2C148221%2C141577%2C148222%2C145815%2C143757%2C145502%2C146346%2C141767%2C151303%2C146625%2C142944&amp;amp;data[]=all&quot;&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from the National Weather Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their water level gauge said the Chattahoochee has been above 27 feet for several days, the official minimum for “flooding.” As of this writing, it is at 28.5 feet, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article52201700.html#storylink=mainstage&quot;&gt;more than enough to put parts of the RiverWalk underwater&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is by all means the most significant flood Columbus has had in 12 years,” said Kent Frantz, a service hydrologist with the National Weather Service. “&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historical data from the NWS reveals the current levels of flooding are comparable to other floods in the last 25 years with water levels such as 35.84 feet on at 12:30 p.m. on Christmas Day. Frantz said this year’s surge was the 18th-highest on record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The highest crests, according to the records, were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;55.20 feet on March 15, 1929&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;52.60 feet on Dec. 12, 1919&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;49.80 feet on Feb. 26, 1961&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;48 feet on Jan. 19, 1925&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;45.89 feet on April 8, 1964&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those numbers have dropped in recent years because of development from the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers and Georgia Power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The biggest thing is all of the dams that were built,” Frantz said, citing the Buford and West Point Dams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the NWS site, “moderate” flooding occurs at 42 feet. The flooding is rated is “major” once it crosses 47 feet. The river is “flooding” when it gets above 27 feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frantz said 34 feet used to be the minimum for a flood until it was lowered to 27 to accommodate the Riverwalk and Phenix City Ampitheater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Floods are rated and tracked by their potential to cause damage to the city, Frantz said. The NWS site includes a damage chart that estimates the costs of every extra foot of water. For example, the NWS guesses that 35 feet of flooding would expand upstream and downstream from the 14th Street Bridge. It would also put the Riverwalk under 8 feet of water and flood the maintenance room under the Trade Center up to 3 feet. “Portions of the Oxbow Creek Golf Course in south Columbus will be flooded,” according to the chart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 45 feet, portions of Bay Avenue and 14th Street in Columbus and Second Avenue in Phenix City start flooding. Homes in low-lying areas of the Valley start seeing water from the Weracoba and Bull Creeks. The Phenix City Ampitheater would be completely flooded and large portions of the Alabama Riverwalk would be under 7 feet of water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That was very close [to causing more damage] at 36 feet,” Frantz said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;55 feet of flooding is considered “catastrophic” with “most bridges closed with extensive damage to homes and businesses.” Thankfully, the Chattahoochee &lt;a href=&quot;http://water.weather.gov/ahps2/crests.php?wfo=ffc&amp;amp;gage=cbug1&amp;amp;crest_type=historic&quot;&gt;does not appear to often reach those levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The forecast for the next few days’ flooding has the river hovering around 28 feet through the New Year before dropping down to 25.3 feet by noon Jan. 4, depending on weather. A high pressure buildup and a few days’ break from rain should lower the water levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Everything should finally have the chance to flow out,” Frantz said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tim Chitwood contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;columbus-floods-throughout-history&quot;&gt;Columbus floods throughout history&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1929&lt;/strong&gt;: The 1929 flood, according to Wes Owens’ article in a 1961 issue of the Sunday Ledger-Enquirer, saw waters rise more than halfway up the fence around Golden Park and flood the stands. Bay Street and Front Avenue were covered with several feet of water. The flood also knocked out the city’s gas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1919&lt;/strong&gt;: The 1919 flood was known as the “Pershing Flood” because it coincided with Gen. John J. Pershing’s visit to Fort Benning. The area flooded again when Pershing visiting in 1922, causing him to quip, “I thought all along Columbus would make a good Army post, but I’m beginning to think it could also be used by the Navy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1841&lt;/strong&gt;: The Dillingham Street Bridge gave in to a flood in March 1841 locals called “the Harrison freshet” after the new president, William Henry Harrison. Two days of rain lifted one end of the bridge from its pier and floated ti downstream. The newspaper reported, “…never was there a more majestic sight seen, than the departure of that noble bridge, on its remarkable voyage. Its course was uninterrupted as we learn, until it reached Col. Woolfolk’s plantation, eight miles below, where it took up new moorings, in the centre of a large cotton field.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— Virginia Causey&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/30/chattahoochee-flooding-historic.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/30/chattahoochee-flooding-historic.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>flooding,</category>
        
        <category>weather,</category>
        
        <category>columbus,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five ways to feel better and live better during the New Year</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As New Year’s Day approaches, it’s time to make changes and focus on personal growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To celebrate, we’ve compiled a list of small things to do once a year that can help improve or tidy your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clean out your closet&lt;/strong&gt;: Look through your clothes. Is there anything in there you haven’t worn in the last year? Why not? Would you wear it tomorrow? If not, do you really need it? Some outfits (formal wear or interview suits) might need to stay, but consider donating what you don’t need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteer for the holidays&lt;/strong&gt;: One of the best things anyone can do around this time of year is volunteer to help others. Ask your church what they’re doing around town to help out, and help them. Charities always need time or money from those who can afford to give either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go somewhere unusual&lt;/strong&gt;: Do you eat at the same restaurant? Hang out at the same bar? Change it up! Regularity brings comfort in one hand and discontent in the other. Variety can help you see different people and break out of a rut.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change the batteries on your smoke alarm&lt;/strong&gt;: There is nothing more infuriating than hearing a chirping noise from a smoke detector running out of power. Save yourself the frustration and change the batteries before they start beeping at you. Oh, and it’ll keep you safe from fires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Write down a list of what you’re proud of&lt;/strong&gt;: Obviously this varies from person to person, but people can be hard on themselves. Take a minute after the New Year’s Eve parties to write down five things you’re proud of doing or having. They can be personal accomplishments, relationships, whatever. It’s just good to remember all the good things.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/29/new-year-todo.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/29/new-year-todo.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>newyears,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>living,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
