<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 15:35:33 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 15:35:33 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fort Benning couple going to court over surrendered dog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A Fort Benning couple is going to court to get their dog back after giving it up at Fort Benning Animal Control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R. Edward Furr, their attorney, said he hoped to commence legal action in the Superior Court of Chattahoochee County on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have tried mild and lenient measures,” Furr said. “It’s pretty clear to us based on what we’ve learned today that we just have to file suit.” &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conflict began when 21-year-old Blake Lechner, a specialist in the 3rd Infantry Division, received news that he would be transferred to Korea. The transfer would happen between January and August 2016, according to his wife, Ashley Lechner, 23.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley said the two thought they would have to give up their 1-year-old bulldog named Spot. Blake took the dog to Fort Benning Animal Control on Saturday. Later that day, Ashley said he learned that there was a way to transport his family and dog back to their relatives in Lancaster County, Penn. Because the family could help take care of Spot, they tried to get him back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley said they tried calling the Tri County Animal Rescue, which handles strays and surrenders for Fort Benning, but received no answer. She said she tried messaging them Sunday morning and was told that she’d have to wait until Monday. On Monday, the couple went to the shelter but did not get their dog back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We know that we made a mistake, and we tried to fix that mistake right away,” Ashley said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tri County Rescue offers a 12-hour window in which owners who change their mind can take their dogs back. Furr said the Lechners did not receive a fair 12-hour period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/46939711-story&quot;&gt;originally reported by Fox 5 in Atlanta&lt;/a&gt;, has sparked a reaction that strikes the employees of the Tri County Rescue as misguided. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:2&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The truth of the whole thing is completely different,” said Andrea Hoffman, who works at the shelter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hoffman said when Spot was dropped off at the rescue he was shaking, not neutered and not registered on base. Her son, Thomas Hoffman, said the dog’s medical records were inaccurate, listing him as neutered when he wasn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoffman said the rescue refused to give Spot back because of concerns about his living conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If they would have come to us as an adopting client, they wouldn’t have met the criteria,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoffman cited concerns about letting an intact bulldog back into a family with a 2-year-old and a 3-month-old. He also said the dog was jumpy and not leash trained. He said he feared it got into fights with the Lechners’ other dog, a 4-year-old boxer lab mix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Lechner said while Spot could be “jumpy,” he had never touched their children other than to lick them while giving kisses and never fought with the other dog. She also said they’d be willing to get Spot, a “hyper” dog, the proper medical care and further training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoffman also disputes that the dog was surrendered because of the Lechners’ concerns over a transfer to Korea. He said the form they filled out mentions behavioral issues and nothing about a transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They surrendered the dog because of behavioral concerns, Thomas Hoffman said, adding they tried to get it back because they were embarrassed when neighbors and others found out the dog was at the rescue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two parties offer differing versions of other issues as well. Furr said the Tri County Rescue posted a picture of Spot Sunday morning on Facebook offering him up for adoption, just a day after receiving him, in order to make money off of adoption fees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post and Facebook page have been deleted because Thomas Hoffman said he and his family received threats. A &lt;a href=&quot;http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:old7U8f527MJ:https://www.facebook.com/pages/Fort-Benning-Animal-Control/1603152486626439+&amp;amp;cd=5&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;ct=clnk&amp;amp;gl=us&quot;&gt;cached page&lt;/a&gt; saved by Google shows Fort Benning Animal Control calling Spot an “owner surrender” and “adoptable this next week!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thomas Hoffman said the rescue was not motivated by profit, saying that the shelter relies on his father’s pension after 27 years in the military.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Lechner said she realizes the family made a mistake and wants Spot back, even if it means going to court.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Our family did not want to come to this,” Lechner said. “It’s not cheap, but for our family this is what we have to do.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Perhaps unsurprisingly, both parties told me they feel they have the moral high ground and feel sorry for the other, who are nice people who just got caught up in the wrong thing.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:2&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It looks like Fox 5 tried to get the rescue’s side but they did not give it to them at the time. The backlash after the first story definitely changed staffs’ minds.  &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:2&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/13/fort-benning-couple-sue-surrender-dog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/13/fort-benning-couple-sue-surrender-dog.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>animals,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Play &#39;Minecraft&#39; in a movie theater this Saturday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Carmike 15 will allow “Minecraft” fans to play the game in the theater with the help of &lt;a href=&quot;https://superleague.com/&quot;&gt;Super League Gaming&lt;/a&gt;. The group created a mod called “theater mode” that allows up to 100 gamers to play simultaneously while watching the action unfold on screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event host will be prominent Minecraft YouTuber &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/MineplexOfficial&quot;&gt;ParkerGames&lt;/a&gt;. The event starts at 10:30 a.m., Nov. 14. It will last 100 minutes. &lt;a href=&quot;https://superleague.com/carmike&quot;&gt;Tickets&lt;/a&gt; cost $20. Parents are welcome to stay and watch for free. Participants should bring their own laptops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We know gamers really want to get out of their rooms and start playing video games in a much more social atmosphere surrounded by like-minded peers,” said Super Leage Gaming president and COO Brett Morris. “Competing in solitude is outdated.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/sJMzZolKe8Q&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/12/minecraft-movie-theater.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/12/minecraft-movie-theater.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>minecraft,</category>
        
        <category>gaming,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Georgia and Alabama earn failing grades in government corruption index</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Georgia state government is the 24th-least corrupt in the nation, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.publicintegrity.org/2015/11/09/18367/georgia-gets-d-grade-2015-state-integrity-investigation&quot;&gt;according to the Center for Public Integrity&lt;/a&gt;, a nonprofit investigative journalism group. The rating is an improvement from three years ago when the state was rated dead last on a different scale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Center praised 2013’s Georgia Government Transparency and Campaign Finance Act, which limited gifts to individual lawmakers at $75.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Lawmakers and lobbyists are adjusting to the new reality,” the report said. “For the most part, the swanky steak dinners and “educational” golfing trips have been replaced by more modest expenditures.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the law does not require state employees to register as lobbyists. This allows members of the government, such as employees at public universities, to lobby lawmakers without being subject to the $75 gift limit. State employees can give football tickets to politicians, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You can’t get tickets to the Falcons, but [the University of Georgia] can say here are tickets to the president’s box,” said UGA political science professor Charles Bullock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Georgia also earned poor marks for a weak ethics agency and restricting access to what should be open records.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Georgia’s shortcomings in oversight and accountability pose a continued risk for corruption and unethical conduct in state government, and the State Integrity Investigation shows that improvements over the past few years are largely incremental,” the Center said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.publicintegrity.org/2015/11/09/18322/alabama-gets-d-grade-2015-state-integrity-investigation&quot;&gt;Alabama&lt;/a&gt; actually earned the seventh-highest place on the list with a D+ ranking. Its grade was brought down by the widespread and rampant corruption among its politicians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Two of Alabama’s past six governors have been convicted while in office and sent to prison, one on a bribery conviction he still is appealing and the other for appropriating inaugural campaign funds for personal use,” the Center said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alabama’s rating also dropped because of the trial of Auburn representative and Alabama House Speaker Mike Hubbard. Hubbard, after championing an ethics law, was charged with 23 felonies under that same law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.publicintegrity.org/2015/11/09/18822/how-does-your-state-rank-integrity&quot;&gt;Read the evaluations for all 50 states.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/10/georgia-alabama-failing-corruption.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/10/georgia-alabama-failing-corruption.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>corruption,</category>
        
        <category>georgia,</category>
        
        <category>alabama,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Video- Alabama student tased and beaten by Tuscaloosa police after noise complaint</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Internal affairs investigators for the Tuscaloosa Police Department are looking into officers reportedly beating and tasing an Alabama student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tuscaloosa police said the incident occurred on Nov. 8 at 3:19 a.m. and happened because of a loud music call, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cw.ua.edu/article/2015/11/video-shows-police-using-taser-on-ua-student&quot;&gt;Crimson White&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Videos of the incident were released on Twitter Sunday ( &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/petepajor/status/663516103377817600&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coyotehunter25/status/663544355748257793&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kelloggskling/status/663507438298116097&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Np53t79rQ4&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;). The videos show several Tuscaloosa police officers dragging a man out of an apartment before using a stun gun on him and hitting him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://totalfratmove.com/police-beating-tasing-in-tuscaloosa/&quot;&gt;Total Frat Move&lt;/a&gt; said the student has been charged with harassment, obstruction and resisting arrest. He declined to comment to the Crimson White about the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A full investigation of the circumstances that are depicted in these videos will be conducted and all appropriate measures taken to ensure the integrity of the Tuscaloosa Police Department in serving the citizens of Tuscaloosa,” police said in the statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;display: inline-block; margin: 2.25%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-video&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Is this legal? This happened in Tuscaloosa over a noise complaint. Make this go viral &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/sb7UG34sPa&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/sb7UG34sPa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Kellen Kling (@kelloggskling) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kelloggskling/status/663507438298116097&quot;&gt;November 9, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;display: inline-block; margin: 2.25%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-video&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Video from last night of the Tuscaloosa Police aggressively arresting 2 guys outside their apartment. Very intense. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/RI50UFu1ta&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/RI50UFu1ta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Pete Pajor (@petepajor) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/petepajor/status/663502427513970688&quot;&gt;November 8, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;display: inline-block; margin: 2.25%;&quot;&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-video&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/VICE&quot;&gt;@vice&lt;/a&gt; 3rd video &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/tuscaloosapolicedepartment?src=hash&quot;&gt;#tuscaloosapolicedepartment&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tuscaloosa?src=hash&quot;&gt;#Tuscaloosa&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/police?src=hash&quot;&gt;#police&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/brutality?src=hash&quot;&gt;#brutality&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/makeitstop?src=hash&quot;&gt;#makeitstop&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/PhDCbNWdYx&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/PhDCbNWdYx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; John Jameson (@coyotehunter25) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coyotehunter25/status/663544355748257793&quot;&gt;November 9, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/09/alabama-student-beaten-tased-noise-complaint.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/09/alabama-student-beaten-tased-noise-complaint.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>tuscaloosa,</category>
        
        <category>bama,</category>
        
        <category>alabama,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police officer body cam shows him shooting suspect</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Towon Earl was arrested Tuesday morning after he injured three police officers when he put his vehicle in drive, striking two officers and injuring another that became stuck in the vehicle. Officer Raymond Harralson shot Earl in the right leg during the incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/crime/article43267758.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/crime/article43272885.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My editor, Stephanie Pedersen, pulled these videos from the Georgia Bureau of Investigation. I edited them for publication and we put them out. They quickly became some of the most-viewed videos in all of McClatchy. It’s easy to see why. The whole incident is absolutely crazy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/07/cpd-officer-shooting-bodycam.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/07/cpd-officer-shooting-bodycam.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>guns,</category>
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>video</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>See the Sibley Horticultural Center at Callaway Gardens for free before it closes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Callaway Gardens will admit all guests for free this Friday in honor of the birthday of founder Cason J. Callaway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be an organ concert from noon to 4 p.m. at the Ida Cason Callaway Memorial Chapel to mark the occasion, according to a release. The concert will be played on a custom-built Möller pipe organ in a chapel that was designed and built as a tribute to Ida.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.callawaygardens.com/events/2015-11-06&quot;&gt;day calendar&lt;/a&gt; on the website also lists a free birds of prey show featuring owls, hawks and other raptors at 10:30 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will also be a classic Southern buffet between 5 p.m. and 9 p.m. at The Plant Room Restaurant. Cost to attend is $25.95 per adult and $12.50 per child ages 6-10. Children 5 and under are free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The free admission comes just days before Callaway Gardens’ &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/business/article41968617.html&quot;&gt;planned closure&lt;/a&gt; of the Sibley Horticultural Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The closure of the Sibley Horticultural Center is a measure that allows us to focus on a better gardens experience and put the polish on another jewel, the Day Butterfly Center,” said William “Bill” Doyle III, president and CEO. “That work is already under way, with measurable progress by mid- to late-November. Guests should mark their calendars to visit this spring to see the new, colorful displays.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr. Cason’s Vegetable Garden has already been closed, apparently to be relocated. It and the Sibley Center have &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.callawaygardens.com/about-us/history/timeline&quot;&gt;long histories&lt;/a&gt; at Callaway Gardens, which was founded out of farm and forest lands in 1952 by Cason J. and Virginia Hand Callaway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Sibley Center is located on five ares and was built with private donations. It uses 300 tons of Tennessee fieldstone, 7,000 glass blocks and 26 folding doors. Each door is 24 feet tall and weighs 1,600 pounds. There is also a 22-foot waterfall with 350 gallons of water cascading downward each minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The facility, at one time marketed by Callaway Gardens as “one of the most advanced garden/greenhouse complexes in the world,” is about 22,000 square feet, with an additional 30,000 square feet of greenhouse production space. The complex, with floral and plant displays inside and out, underwent a $3.5 million renovation in 2003.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/04/callaway-gardens-free-day-close.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/04/callaway-gardens-free-day-close.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>opening,</category>
        
        <category>business,</category>
        
        <category>environment,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Cross needs blood during the holidays</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The American Red Cross is encouraging people around Columbus and Phenix City to donate blood during the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A seasonal decline in donations often occurs from Thanksgiving to New Year’s Day when donors get busy with family gatherings and travel,” a spokeswoman said in a release. “However, patients don’t get a holiday vacation from needing lifesaving transfusions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone who donates between Nov. 25 and Nov. 29 will receive a Red Cross mixing spoon and celebrity chef recipe set while supplies last.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Red Cross said donors of all blood types are needed, especially those with O-negative, B-negative, A-negative and AB blood. Anyone who would like to donate needs a blood donor card, driver’s license or two other forms of identification. You must be at least 17, weigh 110 pounds and be in “generally good health.” High school students and other donors 18 and younger may also have to meet “certain height and weight requirements.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make an appointment to donate blood, download the Red Cross Blood Donor App (Android and iPhone), visit the Red Cross’ website or call 1-800-733-2767.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The release also listed several blood donation opportunities at these times:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/16/2015: 11 a.m. - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/16/2015: 2 - 7 p.m., Baptist Tabernacle Church, 849 South Davis Road&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/17/2015: 11 a.m. - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/17/2015: 11:30 a.m. - 3:30 p.m., Department of Public Works, 1152 Cusseta Road&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/17/2015: 3 - 7 p.m., Webster County Schools, 7168 Washington St. Preston&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/18/2015: 12 - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/19/2015: 12 - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/20/2015: 8 a.m. - 2 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/21/2015: 7 a.m. - 2 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/21/2015: 12 - 5 p.m., LaGrange Mall, 1501 LaFayette Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/23/2015: 11 a.m. - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/24/2015: 11 a.m. - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/25/2015: 7 a.m. - 2 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/27/2015: 8 a.m. - 2 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/27/2015: 1 - 6 p.m., The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints, 4400 Reese Road&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/28/2015: 7 a.m. - 2 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;11/30/2015: 11 a.m. - 7 p.m., Columbus Blood Donation Center, 7490 Veterans Parkway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/03/red-cross-needs-donations.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/03/red-cross-needs-donations.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thanksgiving,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>health,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This family lost their home in a fire, but the community gave back</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the Robinson family, Halloween was Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anthony St. Pierre, a Columbus firefighter paramedic, &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/09/29/batman.html&quot;&gt;collected donations&lt;/a&gt; of toys, blankets and clothing for the family for the past month. On Halloween, he presented the family with the collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Robinsons have had a hard month. On Sept. 15, Tuesday, John Robinson’s mother passed away. Her funeral was on Friday. On Saturday, the Robinson’s rental trailer caught fire. Sunday was Robin’s fifth birthday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We lost it all,” John said. “Every bit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John said what wasn’t ruined by the fire was stolen when the family was living out of a motel. He said the “scavengers” took kitchen appliances, DVD players (only one worked) and a TV bought for $3 at a garage sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre said when he saw Raven Rose Robinson, 2, and Robin Renee Robinson, 5, he thought of his own children and wanted to give them a good Halloween. He originally planned to have the kids go to fire stations all over Columbus for a private trick-or-treat, but the Robinson parents John and Jessica decided it would be better to stay at fire station #4 on North Oakley Drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For their private Halloween, Robin and Raven dressed up as princesses. St. Pierre, a comic book fan, came as Batman. His friend Caitlin Norton drove in from Atlanta and dressed as Batgirl to help present the donations to the family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/incoming/article42072678.html/video-embed&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The oldest one, Robin, she almost started crying when she saw all of this,” Norton said. “Even Raven was starting to cry because all of the stuff was for them. That’s what it’s all about right there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robin and Raven got to play with dozens of toys donated by people as far away as Los Angeles and Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Pierre said news of the family’s plight spread over social media and inspired an outpouring of donations. He said he filled up one of the ambulances several times over with all the blankets and toys people donated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(This) gives our girls things they haven’t had for a month,” John said. “We appreciate it. It’s nice to see people willing to help.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to donate gently used goods or toys, drop them off at the fire station at 200 North Oakley Drive, Columbus, GA 31907.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/31/halloween-charity-batman.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/31/halloween-charity-batman.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>halloween,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>humaninterest,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ToDo this Halloween- Trunk-or-treat, Spooktacular and a Paw-rade</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t already carved your pumpkin, you only have a couple more days left to dig out those seeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is Saturday and there are numerous things going on around town for your fall festival pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trick-or-treat times in the area vary a little: Columbus 6-9 p.m., Phenix City 5:30-8:30 p.m., Fort Benning 6-8 p.m. and Hamilton 5-7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, be careful crossing the streets if you’re out asking for candy. Drivers, be wary of kids and keep an eye out especially when it gets dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some Halloween events going on in the area. If we’re missing any, email me at knazario@ledger-enquirer.com and I’ll add it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;friday&quot;&gt;FRIDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ZOMBIE ZIP: Zip over the Chattahoochee and enjoy two towers full of terrors. 10 percent of proceeds benefit the Springer Opera House. Friday and Saturday. $40, 8 p.m. 1000 Bay Ave. Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NORTH HIGHLAND PUMPKIN PATCH: Runs through Saturday. Call 706-561-7777 for group reservations. $2 and up per pumpkin, 10 a.m.-dark Friday and Saturday. 7300 Whittlesey Blvd Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUMMERVILLE PUMPKIN PATCH: Runs through Saturday. Free, 1-7 p.m. 1201 32nd St., Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JACK-O-LANTERN LANE: Come see the beautiful country setting, pumpkin patch, fresh corn meal, train rides, pony rides and farm animals. Admission includes a wagon ride and pumpkin, but other activities cost extra. $7, Noon-5 p.m. Friday, 9 a.m.-6 p.m. Saturday. 18151 Veterans Memorial Parkway, LaFayette, Ala. 36862&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GEORGIA PUMPKIN PATCH: Celebrate the harvest with corn stalks, decorative gourds, terra-cotta pumpkins, marigolds, mums, autumn merchandise, and every pumpkin related food you can imagine. Free, 8 a.m.-6 p.m. Friday and Saturday. 9616 Fortson Road Fortson, Ga. 31808&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALL HALLOWS EVE: Columbus Public Library will host family fun with movies and treats in the auditorium. There is limited space. Free, 3-6 p.m. 3000 Macon Road, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL AT THE Y: D.A. Turner YMCA will host a festival with a treat trail, pumpkin carving contest, costume contest, face painting, arts and crafts, carnival games and a bounce house. No masks or weapons. Free, 4 p.m. 4384 Warm Springs Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ROCK-O-WEEN: Treadstone Climbing Gym will have candy, prizes, a costume party, games and black light climbing. $25 per person, $5 off with costume, 6-10 p.m. 4209 Milgren Road, Suite 7. Columbus 31907&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLELUJAH NIGHT: New Birth Outreach Church will have hay rides, face painting, a wing-eating contest, cake walk, cotton handy, hula-hoop contest and free food. Free, 6:30-8:30 p.m. 10107 Veterans Parkway, Midland, Ga. 31820&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRUNK OR TREAT: Rose Hill Church is having a night of family fun with dinner, games, hay rides and more. Free, 6:30 p.m. 7479 Old Moon Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE ROCKY HORROR SHOW: See the spooky rock-n-roll musical that inspired the cult movie. Also plays at 7:30 p.m. and 11 p.m. Saturday. $20 for adults, $17 for seniors/active duty military/groups of 10+, $12 for children 12 and under. 7:30 p.m. 6 W. 10th St. Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN HOTEL HORROR: See the dinner theater show that will have you guessing who the villain is to win a special prize. Guests are encouraged to come in costume and compete for best costume. Two audience roles will be assigned each evening to the most promising actors as well. Runs at the same times on Saturday. $30, with discounts for groups, 12 a.m. and 9:30 p.m. 8701 Garrett Road Midland, Ga. 31820&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;saturday&quot;&gt;SATURDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OPERATION TROOP TREATS: Kool Smiles Columbus is encouraging children to bring their Halloween candy to any area Kool Smiles dental offices in exchange for a toy. The candy will be sent in care packages to U.S. soldiers overseas as part of Operation Gratitude. Children will receive one toy for every 25 pieces of unopened candy in its original packaging. Limit three toys per child. Runs through Nov. 4. Free, All Day, 4519 Woodruff Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SPOOKTACULAR HALLOWEEN FESTIVAL: A free and safe environment for children to enjoy an afternoon of ghosts and goblins, spooky activities, candy and lots of fun. There will be a costume contest. Free, 2-4 p.m. 25 W. 10th St., Ste 4, Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRUNK OR TREAT: Candy, rides, inflatables, games, a petting zoo, pony rides and a rock wall. $5, 5-7 p.m. 7300 Whittlesey Blvd. Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN AT BUTTS MILL FARM: Celebrate Halloween at Butts Mill Farm. The first 100 kids will receive a free pumpkin to collect candy, which will be given out for free by staff throughout the farm. There will be carnival games, a bonfire, carnival food and a free mini-pumpkin to paint for the first 50 kids. $10, 10 a.m.-4 p.m., 2280 Butts Mill Road, Pine Mountain, Ga. 31822&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BROADWAY PAW-RADE: The fourth annual Broadway Paw-rade at Market Days raises money for Paws Humane and the Columbus Animal Care &amp;amp; Control Center. There will be a costume contets for the dogs and a live DJ. $10, 9:30 a.m. Broadway, in the median in front of The Loft&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOT SO SPOOKY HALLOWEEN FESTIVAL: The Rock Ranch will have magic shows, a children’s costume contest, pet costume contest, trick-or-treating, the Frisbee dog state championship, a pumpkin cannon and a magician. $15, 10 a.m.-8 p.m. 5020 Barnesville Highway, The Rock, Ga. 30285&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SUMMERVILLE UMC FALL FESTIVAL: Summerville United Methodist Church is hosting a Fall Festival every Saturday during October. This week will have games, inflatables, baked goods, a pumpkin patch and a huge corn bin. Games and inflatables are free. $1 per person for groups, 10 a.m.-2 p.m. 1201 32nd St., Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FARM HOUSE PUMPKIN PATCH: Take a hay ride over to the pumpkin field and enjoy lunch with fall activities. Price not listed, 10 a.m., 469 Farmhouse Road, Ellerslie, Ga. 31807&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL: Redeemer Lutheran Church will have a Fall Festival with carnival games, a bounce house, food, fall crafts, a cupcake walk and Trunk or Treat. Bring a canned good to support Feeding the Valley. Free, 11 a.m.-2 p.m. 4700 Armour Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN STORYTIME: Barnes &amp;amp; Noble will feature Halloween stories and complete a craft. Children are encouraged to come in costume and parade around the store for trick-or-treat goodies. Free, 11 a.m.-12 p.m. 5555 Whittlesey Blvd No. 1800, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK-OR-TREAT AROUND THE LIBRARY: Come hear not-so-scary stories at the Columbus Public Library. Free, 2-4 p.m. 3000 Macon Road, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BLOCK PARTY: There will be a free block party behind the Huddle House with free food, refreshments, giveaways, and free candy for children. Free, 2-4 p.m. 1811 Victory Drive, Suite 3 Columbus 31901&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLELUJAH FESTIVAL: Mt. Zion UMC will have games, a costume contest, Trunk or Treat, a cake walk, inflatables and Elsa and Anna from “Frozen.” Free, 3-5 p.m. 2616 Lee Road 243 Smiths Station, Ala. 36877&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK OR TREAT AT PUBLIX: Come to Publix to get a coloring sheet and candy. Free, 4-7 p.m. 3201 Macon Road Ste 201, Columbus 31906&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL FESTIVAL: Epworth UMC will have a festival with food, music, inflatables and Trunk or Treat. 4 p.m. 3763 U.S. 280, Phenix City 36867&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TRICK OR TRUNK: The Way Church will host a Trick or Trunk. Free, 1593 Lee Road 242 Smiths Station, Ala. 36877&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN AT THE SPEEDWAY: The East Alabama Motor Speedway will celebrate Halloween with trick-or-treating, face painting, balloon animals, and a costume contest. Free with price of admission, 5-7 p.m. 4238 U.S. 80 Phenix City 36869&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ARK IN THE PARK: Join Britt David Baptist Church for a safe, Christ-centered trick-or-treat alternative with candy, games, rides, inflatables, food and prizes. Free, 5:30-7:30 p.m. 5560 Armour Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HALLOWEEN BASH: Stop by Fuddruckers for a special Halloween party with live music from Johnny Kempt. Free kids’ meals for children 12 and under in costume. 6-9 p.m. 5524 Whitesville Road, Columbus 31904&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sunday&quot;&gt;SUNDAY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FALL BACK SERVICE AND FESTIVAL: Join RiverTown Church for a Fall Back Worship Service and festival with hay rides, a petting zoo, popcorn, a bake sale and barbecue. A $10 lunch includes chicken or pork, sides, bread and drinks. Proceeds support missions in Guatemala. $10, 6953 Schomburg Road, Columbus 31909&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/30/halloween-todo-events.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/30/halloween-todo-events.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>halloween,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eufaula latex plant to restart under Steve Harvey, Greg Calhoun</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Comedian Steve Harvey and Montgomery businessman Greg Calhoun are reopening a latex plant in Eufaula next year, according to Calhoun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We wanted to put people back to work,” Calhoun said. “It’s a blessed opportunity.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun, who has been friends with Steve Harvey for 15 years, said the two were interested in Eufaula because it has the only latex plant in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eufaula Mayor Jack Tibbs Jr. said the plant now known as Ameritex closed down in 2008 when it lost its contract with USAID producing condoms for AIDS prevention. Tibbs estimated that contract was 95 percent of the plant’s business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said he plans to have the factory produce mostly latex gloves for major organizations such as Wal-Mart, the Transportation Security Administration, poultry producers and hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said he’s already spoken with Rob Walton, chairman of Wal-Mart, who has indicated interest in buying gloves from the factory as part of the retailer’s initiative to move jobs back to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said he hopes to have the first two lines operational by January 2016 and the whole plant online in four phases through 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Calhoun said it was “nice to have Wal-Mart to start out with,” he doesn’t plan on having only one major customer like the plant did before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(Walton) didn’t want to be our only customer,” Calhoun said. “He wanted us to get out there and find others.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calhoun said the output from one line in Ameritex could supply Wal-Mart, leaving several others for different customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Bradley, director of economic development for the city of Eufaula, said there are about 10 people working on retooling the four production lines to make them ready to produce latex gloves instead of condoms. He said only one of the four was already set up to do gloves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tibbs said there is a great deal of excitement for the plant, which is estimated to bring 300 jobs over two years. Each line will require 65-70 people, plus supervisors, management and warehouse employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bradley said the plant will slowly staff up as more of it comes online. He estimates that 27 people will be working there on Jan. 4, 2016, and 100 by the end of 2016. By 2018, there should be 350 people hired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s a long, complicated process, but Mr. Harvey and Mr. Calhoun have a terrific vision for the future of latex,” Bradley said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tibbs said he was happy to see jobs returning to Alabama and especially Eufaula.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“(Harvey) can be a serious guy,” Tibbs said. “He wants to put people back to work.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;***STEVE HARVEY TALKING JOBS FOR EUFAULA***&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/&quot;&gt;Help Eufaula Alabama Live&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/helpeufaulaalabamalive/posts/980656351997870&quot;&gt;Friday, October 23, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/steve-harvey-eufaula-condom-factory-plant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/10/29/steve-harvey-eufaula-condom-factory-plant.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>eufaula,</category>
        
        <category>opening,</category>
        
        <category>business,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
