<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 16:24:27 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 16:24:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to &#39;Y&#39;allywood&#39; (also known as Columbus, Georgia)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If all goes well, Columbus is going into show business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus State, the Springer Opera House and the state of Georgia are starting a special program to train Georgians to work on the sets of movies and TV shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Springer artistic director Paul Pierce said film has become a $6 billion industry in Georgia because of the state’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/opinion/opn-columns-blogs/article29456854.html&quot;&gt;generous tax credits&lt;/a&gt;. With 157 feature films produced in this state in fiscal year 2015, Pierce said, there are more jobs in the movie industry than ever before. However, there aren’t enough Georgians to fill these jobs.&lt;style&gt;
#footnote_1 {
	-webkit-animation-duration: .3s;
	-moz-animation-duration: .3s;
	animation-duration: .3s;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;sup&gt;&lt;button class=&quot;fn_button&quot; onclick=&quot;showDiv()&quot; style=&quot;position: relative; left: 0px;&quot;&gt;1
&lt;span class=&quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot; id=&quot;footnote_1&quot; style=&quot;display: none;&quot;&gt;There is a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.boston.com/news/opinion/2015/03/06/what-wrong-with-film-industry-tax-incentives-they-don-work/wRzsGm3OegxBjDCgINEj9L/story.html&quot;&gt;major debate&lt;/a&gt; over whether these things actually work. I would love to explore that, but this story was already pushing it at a thousand words.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
	function showDiv() {
		if (document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
			== &quot;none&quot;) {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display 
				= &quot;inline&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.position 
				= &quot;absolute&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.top = &quot;30px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.right = &quot;0px&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.left = &quot;-120px&quot;;
		}
		else {
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).style.display = &quot;none&quot;;
			document.getElementById(&#39;footnote_1&#39;).className 
				= &quot;footnoting animated fadeIn&quot;;
		}
	}
&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Georgia just doesn’t have the volume of scenic carpenters, scene painters, set decorators, lighting electricians, grips, prop masters, audio engineers or wardrobe professionals to crew all these films,” Pierce said. “Jets are landing in Hartsfield-Jackson every day with film workers from other states who are going directly to work sites. Gov. Deal is determined to put a stop to that, and we are determined to help him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deal invited Pierce to bring the Georgia Film Academy to Columbus. In just four weeks, a task force with representatives from CSU, the Springer, Columbus Tech, Columbus CVB, the Columbus Film Office and the Muscogee County School district put together a plan to meet the need for film-trained workers, according to Richard Baxter, dean of the College of the Arts at Columbus State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In January, CSU will offer a six-credit hour class starting Jan. 11 training 60 students in the basics of the film business. The class will use the Springer facilities. When students have learned about working on a set and know some of the equipment, they’ll spend a second 12-credit hour class working at Pinewood Studios in Fayette County on an actual film.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baxter said students could put the credits toward their baccalaureate or take just those two semesters and leave with a certification. Students can take that certification to the Georgia Film Academy and get certified to work within a union on films anywhere in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“More and more film is coming to Georgia, and we’re happy to announce Columbus is going to be ground zero in the training of these new workers for these lucrative jobs,” Pierce said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSU will be one of only three schools in Georgia tasked by the Georgia Film Academy to offer these certifications (the other two are Clayton State University and Gwinnett Technical College).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baxter said the waiting list for this uncommon program is long enough that they’re working on a second section that will use Springer’s facilities on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the program will take advantage of Columbus’ capabilities to train students, working in most of Georgia’s film industry will take them outside the Chattahoochee Valley. There is no Columbus equivalent to the sound stages for movie-making like the ones in production in Effingham and Gwinnett Counties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We recognize this opportunity for Columbus means that we’re going to be training workers for the production studios outside of Columbus initially, but our hope is this cadre of talented students in the motion picture business will get the attention of those studios who will look to Columbus for their next project,” said Bill Murphy, executive vice president of economic development for the Greater Columbus Chamber of Commerce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kevin Flowers, a music producer better known as Kevin Gr8 Trakz Lamar, tentatively guessed Columbus could get its own sound stage within a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They’ve been talking about this for the last year or so,” he said. “It’s going to be taken care of.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flowers said he was interested in working with students from the program. He said he already uses the CSU orchestra for producing film scores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terrence Manns, an independent filmmaker who works in Columbus, said he’s used Columbus State students for his job as well. He told the Ledger-Enquirer he wouldn’t mind hiring people straight out of the new program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was thinking of taking the program myself,” Manns said. “As a filmmaker, you can never stop learning.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A little bit of learning could result in a big payoff. Pierce said the jobs are so lucrative that even an entry-level position could pay $45 per hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flowers confirmed the pay scale, saying he’s charged $100 per hour on some projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like other industries, the money depends on the specific job and hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Payden Evans is a senior at Auburn University who works in the film industry. He’s worked as an extra and production assistant on shows like “The Vampire Diaries” and “Sleepy Hollow” and movies in the “Divergent” series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans said as a production assistant, he makes about $120 for a 12-hour shift. He said salaries in the movie industry vary by department and whether the person is in a union. Union rules mandate things like time-and-a-half pay for hours worked past a certain point and double pay on Saturdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evans said it while a program like CSU’s is not mandatory for joining the movie business, it can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think it’s smart to have a working idea of set lingo and how things flow,” he said. “You don’t need it, but it’s not a bad idea. My learning curve was a lot steeper because I had a lot of lingo thrown at me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior, who graduates Saturday with a degree in media studies, said breaking into the industry was tough. He attributes his chance to a fraternity brother with a family friend in the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie industry is great for those who want to get in, Evans said. It just requires an incredible amount of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s not the glitz and the glamor that’s on the screen,” he said. “It’s early mornings and late nights. I was on set at 4 a.m. and I wouldn’t get off until 6 to 8 at night.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The job isn’t regular like a 9-5 either. Evans said working on a TV show could mean nine months of work. A movie could be anywhere from a few weeks to a few months, depending on the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To students who want to get into that business, Evans advised persistence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do what is asked of you and do more if you can,” Evans said. “People take note of hard work… Georgia is a great place to be if (film is) something you’re into. Go for it. The opportunity is there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Credit to the Columbus, Georgia Film Office for the title. They claim “industry insiders” call Georgia’s burgeoning film industry ‘Y’allywood.’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a highlight:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a big story for our area. Georgia’s film industry is big business. However, we need to ask who is getting the benefit of that business. CSU and Springer are selling this program on $45/hr for entry-level jobs, and that’s just not what everyone will get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I consider this a good story because it covers an important event while offering another perspective for some realism. Maybe these kids really will get $45/hr, I don’t know. But they do deserve to hear what it’s really like from someone who’s not trying to sell them an 18-credit hour class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/10/columbus-movie-training.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/10/columbus-movie-training.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movies,</category>
        
        <category>csu,</category>
        
        <category>columbus,</category>
        
        <category>georgia,</category>
        
        <category>education,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This song about Georgia Sen. Johnny Isakson is awful and amazing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Georgia Senator Johnny Isakson drew my attention this morning when he tweeted his thanks to a band for writing a song about… Sen. Johnny Isakson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Wow, never had a song written about me. Thanks &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/hashtag/PapaRazziAndThePhotogs?src=hash&quot;&gt;#PapaRazziAndThePhotogs&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;#39;m undeserving but flattered nonetheless. &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/SdPaMKVgOI&quot;&gt;https://t.co/SdPaMKVgOI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Johnny Isakson (@SenatorIsakson) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SenatorIsakson/status/672423470349832192&quot;&gt;December 3, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve linked another copy of the song below, and it is… something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p8f1ysdH3GQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The singer is an odd duck. From &lt;a href=&quot;http://noisey.vice.com/blog/This-Genius-Lunatic-Has-Recorded-16000-Songs-About-Everything-from-Poop-to-Ellen-Degeneres&quot;&gt;Vice&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Matt Farley is a guy in his mid-30s living in Northeastern Massachusetts. He runs an entertainment company called Motern Media that manages about 70 bands that together have recorded just over 16,000 songs. The thing is, he also plays in all of the bands and sings in all of the bands and is the only person in all of them. Motern Media is Matt Farley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This guy churns out an average of 20 songs per day. It’s all weird stuff designed to pick up people searching weird terms for very specific songs. He makes a little bit of money every time you search for a song about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-SLX_qO1uvQ&quot;&gt;knowing how to tie a tie&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBfX9ucGXNU&quot;&gt;how great Robert Downey, Jr. is&lt;/a&gt;. It works, too- &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/media/media-blog/2014/jan/29/spotify-how-a-busy-songwriter-youve-never-heard-of-makes-it-work-for-him&quot;&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt; said Farley makes $23,000 a year from his entire catalogue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This song about Johnny Isakson comes from &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/u.s.-senators/id954900502&quot;&gt;an album of songs about U.S. Senators&lt;/a&gt;. Why does that exist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why not?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/johnny-isakson-song.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/johnny-isakson-song.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>music,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mixed reaction among Columbus residents to women in combat</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Women are joining men on the front lines of combat, and some people in Columbus are okay with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An informal poll revealed support for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/article47724225.html#storylink=mainstage&quot;&gt;the decision&lt;/a&gt;, with a few qualifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Women should be allowed to do anything that they can,” said Margie Watson, of Columbus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Watson said she hopes the military holds men and women to the same standards and doesn’t change them just because women are allowed in combat positions. She said she was also concerned about the physical ability of women to fight on the frontlines because they are not as strong as men “for the most part.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob Manzi, who was visiting from Denver, said he could think of a few women who were strong enough to meet the combat standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I work out twice a day, five days a week, and some of the women [in the gym] are impressive,” Manzi said. “If they want to do it and they can do it, that’s great.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manzi said he supported the decision and would not change anything about it. He pointed to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/military/article39389271.html&quot;&gt;first three women to graduate Ranger School&lt;/a&gt; as an example of what female soldiers can do if given the opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ashley Meadows, a master’s student in history at Columbus State, said she approved of opening combat positions to women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is a huge, huge step,” she said. “It is equal to women earning the right to vote.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meadows qualified her support as well, citing concerns about physiology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are built different,” she said. “There’s no denying that one.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Meadows said she expected female soldiers would overcome physical limitations through training.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lester Mahone said he did not approve of women being on the front lines. He told the Ledger-Enquirer it would be better to keep them in non-combat support roles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s too dangerous for a woman,” he said. “It’s really not a lady thing. It’s not.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His wife Lisa Mahone agreed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let the men do the fighting,” she said. “We need our women out here to help our men.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/army-women-combat-reactions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/03/army-women-combat-reactions.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>rangerwomen,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opelika woman hikes more than 2,000 miles from Georgia to Maine</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auburn graduate and Opelika resident Jessica Mills recently completed a hike of 2,189.2 miles along the Appalachian Trail from Springer Mountain, Ga., to Mount Katahdin in Maine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;The Auburn Plainsman&lt;/a&gt; reported Mills’ trip, which began at Amicalola Falls State Park in Georgia on March 29. Mills told The Plainsman she planned to hike it in 2012 but took a job in Colorado instead. After returning to Auburn in the fall of 2014, she tackled the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“When Jessica left for the trail, I was naturally afraid for her safety,” said her mother Rhonda. “Although I would have felt better if she wasn’t starting out by herself, I knew she would soon make friends and wouldn’t be hiking alone for long.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills kept a journal along the trail, recording her thoughts in &lt;a href=&quot;http://homemadewanderlust.com/cross-the-line/&quot;&gt;text&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQhqmV26773qZhzqJz4VFcw&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. She has a great eye for capturing the local color in an area. It’s worth reading for anyone curious about the experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mills recommended hiking the trail to any Auburn student.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re going to be an expert at hanging a bear bag because you have so much experience throwing paper towel rolls,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theplainsman.com/article/2015/12/local-woman-completes-2189-2-mile-hike-from-georgia-to-maine&quot;&gt;Read the full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TSWTjQ0p3nU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/opelika-appalachian-trail.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>hiking,</category>
        
        <category>environment,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling &#39;politically incorrect&#39; T-shirts for charity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Harris County Sheriff Mike Jolley is selling T-shirts with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/news-columns-blogs/chuck-williams/article47197945.html&quot;&gt;the sign that broke the internet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For $12-19 (depending on size), you can buy a politically incorrect T-shirt with “Harris County Georgia” on the front and “WARNING: Harris County is politically incorrect. We say: Merry Christmas, God Bless America and In God We Trust. We salute our troops and our flag. If this offends you… LEAVE!” on the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Harris County &lt;a href=&quot;http://harris-county.com/pc/&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; selling the shirts said all profits from the sales will go to Jolley’s favorite charities, Georgia Sheriffs’ Youth Homes and Scott’s Miracle Riders. Buyers can also get the shirts from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Boutiqueonthesquare/&quot;&gt;Boutique on the Square&lt;/a&gt; in Hamilton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jolley’s decision to sell shirts showing his &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article46241055.html&quot;&gt;controversial sign&lt;/a&gt; drew a condemnation from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://americanhumanist.org/&quot;&gt;American Humanist Association&lt;/a&gt;, a group headquartered in Washington, D.C., which works to protects the rights of humanists, atheists and Americans who don’t believe in a god.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Far from being a politically incorrect joke, the Harris County sheriff’s sign and t-shirts are an egregious violation of the Establishment Clause [of the Constitution],” said Monica Miller, senior counsel at the Appignani Humanist Legal Center. “Many local citizens object to the divisive message of the sign and t-shirts, which send a disturbing message of intolerance.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Association asked Harris County stop selling the T-shirts on a government website and move the sign to private property.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AHA gave legal reasoning to support its claim that the original sign was unconstitutional in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://aha-files.s3.amazonaws.com/2/3b/6/5831/20151125_Harris_County_-_Georgia_Sheriff_Sign_-_AHA_Letter.pdf&quot;&gt;letter sent on Nov. 25&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If it truly offends someone, they’re more than welcome to leave,” Jolley &lt;a href=&quot;http://insider.foxnews.com/2015/11/27/georgia-sheriff-mike-jolley-proud-be-politically-incorrect&quot;&gt;told Fox &amp;amp; Friends&lt;/a&gt; in response to the AHA. “I spent 20 years in the Army to give everyone the right to disagree with me or anyone else. If they disagree, they can voice that opinion. But if it offends them, truly offends them, then maybe they’re in the wrong country.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/jolley-christmas-shirt.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>christianity,</category>
        
        <category>christmas,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check out these UFO reports from around the Chattahoochee Valley</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, there have been a half-dozen UFO sightings around Columbus and Phenix City over the past two years according to an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/webreports/ndxloc.html&quot;&gt;online database&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center collects anonymous reports from around the country on strange and unexplainable sights. They have reports of sightings going back to the ’60s, and from every state. We put together an infographic of reports from the Chattahoochee Valley over the last two years, as well as Alabama and Georgia for the previous seven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take all of this with a huge grain of salt&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; These are unconfirmed, anonymous reports about things that sound a lot like military aircraft. The CIA &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.popularmechanics.com/space/a3995/4304207/&quot;&gt;estimated&lt;/a&gt; that more than half of all UFO sightings in the ’50s and ’60s were actually secret U-2 and SR-71 spy planes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One British journalist who produced “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Mirage-Men-Adventure-Espionage-Psychological/dp/1602398003&quot;&gt;Mirage Men: An Adventure into Paranoia, Espionage, Psychological Warfare, and UFOs&lt;/a&gt;” said the government actually encouraged UFO theories and conspiracies to cover up experimental aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“UFO stories are used as a cover story for the flight-testing of experimental and clandestine aircraft,” &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.usnews.com/opinion/articles/2010/09/16/the-truth-behind-ufo-sightings-and-the-us-air-force&quot;&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; author Mark Pilkington. “If you look at the places where UFO sightings are frequent, they are also the places where the military tests its experimental aircraft.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_ufo_sightings-120&quot; title=&quot;UFO Sightings&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?Zer&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/ufo_sightings-120&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;UFO Sightings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National UFO Reporting Center was founded in 1974 by UFO investigator Robert J. Gribble. The Center’s primary purpose, according to its &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nuforc.org/General.html&quot;&gt;biography&lt;/a&gt;, is to record and document reports from individuals who have witnessed unusual or UFO-related events. Its data has been used by other outlets to create products like &lt;a href=&quot;http://metrocosm.com/ufo-sightings-map.html&quot;&gt;this US map of sightings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I considered trying to make excuses for the quality of this database but quickly realized that was impossible. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/02/chattahoochee-ufo-sightings.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>ufo,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sergeant in marshals honored for rushing into house fire while injured</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sgt. Kurt Weathered of the Muscogee County Marshals was honored with the department’s first-ever Medal of Bravery at the Government Center Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/1125_COLO_fire2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kevin Flowers, left, lost his home to a fire. Kurt Weatherd, right, said he rushed inside the home to make sure Flowers wasn&#39;t asleep inside.&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Kevin Flowers, left, lost his home to a fire. Kurt Weatherd, right, said he rushed inside the home to make sure Flowers wasn&#39;t asleep inside.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he was on his couch at home, recovering from surgery on his Achilles tendon and about to watch “Gunsmoke,” when he saw smoke coming from his neighbor’s house. He said he put his boot on his bad foot and &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/11/25/man-rushes-burning-house.html&quot;&gt;hopped across the street without crutches into the house&lt;/a&gt;. He said he was afraid his neighbor Kevin Flowers was asleep inside the burning house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are here because Sergeant Weathered saw the need to lay down his own life and go into a burning house to save the life of his friend and neighbor,” said Muscogee County Marshal Greg Countryman. “He did not know if he would come out of that burning house. This was a very heroic act.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For his bravery, Weathered received the Medal of Bravery. Countryman said the department has had the award but never given it before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We never do anything expecting to get anything in return,” Weathered said. “It means a lot to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he tried to open the door by smashing a window with his ASP baton. When he saw the door had a chain on it, he hopped in front of it, stood on his boot and used his good foot to smash open the front door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A quick search of the living room revealed a collapsing ceiling but not Flowers. Weathered ran back outside, got a flashlight from his wife Angela and went back into the house. He said he kicked down the bedroom door looking for Flowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My heart dropped because I thought he was on the bed,” Weathered said, choking up as he spoke at the ceremony. “He wasn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Weathered saw Flowers’ car was not in the garage, he left the house. Flowers told the Ledger-Enquirer he was at the bank at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just thank God for giving me the courage not to follow my mind saying, ‘Man, get out of here. It’s hot,’” Weathered said. “Thank god for my training. I’m just glad (Flowers) is safe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weathered said he was also glad to provide a &lt;a href=&quot;/2015/10/09/stickers.html&quot;&gt;positive example of public service&lt;/a&gt; to contrast with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/article46184715.html&quot;&gt;negative news about law enforcement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to do some good because that’s what you signed up for,” he said. “The badge that you wear don’t make you a god. It sets you out to be that example and be that one to help when someone’s in need.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/01/marshal-medal-bravery-fire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/12/01/marshal-medal-bravery-fire.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>localhero,</category>
        
        <category>fire,</category>
        
        <category>police,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hundreds fed at Valley Rescue Mission</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Volunteers and needy families filled the large white tent by Valley Rescue Mission on Thanksgiving to both give and be served.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just really wanted to serve the Lord,” said Kathy Hutto, who drove in from LaGrange to help. “He’s been really good to me lately and I wanted to serve Him.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mitzi Oxford, the Mission’s development director, estimates that they served more than 800 people at the tent. The women and children’s center, Damascus Way, also fed everyone at the shelter and delivered meals to more than 300 elderly shut-ins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event required more than 100 volunteers, donations from around the community and a great deal of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script id=&quot;infogram_0_thanksgiving_charity&quot; title=&quot;Thanksgiving charity&quot; src=&quot;//e.infogr.am/js/embed.js?y1o&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;width:100%;padding:8px 0;font-family:Arial;font-size:13px;line-height:15px;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am/thanksgiving_charity&quot; style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot;&gt;Thanksgiving charity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a style=&quot;color:#989898;text-decoration:none;&quot; href=&quot;https://infogr.am&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Create your own infographics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masterbuilt smoked more than 100 turkeys so the Downtown Rotary Club could de-bone them. Summerville Road Baptist Church delivered desserts, and St. Luke School made the table centerpieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abigail Pritchett, 10, came with her grandparents Christopher and Debbie Kearns from Ellersly to help serve others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just love to see their happy faces,” Pritchett said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hutto agreed, calling it “a worthwhile trip.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/valley-rescue-mission-thanksgiving.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/valley-rescue-mission-thanksgiving.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thanksgiving,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>charity,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lonely, poor and addicted invited to charitable Thanksgiving</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Trevor Morris just wanted to help some people for Thanksgiving. On Monday, he posted to Facebook that his restaurant, the Trevioli Artisan Pasta Company, would close to the public and instead open to people who needed a good Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;fb-root&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(d, s, id) {  var js, fjs = d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0];  if (d.getElementById(id)) return;  js = d.createElement(s); js.id = id;  js.src = &quot;//connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3&quot;;  fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js, fjs);}(document, &#39;script&#39;, &#39;facebook-jssdk&#39;));&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fb-post&quot; data-href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot; data-width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;fb-xfbml-parse-ignore&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote cite=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trevioli will be closed to the public this Thursday, November 26th. Conversely, we will be opening our doors to the less...&lt;/p&gt;Posted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Trevioli-artisan-pasta-company-648844985150099/&quot;&gt;Trevioli artisan pasta company&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1189041907797068&amp;amp;id=648844985150099&amp;amp;substory_index=0&quot;&gt;Monday, November 23, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post, which Facebook said was viewed by more than 50,000 people, attracted around a dozen customers and 20-25 volunteers in the first hour. The event was Thursday from 3 p.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company gave away food donated by groups around the Valley. Morris estimated he could feed up to 500 with everything he had received. He said he wasn’t sure what to do with the extra food, but would probably give it to another charity or hand it out to the needy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the first time Morris has tried something like this charitable Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said it was just something good he wanted to try, especially after experiencing the other end of charity as a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There was a time in my life when I was on the other side of the coin, when I was in line to get a free meal,” Morris said. “I was thankful to whoever did it. So I feel like if you can, you should.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The restaurant owner said he grew up in a family with a lot of kids and little money. Welfare, food stamps and free lunches at school were what Morris said got his family by. In a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/local/article29435938.html&quot;&gt;Job Spotlight from March 2015&lt;/a&gt;, he also told the Ledger-Enquirer his upbringing included a mother addicted to drugs and his own depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I remember that there was a local bakery that would find needy families like ours and they would bring stuff by all the time,” Morris said. “I always thought that was super cool as a kid.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Natalie Blackwell, 26, said she volunteered to help the dinner as part of a joint decision with her mother. Her brother is in Atlanta and her mother is in South Carolina and they could not get together for Thanksgiving. Instead, Blackwell and her mother decided to do charity for the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s the whole purpose of Thanksgiving,” Blackwell said. “What better way is there to give back?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Morris said he asked for the lonely and anxious to visit as well because of the problems associated with the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is the time of the year where your suicide rate goes up,” he said. “If there’s a chance that somebody came in today who needed just one more day of being around people to save them from going over the edge or relapsing or suicide or whatever, it would be so awesome if we could be something that prevents that from happening.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/trevioli-thanksgiving-meal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/trevioli-thanksgiving-meal.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>thanksgiving,</category>
        
        <category>holidays,</category>
        
        <category>charity,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime briefs for 11/26/15</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;An unknown suspect robbed the Mystik Gas Station at 645 Brown Ave., according to a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police said a young black man in a black hoodie with a white emblem and red mask, blue gloves, dark jeans and black and white shoes entered through the east-facing door. The report said the suspect used a black semi-automatic handgun to rob the store between 6 p.m. and 6:18 p.m. Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police did not list what was taken and are still investigating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;man-arrested-for-possession-of-crack-cocaine-and-pills&quot;&gt;Man arrested for possession of crack cocaine and pills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- Imports an image and styles it properly, with caption if 
included. --&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;imgRight capbox &quot; style=&quot;overflow: hidden;&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img class=&quot;inline capped &quot; src=&quot;/blog/assets/gardner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Antoine Gardner, 31&quot; /&gt;
	
		&lt;div class=&quot;cap&quot;&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Antoine Gardner, 31&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
	&lt;hr /&gt;
	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police arrested a man for possession of multiple types of drugs, a report said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several officers were at 947 Illges Road in an attempt to locate a wanted person. Police said at the residence they found .1 grams of crack cocaine (street value $10) and 5 Zolpidem Tartrate pills, also known as Ambien (street value $50).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Antoine Gardner, 31, was arrested and charged with possession of Schedule IV and II drugs and possession of a Walther .22 pistol, the report said. Police are not planning a follow-up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;police-4-year-old-girl-molested&quot;&gt;Police: 4-year-old girl molested&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police responded to a call about an alleged molestation of a 4-year-old girl, according to a report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victim’s mother called police around 1 p.m. Wednesday to report an incident that happened between 8 p.m. Nov. 20 and 8 p.m. Nov. 22, according to police. The report does not list any suspects, only that the assailant was not a stranger and the incident occurred somewhere on Avery Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The case remains under investigation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chevy-malibu-reported-stolen-from-woodruff-farm-road&quot;&gt;Chevy Malibu reported stolen from Woodruff Farm Road&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A car was stolen in the 3000 block of Woodruff Farm Road, according to a police report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Columbus police said a gold four-door 2007 Chevy Malibu with the temporary tag 14944327 was stolen between 12 a.m. and 7 a.m. Wednesday morning. The report does not list how much the car is worth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police are investigating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/drug-arrest-cocaine-pills-robbery.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2015/11/26/drug-arrest-cocaine-pills-robbery.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>crime,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
