<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories by Kyle Nazario</title>
    <description>I built this website to store my previous work, some of which has vanished since publication. News stories tend not to have an incredibly long lifespan, especially on the internet. This site is a way to preserve my old stories and show my talents to  employers. Please feel free to contact me with any questions.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kylenazario.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 23:33:22 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 23:33:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Almost every Ryan&#39;s in Alabama has shut down</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan’s buffets closed across Alabama Sunday. From &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/birmingham/index.ssf/2016/03/ryans_apparently_no_long_on_me.html#incart_most-commented_opinion_article&quot;&gt;AL.com&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Ryan’s locations in Gardendale, Tuscaloosa, Cullman, and Prattville were closed Sunday, according to a statement from the spokesperson for Buffets, LLC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The site said it was able to confirm that the Ryan’s at 2301 S. McKenzie Street in Foley, Ala., is open as of 11 a.m. Tuesday, so there is at least one operating in the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shutdowns come after the Ryan’s on Manchester Expressway was &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/02/04/ryans-manchester-expressway-close-down.html&quot;&gt;closed without warning last month&lt;/a&gt;. Vice president of development for Ovation Brands (a parent company of Ryan’s) Peter Donbavand said at the time closing stores would help stabilize the company’s performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We know that these decisions are not easy,” he said in the statement. “However, we strongly believe that this direction is best for the long-term health of all brands.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food Management Partners acquired Ovation Brands in August 2015. Donbavand said one parent company of Ryan’s, Buffets LLC, is filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy to strengthen its business through restructured debt and fewer weak restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The Chapter 11 filing is prompted by the discovery of liabilities, or alleged liabilities, that we believe were not disclosed in our negotiations,” Donbavand said. “We intend to investigate the propriety of the disclosures, and intend to consult with our counsel regarding any remedies we may have.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/08/ryans-alabama-closing-ovation-bankruptcy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/08/ryans-alabama-closing-ovation-bankruptcy.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>closing,</category>
        
        <category>business,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Tim Cook&#39;s Alabama upbringing affects his leadership</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook has a conflicted relationship with his roots. Cook is a Southerner, raised in Robertsdale, Ala., and an Auburn graduate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite being the head of the world’s most valuable company, his hometown doesn’t seem enthusiastic about recognizing him. The Washington Post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2016/03/07/in-rural-alabama-the-activist-roots-of-apples-tim-cook/?tid=sm_tw&quot;&gt;investigated&lt;/a&gt; and found a town with few fond memories of the man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[Cook’s] name is not noted on the town’s welcome signs along the main drag, Route 59. There’s nothing in the local chamber’s brochures, and the local paper rarely has anything about him. His old high school keeps a glass case celebrating former NFL running back Joe Childress, Class of 1952, but not the leader of the world’s most valuable company, Class of 1978. […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Cook never sought out attention and many here are quietly proud of him, but Ousley suspects the lack of recognition is also tied to Cook’s prominent positions on sensitive social issues. Cook, who is gay, has advocated for gay rights. He once criticized Alabama for its lack of progress in a speech at the state capitol in Montgomery. He also helped fund a gay rights initiative in the Deep South.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“That was offensive to a lot of people down here,” Ousley said. One local pastor even vowed to stop using his iPad because of the Apple leader’s views.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cook, 55, has drawn Apple into a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/nation-world/national/article63826002.html&quot;&gt;heated battle&lt;/a&gt; with the FBI over the encrypted iPhone of one of the San Bernardino shooters. The FBI has demanded Apple help them unlock the phone. Apple has refused, calling it a danger to encryption and too strong a precedent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Post profile, Cook’s upbringing in a “tiny town midway between Mobile and Pensacola” helped develop his sense of right and wrong, which helped dictate the current encryption battle. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2016/03/07/in-rural-alabama-the-activist-roots-of-apples-tim-cook/?tid=sm_tw&quot;&gt;whole profile&lt;/a&gt; is worth reading for anyone curious about how a Southern boy from the middle of Alabama ended up at the head of the world’s most valuable company and opposite the FBI.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/07/tim-cook-robertsdale-alabama.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/07/tim-cook-robertsdale-alabama.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>encryption,</category>
        
        <category>apple,</category>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>alabama,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Daughtry and Lecrae to perform free at Fort Benning</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Daughtry and Lecrae will perform at Fort Benning’s Wetherby Field on May 7. The event is free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daughtry is a rock band named for 2006 “American Idol” finalist Chris Daughtry. They’ve won four American Music Awards and sold 8 million albums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lecrae is a Christian hip hop artist whose 2008 album “Rebel” became the first Christian hip hop album to reach number one of the “Billboard” chart. He was the first rapper to win the BET’s Best Gospel Artist Award in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Spring into Summer Concert will be opened by Brooke Eden at 6 p.m., with gates opening at 5 p.m. Eden is known for his hits “Daddy’s Money” and “American Dreamin’.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Wetherby field is an open-air venue, Fort Benning staff recommend lawn chairs and blankets. Only service animals are allowed. They do not permit all other pets, weapons, professional video equipment and smoking in event areas. Visitors cannot bring food or coolers onto the field, though food and beverages will be available for purchase on site. Directions to Wetherby Field are on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.benningmwr.com/directions/&quot;&gt;Fort Benning’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/07/daughtry-lecrae-fort-benning-concert.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/07/daughtry-lecrae-fort-benning-concert.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>fortbenning,</category>
        
        <category>music,</category>
        
        <category>arts,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kick-Six named most iconic SEC play of the decade by ESPN</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ESPN’s SEC writers put together a &lt;a href=&quot;http://espn.go.com/blog/sec/post/_/id/115004/counting-down-the-most-iconic-sec-plays-of-the-past-decade-nos-1-5&quot;&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; of the 25 biggest, most iconic plays in Southeastern Conference football in the last decade. Number one was Chris Davis’ game-winning 109-yard kick return to beat Alabama in the 2013 Iron Bowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Would you expect any other play than this one to be No. 1? This play had it all: the Iron Bowl rivalry, national championship implications and the drama of an as-time-expired finish. By now you know how it went: Alabama kicker Adam Griffith left a 57-yard field goal attempt short, Auburn’s Chris Davis caught it nine yards deep in the end zone and began running. And running. And running some more, 109 yards to the opposite end zone to give the Tigers a 34-28 win over the Crimson Tide. It’s a play that will live on forever in Iron Bowl – and college football – lore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Auburn also took the number-three spot with “The Prayer at Jordan-Hare,” their other crazy win from 2013 that happened just two weeks before the Iron Bowl. On fourth-and-18 with just 36 seconds left, Nick Marshall launched a Hail Mary to Ricardo Louis, who was surrounded by Georgia defenders. The ball bounced off a Bulldog helmet and into Louis’ hands for the win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As pointed out by &lt;a href=&quot;http://yellowhammernews.com/sports/kick-six-decades-most-iconic-play/&quot;&gt;Yellowhammer&lt;/a&gt;, 13 of ESPN’s top 25 plays involve Auburn or Alabama. The Crimson Tide claimed the number four, six and seven spots in the top 10 alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://espn.go.com/blog/sec/post/_/id/115004/counting-down-the-most-iconic-sec-plays-of-the-past-decade-nos-1-5&quot;&gt;whole list&lt;/a&gt; is worth a read. The ESPN writers have a long memory and do a great job of pulling up highlight moments from 2007 or bowl games you may not have watched.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/04/kick-six-auburn-iconic-espn.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/04/kick-six-auburn-iconic-espn.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>aufb,</category>
        
        <category>bama,</category>
        
        <category>cfl,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gallery- Four homes around Columbus a millionaire could buy today</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Quick gallery of nice houses around town I put together. Click the link below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/03/houses-columbus-millionaire-gallery.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/03/houses-columbus-millionaire-gallery.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>realestate,</category>
        
        <category>living,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s hard to find benefits to Americans&#39; diet, Auburn professor says</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael Greene, an assistant professor of nutrition at Auburn University, is worried about the effects and growing popularity of the Western (North America, Europe, etc) diet. He and other researchers presented their work at Boshell Research Day on Feb. 26. From an interview with the university press:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I’m concerned about the next generation in our contry and for other countries that aspire to become more Westernized,” said Greene. “There are health consequences that come with Westernization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We [are] very focused on the maladies. It’s hard to find any positives associated with consuming this diet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greene said his research found that a Western diet with high amounts of fat and sugar water (like you’d find in soda) could cause advanced liver disease in mouse models of obesity. He told the university press that eating high amounts of red meat, refined sugars, saturated fat and few fibers plays a role in diseases of the gut, brain, body fat or liver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The research fair also included studies about the effects of genetics and meal timing on weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Healthy food has been a concern for Columbus recently, with our city hosting the 19th annual Georgia Organics Conference to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/latest-news/article62040937.html&quot;&gt;focus on locally grown and organic food&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ocm.auburn.edu/newsroom/news_articles/2016/03/assistant-professor,-students-investigation-of-western-diet-presented-at-boshell-research-day.htm&quot;&gt;Read the full interview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/02/western-diet-benefit-bad-auburn.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/02/western-diet-benefit-bad-auburn.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>nutrition,</category>
        
        <category>health,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinion- Alabama government can&#39;t be trusted to police itself</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;AL.com columnist John Archibald has never held back from criticizing the state government of Alabama, but his most recent column is exceptional even by those standards. Archibald excoriated Gov. Robert Bentley for punishing state officials who assisted in the prosecution of Alabama House Speaker and Auburn representative Mike Hubbard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But I believe [the ALEA corruption scandal is] a diversion. It is too fast. Too convenient. I believe, on the eve of a critical Mike Hubbard hearing, there is more here than meets the eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I believe laws have been broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And I believe in my heart and soul that the FBI needs to examine Alabama and this whole process with the thickest magnifying glass they have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Alabama, at this point, cannot be trusted to police itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/opinion/index.ssf/2016/03/hubbard_case_reeks_all_the_way.html#incart_river_home&quot;&gt;Read the full column&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/02/alabama-government-mike-hubbard-trial.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/03/02/alabama-government-mike-hubbard-trial.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Upatoi Creek bridge to undergo construction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Repairs on the northbound bridge over Upatoi Creek on I-185 will affect traffic starting March 5, according to a release from Fort Benning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The release said concrete barriers will go up Saturday to control traffic, with construction starting Monday. Traffic will be restricted to one lane in each direction over the southbound bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This phase of construction is expected to take four months, according to the release, which also recommends using alternate routes. The speed limit in the construction zone is 35 miles per hour.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/29/upatoi-creek-bridge-closing-fort-benning.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/29/upatoi-creek-bridge-closing-fort-benning.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>psa,</category>
        
        <category>fortbenning,</category>
        
        <category>army,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>briefs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NFL legend, Alabama QB Bart Starr was brutally hazed in college</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alabama fans with long memories may remember Bart Starr, the hall of Fame quarterback who played for the Tide and the Green Bay Packers. His wife Cherry Starr recently spoke with AL.com to explain the real reason behind Bart’s back injuries:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“[H]is back was never right after [the hazing],” Cherry Starr said. “It was horrible. It was not a football injury. It was an injury sustained from hazing. His whole back all the way up to his rib cage looked like a piece of raw meat. The bruising went all the way up his back. It was red and black and awful looking. It was so brutal.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starr’s injuries played a critical role in Alabama history. As the story notes, coach Harold “Red” Drew lost his star quarterback for most of the season in the fall of 1954. When Drew was fired that November, a “timeline of events” was put into motion that ended with Paul “Bear” Bryant as Alabama’s coach in 1957.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/sports/index.ssf/2016/02/nfl_legend_bart_starr_was_vict.html#incart_big-photo&quot;&gt;Read the full story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/29/nfl-alabama-bart-starr-hazing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/29/nfl-alabama-bart-starr-hazing.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>bama,</category>
        
        <category>cfl,</category>
        
        <category>sports,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trump leads other Republican candidates in Georgia, Alabama</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg Politics published a poll conducted by Purple Strategies that found Donald Trump led the other Republican candidates in Southern states due to vote by March 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An online Bloomberg Politics poll shows the billionaire is backed by 37 percent of likely Republican presidential primary voters in the seven states surveyed, while Senators Marco Rubio of Florida and Ted Cruz of Texas are tied at 20 percent. […]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The findings demonstrate the broad-based nature of Trump’s support and how primary voters – even conservatives and evangelicals who might find issues with his personal history – have accepted him, making it harder for his rivals to take him down.
Georgia and Alabama are considered to have some of the most conservative and religious voters in the country. Early in the campaign season pundits expected Trump, a twice-divorced New Yorker, to not be able to connect with religious voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Bloomberg poll, Trump did not do as well on questions of being a committed Christian as he did on those of terrorism and having a vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“These voters rate Trump as the least conservative and the least committed Christian of the three top candidates, and yet he still leads,” said pollster Doug Usher, who led the survey. “He’s turning everything we thought we knew about Republican primary voters on its head.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only presidential candidate to visit Columbus so far is Ted Cruz, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ledger-enquirer.com/news/politics-government/election/article30538233.html&quot;&gt;who came last year&lt;/a&gt;. Our state senator, Josh McKoon, is an &lt;a href=&quot;http://wrbl.com/2015/11/11/poll-state-senator-mckoon-weighs-in-on-gop-presidential-debate/&quot;&gt;avid Ted Cruz supporter&lt;/a&gt;. Stay with the Ledger-Enquirer for more interviews soon with local figures who will weigh in on the presidential race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bloomberg.com/politics/articles/2016-02-25/bloomberg-politics-super-tuesday-sec-primary-republican-poll&quot;&gt;Read the full Bloomberg report here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[h/t &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2016/02/donald_trump_dominating_alabam.html#incart_river_home_pop&quot;&gt;al.com&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/26/trump-alabama-georgia-lead-poll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kylenazario.com/2016/02/26/trump-alabama-georgia-lead-poll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>trump,</category>
        
        <category>rprimary16,</category>
        
        <category>elections,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>ledger,</category>
        
        <category>viral</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
